[
  {
    "category": "Americanisms",
    "question": "Britains say 'tarmac'; Americans say ??????.",
    "answer": "runway"
  },
  {
    "category": "Analogies",
    "question": "Analogy: 'Ancient' is to 'old' as 'recent' is to ????????.",
    "answer": "current"
  },
  {
    "category": "Analogies",
    "question": "Bull - cow as fox - ??????????.",
    "answer": "vixen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Analogies",
    "question": "Goose - geese as passerby - ???????????.",
    "answer": "passersby"
  },
  {
    "category": "Anatomy",
    "question": "Your ???? holds your head to your shoulders.",
    "answer": "neck"
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts",
    "question": "In what field of study would you find \"flying buttresses\"?",
    "answer": "architecture"
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts",
    "question": "The study of building design is ????????????.",
    "answer": "architecture"
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts",
    "question": "This statue was found on the Greek island of Melos in 1820.",
    "answer": "Venus de Milo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts",
    "question": "Three main types of Greek columns are Doric, Ionic, and ??????????.",
    "answer": "Corinthian"
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts",
    "question": "What Dutch master painted 64 self-portraits?",
    "answer": "Rembrandt"
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts",
    "question": "Where is the Louvre located?",
    "answer": "Paris"
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts",
    "question": "Who painted the Mona Lisa?",
    "answer": "Leonardo #da Vinci#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astrology",
    "question": "What is the only sign in the zodiac which doesn't represent a living thing?",
    "answer": "Libra"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astrology",
    "question": "Which month has a diamond as a birthstone?",
    "answer": "April"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "A heavenly body moving under the attraction of the Sun and consisting of a nucleus and a tail is a(n) ?????.",
    "answer": "comet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "Does Uranus have an aurora?",
    "answer": "yes"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "From 1979 until 2000 the most distant planet from the earth was ???????.",
    "answer": "Neptune"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "How many planets are there in our solar system?",
    "answer": "nine"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(nine|9)",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "If you're in the northern hemisphere, Polaris, the North Star, can be found by looking which direction?",
    "answer": "north"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "Name the largest planet in the solar system.",
    "answer": "Jupiter"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "Name the second-largest planet in the solar system.",
    "answer": "saturn"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "Our galaxy is commonly known as the ????????.",
    "answer": "Milky Way"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "The Big Dipper is part of what constellation?",
    "answer": "Ursa Major"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "The North Star is also known as ???????.",
    "answer": "Polaris"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "The fourth planet from the sun is ????.",
    "answer": "Mars"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "The name for the group of stars which form a hunter with a club and shield is ?????.",
    "answer": "Orion"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "The planet closest to the sun is ???????.",
    "answer": "Mercury"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "The spiral galaxy nearest ours is the ????????? galaxy.",
    "answer": "Andromeda"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "The tides on the earth's oceans are actually created by gravitational pull from the ????.",
    "answer": "Moon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "This cluster of stars is also known as the Seven Sisters.",
    "answer": "Pleiades"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "This comet appears every 76.3 years.",
    "answer": "Comet #Halley#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "This planet's diameter is most equal to that of the earth's.",
    "answer": "Venus"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "What does \"Ursa Major\" mean in everyday English?",
    "answer": "great bear"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "What is the astronomical name for a group of stars?",
    "answer": "constellation"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "What is the name for the theoretical end-product of the gravitational collapse of a massive star?",
    "answer": "black hole"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "What is the name used to describe the \"minor planets\"?",
    "answer": "asteroids"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "What is the ocean of air around the earth called?",
    "answer": "atmosphere"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "What is the proper name for falling stars?",
    "answer": "meteors"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "What is the term for the path followed a by a small body around a massive body in space?",
    "answer": "orbit"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "What phenomenon is caused by the gravitational attraction of the moon?",
    "answer": "tides"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "What planet boasts the Great Red Spot?",
    "answer": "Jupiter"
  },
  {
    "category": "Bet you don't know ;-)",
    "question": "The two sexes of humans are male and ???????",
    "answer": "female"
  },
  {
    "category": "Biochemistry",
    "question": "This poisonous, oily liquid occurs in tobacco leaves.",
    "answer": "nicotine"
  },
  {
    "category": "Biochemistry",
    "question": "This protein makes the blood red in color.",
    "answer": "Haemoglobin"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Ha?emoglobin",
    "category": "Biology",
    "question": "Every human has one of these on their tummies.",
    "answer": "navel"
  },
  {
    "category": "Biology",
    "question": "How many large holes are in your head?",
    "answer": "seven"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(seven|7)",
    "category": "Biology",
    "question": "This complex substance makes up all living things.",
    "answer": "protoplasm"
  },
  {
    "category": "Biology",
    "question": "What is normal body temperature for an adult human (in degrees fahrenheit)?",
    "answer": "98.6"
  },
  {
    "category": "Botany",
    "question": "The practice of joining the parts of two plants to make them grow as one is called ????????.",
    "answer": "grafting"
  },
  {
    "category": "Botany",
    "question": "These flowerless plants grow on bare rocks and tree stumps.",
    "answer": "lichen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Botany",
    "question": "This fruit has its seeds on the outside.",
    "answer": "strawberry"
  },
  {
    "category": "Botany",
    "question": "This term means 'cone-bearing trees'.",
    "answer": "conifers"
  },
  {
    "category": "Botany",
    "question": "What fruit bear the latin name \"citrus grandis\"?",
    "answer": "grapefruit"
  },
  {
    "category": "Calendar",
    "question": "How many days where there in 1976?",
    "answer": "three hundred and sixty six"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(three hundred (and )?sixty[- ]six|366)",
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Alvin & Simon had a brother called ????.",
    "answer": "Theodore"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(theodore|theo)",
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "An Andy Panda cartoon gave birth to a famous, cantankerous bird. Name him.",
    "answer": "Woody Woodpecker"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "An adventurous penguin named Tennessee Tuxedo had a sidekick named ????????",
    "answer": "Chumley"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "An alien creature in a funny hat has opposed both Bugs Bunny and Daffy Duck.  Where is he from?",
    "answer": "Mars"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Before Olive Oil met Popeye she was engaged to someone.  Who was he?",
    "answer": "Ham Gravy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Benny and Cecil were at odds with whom?",
    "answer": "John"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Bugs always finds himself at the wrong end of a gun, usually toted by either Elmer Fudd or who?",
    "answer": "Yosemite Sam"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Casper the Friendly Ghost frolicked with which witch?",
    "answer": "Wendy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Charles Boyer inspired a cartoon skunk. Who?",
    "answer": "Pepe le Pew"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Famous Phrases: Who knows? The ??????.",
    "answer": "Shadow"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Gadzookie has a large, green friend. Who is he?",
    "answer": "Godzilla"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Hanna-Barbera rose to fame by creating what duo for MGM?",
    "answer": "Tom and Jerry"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "How does Wonder Woman control her invisible airplane?",
    "answer": "#mental# powers"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(mental|mind|brain|tele(pathy|kinesis))",
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "In the cartoons who was Hokie Wolf's sidekick?",
    "answer": "Ding"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "In what city does Fat Albert live?",
    "answer": "Philadelphia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Mentor of Titan had two children in the Marvel comics, Thanos and ????",
    "answer": "Ero"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Miss Buckley is secretary to what commanding officer?",
    "answer": "General Halftrack"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name Alley Oop's girl friend.",
    "answer": "Oola"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name Cathy's on again/off again boy friend?",
    "answer": "Irving"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name Dennis the Menace's next door neighbors.",
    "answer": "Mr and Mrs #Wilson#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name Donald Duck's girlfriend?",
    "answer": "Daisy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name Hagar the Horrible's dog.",
    "answer": "Snert"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name Li'l Abner's favorite Indian drink.",
    "answer": "Kickapoo Joy Juice"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name the European hit, now an animated series about underwater people.",
    "answer": "The #Snork#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name the apartments the Jetson's live in.",
    "answer": "The #Skypad# Apartments"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name the dog in the Yankee Doodle cartoons.",
    "answer": "Chopper"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name the fastest mouse in all of Mexico.",
    "answer": "Speedy Gonzalez"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name the ranger who was always after Yogi Bear.",
    "answer": "Rick"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name the town that Fred, Wilma, Barney, and Betty lived in.",
    "answer": "Bedrock"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "On what T.V. show could Tom Terrific be found?",
    "answer": "Captain Kangaroo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Popeye's chief adversary has two names, Bluto and ???????",
    "answer": "Brutus"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Porky Pig had a girlfriend named ????????.",
    "answer": "Petunia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Tess Trueheart married which plainclothes detective?",
    "answer": "Dick Tracy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What came out of Milton's head?",
    "answer": "steam"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What character did Tex Avery first create upon arriving at MGM?",
    "answer": "Screwball Squirrel"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What comic strip character is Beetle Bailey's sister?",
    "answer": "Lois (of Hi and #Lois#)"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What did Dagwood give up to marry Blondie?",
    "answer": "A family #inheritance#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What did Peppermint Patty always call Charlie Brown?",
    "answer": "Chuck"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What is Batman's butler Alfred's last name.",
    "answer": "Pennyworth"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What is Blondie's maiden name?",
    "answer": "Oop"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What is Dennis the Menace's last name?",
    "answer": "Mitchell"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What is Smokey Stover's job?",
    "answer": "fireman"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What is Super Chicken's partners name?",
    "answer": "Fred"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What is the mother's name in Family Circus?",
    "answer": "Thelma"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What is the name of Duddley Do-Right's horse?",
    "answer": "Horse"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What is the name of the Family Circus's dog?",
    "answer": "Barf"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What kind of dog is Scooby Doo?",
    "answer": "great dane"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What type of plant does Broom Hilda sell?",
    "answer": "venus flytrap"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What was Daffy Duck's favorite insult?",
    "answer": "#You're dispicable#!"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What was George of the Jungle always running in to?",
    "answer": "A #tree#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What was the first cartoon to feature sound?",
    "answer": "Steamboat Willie"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Steamboat Will(ie|y)",
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What was the name of George of the Jungle's pet elephant?",
    "answer": "Shep"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What was the name of Speed Racer's car?",
    "answer": "The #Mach Five#"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(Mach (Five|5))",
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What was the original name Charles Schultz had for Peanuts?",
    "answer": "Li'l Folks"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Li'?l Folks",
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What was the relationship between Superman and Supergirl?",
    "answer": "cousin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "When Tweety exclaimed, \"I thought I saw a putty tat!\", who did he see?",
    "answer": "Sylvester"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "When danger appeared, Quick Draw McGraw became which super hero?",
    "answer": "El KaBong"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "When not a Birdman, what does Ray Randall do for a living?",
    "answer": "#police# officer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "When not fighting crime, what did Underdog do for a living?",
    "answer": "#shoeshine# boy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Where are Rocket J. Squirel and Bullwinkle Moose from?",
    "answer": "Frostbite Falls"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Where did Clark Kent attend college?",
    "answer": "#Metropolis# University"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Where did George of the Jungle live?",
    "answer": "Imgwee Gwee Valley"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Where did Mighty Mouse get his superpowers?",
    "answer": "supermarket"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "super ?market",
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Where do Rocky and Bullwinkle play football?",
    "answer": "What'samatta University"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "What'?samatta U",
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Where does George Jetson work?",
    "answer": "Spacely Sprockets"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Where does Yogi Bear Live?",
    "answer": "#Jellystone# Park"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Which comic strip was banned from \"Stars and Stripes\"?",
    "answer": "Beetle Bailey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Which superhero loves peace enough to kill for it?",
    "answer": "Peacemaker"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who always tried to kill Krazy Kat?",
    "answer": "Captain Marvel"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who is Donald Duck's uncle?",
    "answer": "Scrooge"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who is Sally Brown's sweet baboo?",
    "answer": "Linus"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who is Scooby Doo's nephew??",
    "answer": "#Scrappy# Doo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who is Snoopy's arch enemy?",
    "answer": "The #Red Baron#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who is stationed at Camp Swampy in the comic strips?",
    "answer": "Beetle Bailey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who runs Andy Capp's favorite pub?",
    "answer": "Jack and Jill"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who says, \"Th-th-th-that's all folks!\"",
    "answer": "Porky Pig"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who shot Bruce Wayne's parents?",
    "answer": "Chill"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who was Dick Dastardly's pet?",
    "answer": "Muttley"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who was always trying to get rent from Andy Capp?",
    "answer": "Percy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who was the Hulk's first friend?",
    "answer": "Rick Jones"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who was the original voice of Mickey Mouse?",
    "answer": "Walt Disney"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "Hydrogen Hydroxide is more commonly known as what?",
    "answer": "water"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "Nitrogen, a poisonous gas, makes up 78% of the ??? that we breathe.",
    "answer": "air"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "Sodium Hydroxide is more commonly known as ???.",
    "answer": "lye"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "Sodium bicarbonate is better known as ?????????.",
    "answer": "baking soda"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "The process of removing salt from sea water is known as ???????????.",
    "answer": "desalination"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "The smallest portion of a substance capable of existing independently and retaining its original properties is a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "molecule"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "This ancient attempt to transmute base metals into gold was called ???????.",
    "answer": "alchemy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "This is the heaviest naturally occurring element.",
    "answer": "uranium"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "This is the symbol for tin.",
    "answer": "Sn"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "This poisonous gas is in the exhaust fumes from cars.",
    "answer": "carbon monoxide"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "Water containing carbon dioxide under pressure is called ???? ?????.",
    "answer": "soda water"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "What is it that turns blue litmus paper red?",
    "answer": "acid"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "What is the abbreviation for trinitrotoluene?",
    "answer": "TNT"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "What is the chemical symbol for copper?",
    "answer": "Cu"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "What is the chemical symbol for gold?",
    "answer": "Au"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "What is the main component of air?",
    "answer": "nitrogen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "What is the more scientific name for quicksilver?",
    "answer": "mercury"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "What is the symbol for iron in chemistry?",
    "answer": "Fe"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "What is the symbol for silver?",
    "answer": "Ag"
  },
  {
    "category": "Christmas",
    "question": "Name the loner rebel reindeer with the red shiny nose.",
    "answer": "Rudolph"
  },
  {
    "category": "Christmas",
    "question": "Santa Claus reportedly lives at the ????? Pole.",
    "answer": "north"
  },
  {
    "category": "Comic Strip Trivia",
    "question": "What comic strip is set at Camp Swampy?",
    "answer": "Beetle Bailey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Computer Science",
    "question": "That big square thing you're staring at right now is called a ????????",
    "answer": "monitor"
  },
  {
    "category": "Computer Science",
    "question": "The Internet Relay Chat Program, which normally connects to port 6667, is more commonly known as ???.",
    "answer": "IRC"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "--isms:  Exalting one's country above all others.",
    "answer": "nationalism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "--isms:  The belief that there is no God.",
    "answer": "atheism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "--isms:  The theory that man cannot prove the existence of a god.",
    "answer": "agnosticism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-ism: The belief in the existence of a god or gods.",
    "answer": "theism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-isms: A diseased condition resulting from the use of beverages such as whiskey.",
    "answer": "alcoholism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-isms: A one-party system of government in which control is maintained by force and regimentation.",
    "answer": "fascism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-isms: A painful stiffness of the muscles and joints",
    "answer": "rheumatism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-isms: A severe or unfavorable judgment.",
    "answer": "criticism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-isms: An economic system characterized by private ownership and competition.",
    "answer": "capitalism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-isms: Excessive emphasis on financial gain.",
    "answer": "commercialism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-isms: Excessive enthusiasm or zeal for a cause.",
    "answer": "fanaticism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-isms: Poisoning caused by a toxin in improperly prepared food.",
    "answer": "botulism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-isms: Public ownership of the basic means of production, distribution, and exchange.",
    "answer": "socialism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-isms: The belief in living a very austere and self-denying life.",
    "answer": "asceticism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A clip, shaped like a bar to keep a woman's hair in place is a ???????.",
    "answer": "barrette"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A depilatory is a substance used for removing ????.",
    "answer": "hair"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A device used to change the voltage of alternating currents is a ??????????.",
    "answer": "transformer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A flat, round hat sometimes worn by soldiers is a ?????.",
    "answer": "beret"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A government in which power is restricted to a few is a(n) ??????????.",
    "answer": "oligarchy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A person in his eighties is called a(n) ????????????.",
    "answer": "octogenarian"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A person who starts fires maliciously is a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "arsonist"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A person with a strong desire to steal is a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "kleptomaniac"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A pugilist is a ?????.",
    "answer": "boxer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A receptacle for holy water is a(n) ????.",
    "answer": "font"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A sun-dried grape is known as a(n) ??????.",
    "answer": "raisin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A word like 'NASA' formed from the initials of other words is a(n) ??????.",
    "answer": "acronym"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Acrophobia is a fear of ???????.",
    "answer": "heights"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "An \"omniscient\" person has unlimited ??????????.",
    "answer": "knowledge"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "An anemometer measures ???? ????????.",
    "answer": "wind velocity"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "An animal stuffer is a(n) ???????????.",
    "answer": "taxidermist"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "An artist supports his canvas on a(n) ?????.",
    "answer": "easel"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "An instrument on a car to measure the distance travelled is called a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "odometer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Androphobia is the fear of ?????.",
    "answer": "males"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(men|males?)",
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Animals that once existed but don't exist now are said to be ???????.",
    "answer": "extinct"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Any object worn as a charm may be called a(n) ??????.",
    "answer": "amulet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Bibliophobia is a fear of ?????.",
    "answer": "books"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Brontophobia is the fear of ???????.",
    "answer": "thunder"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Dendrochronology is better known as ??????????.",
    "answer": "ring dating"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Doraphobia is the fear of ?????????.",
    "answer": "fur"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Eleutherophobia is a fear of ???????.",
    "answer": "freedom"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Gymnophobia is the fear of ??????????.",
    "answer": "naked bodies"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Hills and ridges composed of drifting sand are known as ?????.",
    "answer": "dunes"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Ichthyology is the study of ????????.",
    "answer": "fish"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Legal Terms: A crime more serious than a misdemeanor.",
    "answer": "felony"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Legal Terms: A formal agreement enforceable by law.",
    "answer": "contract"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Legal Terms: A supplement to a will.",
    "answer": "codicil"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Legal Terms: The people chosen to render a verdict in a court.",
    "answer": "jury"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Legal Terms: To steal property entrusted to one's care.",
    "answer": "embezzle"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Name the pain-inflicting person you go to to get your teeth fixed.",
    "answer": "dentist"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Name the porceilan chair you sit on at least once a day.",
    "answer": "toilet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "One who tells fortunes by the stars is a(n) ??????????.",
    "answer": "astrologer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Rats, mice, beavers, and squirrels are all ???????.",
    "answer": "rodents"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The art of tracing designs and taking impressions of them is ???????????.",
    "answer": "lithography"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The covering on the tip of a shoelace is a(n) ?????.",
    "answer": "aglet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The distance around the outside of a circle is its ????????????.",
    "answer": "circumference"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The earth's atmosphere and the space beyond is known as ?????????.",
    "answer": "aerospace"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The effect produced when sound is reflected back is known as a(n) ????.",
    "answer": "echo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The feeling of having experienced something before is known as ???????.",
    "answer": "deja vu"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The science of preparing and dispensing drugs is ????????.",
    "answer": "pharmacy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The science of providing men, equipment and supplies for military operations is called ????????.",
    "answer": "logistics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of human behaviour is ??????????.",
    "answer": "psychology"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of human pre-history is ???????????.",
    "answer": "archaeology"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of insects is ??????????.",
    "answer": "entomology"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of light and its relation to sight is called ??????.",
    "answer": "optics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of man and culture is known as ??????????.",
    "answer": "anthropology"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of natural phenomena: motion, forces, light, sound, etc. is called ??????.",
    "answer": "physics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of plants is ??????.",
    "answer": "botany"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of religion is ????????.",
    "answer": "theology"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of sound is ?????????.",
    "answer": "acoustics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of the composition of substances and the changes that they undergo is ?????????.",
    "answer": "chemistry"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of the earth's physical divisions into mountains, seas, etc. is ?????????.",
    "answer": "geography"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of the manner in which organisms carry on their life processes is ?????????.",
    "answer": "physiology"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The symbols used on a map are explained by the ??????.",
    "answer": "legend"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The treatment of disease by chemical substances which are toxic to the causative micro-organisms is called ????????????.",
    "answer": "chemotherapy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The weight at the end of a pendulum is a(n) ??????.",
    "answer": "bob"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The wide wall built along the banks of rivers to stop flooding is a(n) ?????.",
    "answer": "levee"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The word \"cumulus\" refers to a type of ???????????.",
    "answer": "cloud"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "This instrument is used for measuring the distance between two points, on a curved surface.",
    "answer": "calliper"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "This instrument measures atmospheric pressure.",
    "answer": "barometer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "This instrument measures the velocity of the wind.",
    "answer": "anemometer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "This is the fear of enclosed spaces.",
    "answer": "claustrophobia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "This word is used as the international radio distress call.",
    "answer": "mayday"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "This word means \"split personality\".",
    "answer": "schizophrenia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Throat, foxing, and platform are parts of a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "shoe"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Toxiphobia is a fear of ?????????.",
    "answer": "poison"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What does a brandophile collect?",
    "answer": "cigar bands"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What does a heliologist study?",
    "answer": "the #sun#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What does an ornithologist study?",
    "answer": "birds"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is a device to stem the flow of blood called?",
    "answer": "tourniquet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is a dried plum called?",
    "answer": "prune"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is a female swan called?",
    "answer": "pen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is a figure with eight equal sides called?",
    "answer": "octagon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is another name for a tombstone inscription?",
    "answer": "epitaph"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is measured by a chronometer?",
    "answer": "time"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is the common name for a Japanese dwarf tree?",
    "answer": "bonsai"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is the common name for the Aurora Borealis?",
    "answer": "northern lights"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is the common term for a \"somnambulist\"?",
    "answer": "sleepwalker"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is the name for a branch of a river?",
    "answer": "tributary"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is the study of heredity called?",
    "answer": "genetics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is the study of prehistoric plants and animals called?",
    "answer": "paleontology"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is the term for a castrated rooster?",
    "answer": "capon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Which science studies weather?",
    "answer": "meteorology"
  },
  {
    "category": "Domestic Metallurgy",
    "question": "Name the clothing wrinkle remover that sounds like a kind of metal.",
    "answer": "iron"
  },
  {
    "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
    "question": "A 3 1/2\" floppy disk measures ??? and 1/2 inches across.",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
    "question": "A brown crayon is what color?",
    "answer": "brown"
  },
  {
    "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
    "question": "A smoke detector will alarm if it detects ?????.",
    "answer": "smoke"
  },
  {
    "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
    "question": "A water heater keeps ????? warm for you.",
    "answer": "water"
  },
  {
    "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
    "question": "Although not all come from France, ?????? fries are often served with hamburgers.",
    "answer": "french"
  },
  {
    "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
    "question": "An ????? clock usually wakes you in the morning.",
    "answer": "alarm"
  },
  {
    "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
    "question": "During the American Revolution, the Boston Tea Party took place in ?????? Harbor.",
    "answer": "boston"
  },
  {
    "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
    "question": "How do you spell abbreviation?",
    "answer": "abbreviation"
  },
  {
    "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
    "question": "How many pencils are there in a dozen?",
    "answer": "twelve"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(twelve|12)",
    "category": "Drama",
    "question": "\"Our Town\" is a play by whom?",
    "answer": "Thornton #Wilder#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Drama",
    "question": "The play \"Our Town\" is set where?",
    "answer": "Grover's Corners"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Grover'?s Corner",
    "category": "Fantasy",
    "question": "What is a sorcerer who deals in black magic called?",
    "answer": "necromancer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food",
    "question": "Boston butt, jowl, and picnic ham are parts of a ??????.",
    "answer": "pig"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Even though it tastes nothing like grapes, a ?????????? is often eaten for breakfast.",
    "answer": "grapefruit"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "From what animal do we get venison?",
    "answer": "deer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "From which fish is caviar obtained?",
    "answer": "sturgeon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "From which fruit is the liqueur Kirsh made?",
    "answer": "cherry"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Iceberg, Boston, and Bibb are types of ?????????.",
    "answer": "lettuce"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Laetrile is associated with the pit of which fruit?",
    "answer": "apricot"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Little round chocolate candies are known as _&m's.",
    "answer": "m"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Mustard, ketchup and onions on a hotdog are all ??????????.",
    "answer": "condiments"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Name the only fruit named for its color.",
    "answer": "orange"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Natural vanilla flavoring comes from this plant.",
    "answer": "orchid"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Often drunk, this liquid is normally harvested from female cows.",
    "answer": "milk"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Often eaten for breakfast, bacon is actually the flesh of what barnyard animal?",
    "answer": "pig"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Often eaten for breakfast, the egg comes from what barnyard animal?",
    "answer": "chicken"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Rum is made from this plant.",
    "answer": "sugar cane"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Vermicelli literally means ???????????.",
    "answer": "little worms"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "What do you get when you add fresh fruit to red wine?",
    "answer": "sangria"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "What is Japanese \"sake\" made from?",
    "answer": "rice"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "What is the name of the syrup drained from raw sugar?",
    "answer": "molasses"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "What kind of nuts are used in marzipan?",
    "answer": "almonds"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Where is the best brandy bottled?",
    "answer": "cognac"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Where was Budweiser first brewed?",
    "answer": "St. Louis"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "St.? Louis",
    "category": "Fun",
    "question": "Cocktails: Bourbon, sugar and mint make a(n) ???????????.",
    "answer": "mint julep"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fun",
    "question": "Cocktails: Cognac (brandy) and white creme de menthe make a(n) ?????????????.",
    "answer": "stinger"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fun",
    "question": "Cocktails: Creme de Cacao, cream, and brandy make a(n) ??????????.",
    "answer": "brandy alexander"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fun",
    "question": "Cocktails: Gin and Collins mix make a(n) ??????????.",
    "answer": "Tom Collins"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fun",
    "question": "Cocktails: Rum, lime, and cola drink make a(n) ????????????.",
    "answer": "cuba libre"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fun",
    "question": "Cocktails: Triple sec, tequila, and lemon or lime juice make a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "margarita"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fun",
    "question": "Cocktails: Vodka and Kahlua make a ???????????.",
    "answer": "black russian"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fun",
    "question": "Cocktails: Vodka, orange juice and Galliano make a(n) ???????????.",
    "answer": "Harvey Wallbanger"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fun",
    "question": "Cocktails: Whiskey, hot coffee, and whipped cream make a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "Irish coffee"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "A bridge hand with no cards in one suit is said to have a ???????.",
    "answer": "void"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "A poker hand consisting of three of a kind and a pair is called a ???????.",
    "answer": "full house"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "How many balls are used in a game of snooker including the cue ball?",
    "answer": "twenty two"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(twenty[- ]two|22)",
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "How many dots are there on a pair of dice?",
    "answer": "forty two"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(forty[- ]two|42)",
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "How many squares are there on a chessboard?",
    "answer": "sixty four"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(sixty[- ]four|64)",
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "If you \"peg out\" what game are you playing?",
    "answer": "cribbage"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "In poker five cards of the same suit is called a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "flush"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "In pool, what color is the eight ball?",
    "answer": "black"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "In which game might a person have a \"full house\"?",
    "answer": "poker"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "In which game or sport are \"Staunton\" pieces used?",
    "answer": "chess"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "In which game or sport can a person be \"skunked\"?",
    "answer": "cribbage"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "In which sport are terms \"spare\" and \"gutter\" used?",
    "answer": "tenpin #bowling#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "In which sport or game are the terms: 'pin', 'fork', and 'skewer' used?",
    "answer": "chess"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "In which sport or game is the term \"rook\" used?",
    "answer": "chess"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "Name the only flexible murder weapon in the game of \"Cluedo\".",
    "answer": "rope"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "Name the only woman suspect in the game of \"Cluedo\" who isn't married.",
    "answer": "Miss #Scarlett#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "These are the two highest valued letters in \"Scrabble\".  \"Q\" and ?????.",
    "answer": "Z"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "This ancient Chinese game is played with 156 small rectangular tiles.",
    "answer": "mah jongg"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "mah? ?jong",
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "This is the lowest ranking suit in Bridge.",
    "answer": "clubs"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "This term denotes a chess move in which both the king and the rook are moved.",
    "answer": "castling"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "What bowling term means three straight strikes?",
    "answer": "turkey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "What game or sport is Bobby Fischer identified with?",
    "answer": "chess"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "What number is on the opposite side of the \"five\" on dice?",
    "answer": "two"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(two|2)",
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "What score is not possible for a cribbage hand?",
    "answer": "nineteen"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(nineteen|19)",
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "Which chess piece is usually valued as 5 points?",
    "answer": "rook"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "Which game usually begins with, \"Is it animal, vegetable, or mineral?\"",
    "answer": "twenty questions"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(twenty|20) questions",
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "Although it doesn't sound like a dog, ????dust is ornamental wood chips often placed in flowerbeds.",
    "answer": "bark"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "Chicago Transit Authority is now known as which group?",
    "answer": "Chicago"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "If you drive on a parkway, you park on a ????????",
    "answer": "driveway"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "To refuel your car you go to a ????? station.",
    "answer": "petrol"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "Wedding rings are normally worn on what finger of your hand?",
    "answer": "#ring# finger"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What are catalogued under the Dewey decimal system?",
    "answer": "books"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What are the 3 big colleges of the Ivy League? (name them alphabetically)",
    "answer": "Harvard, Princeton, Yale"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Harvard,? Princeton,?( and)? Yale",
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What company makes Pampers disposable diapers?",
    "answer": "Proctor & Gamble"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Proctor (&|and) Gamble",
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What do the initials U.F.O stand for?",
    "answer": "Unidentified Flying Object"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What do the letters in SAM missiles refer to?",
    "answer": "Surface-to-Air Missile"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Surface[- ]to[- ]Air",
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What does IRS stand for?",
    "answer": "Internal Revenue Service"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What does a compass needle point to?",
    "answer": "north"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What does the abbreviation a.m. stand for?",
    "answer": "Ante Meridian"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What does the acronym CIA stand for?",
    "answer": "Central Intelligence Agency"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What is the minimum IQ score for the genius category?",
    "answer": "one hundred and forty"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(one hundred (and |& )?forty|140)",
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What is this sign called \"&\"?",
    "answer": "ampersand"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "When using a telephone, you must wait for a ???? tone before starting your call.",
    "answer": "dial"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "Which U.S. president is on the five-dollar bill?",
    "answer": "Abraham #Lincoln#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Acadia was the original name of which Canadian province?",
    "answer": "Nova Scotia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Bridgeport is the largest city in which state?",
    "answer": "Connecticut"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Bridgetown is the capital of ????????.",
    "answer": "Barbados"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Brussels is the capital of which country?",
    "answer": "Belgium"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Frankfort is the capital of which state?",
    "answer": "Kentucky"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Guayaquil is the largest city in what country?",
    "answer": "Ecuador"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Halifax is the capital of which Canadian province?",
    "answer": "Nova Scotia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Havana is the capital of which country?",
    "answer": "Cuba"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "He invented the most common projection for world maps.",
    "answer": "Gerardus #Mercator#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "He visited Australia and New Zealand, then surveyed the Pacific Coast of North America.",
    "answer": "Vancouver"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "How many stars are on the flag of New Zealand?",
    "answer": "four"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(four|4)",
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "If its 4:00pm in Seattle, Washington what time is it in Portland, Oregon?",
    "answer": "#4#:00pm"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what city are the famous Tivoli Gardens?",
    "answer": "Copenhagen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what city is the Leaning Tower?",
    "answer": "Pisa"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what city is the Smithsonian Institute?",
    "answer": "Washington"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is Banff National Park?",
    "answer": "Canada"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is Lahore?",
    "answer": "Pakistan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is Mandalay?",
    "answer": "#Myanmar# (formerly known as Burma)"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(Myanmar|Burma)",
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is Taipei?",
    "answer": "Taiwan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is Thunder Bay?",
    "answer": "Canada"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is the Jutland peninsula?",
    "answer": "Denmark"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is the Mekong River Delta?",
    "answer": "Vietnam"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is the Waterloo battlefield?",
    "answer": "Belgium"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is the highest point in South America?",
    "answer": "Argentina"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is the lowest point in South America?",
    "answer": "Argentina"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is the source of the Blue Nile?",
    "answer": "Ethiopia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what island group is Corregidor?",
    "answer": "#Philippine#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what mountain range is Kicking Horse Pass?",
    "answer": "Rocky"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Rock(y|ies)",
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what state is Concord?",
    "answer": "New Hampshire"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which city is Red Square?",
    "answer": "Moscow"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which city is Saint Paul's Cathedral?",
    "answer": "London"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which city is Wembley Stadium?",
    "answer": "London"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which city is the Bridge of Sighs?",
    "answer": "Venice"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which city is the C.N. Tower?",
    "answer": "Toronto"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which city is the Canale Grande?",
    "answer": "Venice"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which city is the Colliseum located?",
    "answer": "Rome"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which city is the Wailing Wall?",
    "answer": "Jerusalem"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is Angel Falls?",
    "answer": "Venezuela"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is Brest? (NOT Breast!)",
    "answer": "France"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is Chennai (formerly Madras)?",
    "answer": "India"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is Cusco?",
    "answer": "Peru"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is Loch Ness?",
    "answer": "Scotland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is Normandy?",
    "answer": "France"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is Sapporo?",
    "answer": "Japan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is the Calabria region?",
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is the Dalai Lama's palace?",
    "answer": "Tibet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is the Great Victoria Desert?",
    "answer": "Australia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is the Machu Picchu?",
    "answer": "Peru"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country would you find the Yucatan Peninsula?",
    "answer": "Mexico"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which ocean or sea are the Seychelles?",
    "answer": "#Indian# Ocean"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state are Gettysburg and the Liberty Bell?",
    "answer": "Pennsylvania"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state are the Finger Lakes?",
    "answer": "New York"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is Appomattax?",
    "answer": "Virginia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is Cape Hatteras?",
    "answer": "North Carolina"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is Hoover Dam?",
    "answer": "Arizona"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is Mount McKinley?",
    "answer": "Alaska"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is Mount St. Helens?",
    "answer": "Washington"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is Mount Vernon?",
    "answer": "Virginia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is Stone Mountain?",
    "answer": "Georgia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is Walla Walla?",
    "answer": "Washington"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is the Kennedy Space Center?",
    "answer": "Florida"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is the Mayo Clinic?",
    "answer": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is the Painted Desert?",
    "answer": "Arizona"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Into what bay does the Ganges River flow?",
    "answer": "Bay Of #Bengal#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Into what body of water does the Danube River flow?",
    "answer": "Black Sea"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Into what body of water does the Yukon River flow?",
    "answer": "#Bering# Sea"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Into what sea does the Elbe River flow?",
    "answer": "#North# Sea"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Into what sea does the Mackenzie River flow?",
    "answer": "#Beaufort# Sea"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Khartoum is the capital of which country?",
    "answer": "Sudan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Kingston is the capital of which country?",
    "answer": "Jamaica"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Linz, Austria is a leading port on which river?",
    "answer": "Danube"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Madrid and Lisbon are both located near this river.",
    "answer": "Tagus"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Meridians converge at the ????????.",
    "answer": "#pole#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Mount Victoria is the highest peak of this island country.",
    "answer": "Fiji"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name a country which has the same name as a bird.",
    "answer": "Turkey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the U.S. state with the smallest population.",
    "answer": "Alaska"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the capital city of Massachusetts.",
    "answer": "Boston"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the capital city of Rhode Island.",
    "answer": "Providence"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the capital of Argentina.",
    "answer": "Buenos Aires"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the capital of Brazil.",
    "answer": "Brasilia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the capital of Italy.",
    "answer": "Rome"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the city at the west end of Lake Superior.",
    "answer": "Duluth"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the continent that consists of a single country.",
    "answer": "Australia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the desert located in south-east California.",
    "answer": "Mojave"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the large mountain chain in the eastern U.S.A.",
    "answer": "The #Appalachian#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the largest cathedral in the world.",
    "answer": "St. Peter's"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "St.? ?Peter'?s",
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the largest city in Canada.",
    "answer": "Toronto"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the largest island in the world.",
    "answer": "Greenland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the largest lake in Australia.",
    "answer": "Eyre"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the largest river forming part of the U.S. - Mexican border.",
    "answer": "Rio Grande"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the last province to become part of Canada.",
    "answer": "Newfoundland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the longest river in Asia.",
    "answer": "Yangtze"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the longest river in Nigeria.",
    "answer": "Niger"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the most north-easterly of the 48 contiguous states.",
    "answer": "Maine"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the only Central American country without an Atlantic coastline.",
    "answer": "El Salvador"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the sea between Asia Minor and Greece.",
    "answer": "Aegean"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the sea between Korea and China.",
    "answer": "#Yellow# Sea"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the sea north of Alaska.",
    "answer": "Beaufort"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the sea north of Murmansk, Russia.",
    "answer": "Barents"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the sea west of Alaska.",
    "answer": "Bering"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the second largest country in Africa.",
    "answer": "Algeria"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the second largest country in South America.",
    "answer": "Argentina"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the second largest lake in North America.",
    "answer": "Huron"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the smallest of the Great Lakes.",
    "answer": "Ontario"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the strait joining the Atlantic Ocean and the Mediterranean Sea.",
    "answer": "Gibraltar"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the world's most photographed and most climbed mountain.",
    "answer": "Fuji"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Nassau is the capital of which country?",
    "answer": "Bahamas"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "On what island is Honolulu?",
    "answer": "Oahu"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "On what island is Pearl Harbour?",
    "answer": "Oahu"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "On what island is the Blue Grotto?",
    "answer": "Capri"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "On what island is the U.S. naval base, Guantanamo?",
    "answer": "Cuba"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "On what mountain are four presidents' faces carved?",
    "answer": "Rushmore"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "On what peninsula are Spain and Portugal located?",
    "answer": "The #Iberia#n peninsula"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "On what river is the capital city of Canada?",
    "answer": "Ottawa"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "On which river is London, England?",
    "answer": "Thames"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "On which river is Rome located?",
    "answer": "Tiber"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "On which river is the Aswan High Dam?",
    "answer": "Nile"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Over 75% of the Earth's surface is covered by some form of ?????.",
    "answer": "Water"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Rabat is the capital of which country?",
    "answer": "Morocco"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "San Francisco Bay is located near what city?",
    "answer": "San Francisco"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Seoul is the capital of which country?",
    "answer": "South Korea"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "St. George's is the capital city of what island country?",
    "answer": "Grenada"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Surfing is believed to have originated here.",
    "answer": "Hawaii"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The Auckland Islands belong to which country?",
    "answer": "New Zealand"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The Hebrides are part of this country.",
    "answer": "Scotland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The Ionian and Cyclades are island groups of which country?",
    "answer": "Greece"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The Little Mermaid is found in the harbour of which city?",
    "answer": "Copenhagen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The Nationalist Chinese occupy this island.",
    "answer": "Taiwan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The Thatcher Ferry Bridge crosses what canal?",
    "answer": "#Panama# Canal"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The United States is made up of ?? states.",
    "answer": "50"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The Volta is the largest river in which country?",
    "answer": "Ghana"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The countries of Belgium, Netherlands, and Luxembourg are together called ????????.",
    "answer": "Benelux"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The longest river in Western Europe is ??????????",
    "answer": "Rhine"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The sun sets in the ?????",
    "answer": "west"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This Canadian island is the world's fifth largest.",
    "answer": "Baffin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This Pacific island's puzzling monoliths attract ethnologists.",
    "answer": "Easter Island"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This country is divided at the 38th parallel.",
    "answer": "Korea"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This country occupies the \"horn of Africa\".",
    "answer": "Somalia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This country's flag has a large \"R\" on it.",
    "answer": "Rwanda"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This imaginary line approximately follows the 180 degree meridian through the Pacific Ocean.",
    "answer": "international date line"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This is called the \"Honeymoon Capital\" of the world.",
    "answer": "Niagara Falls"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This is the bridge with the longest span in the U.S.A.",
    "answer": "Verrazano Narrows"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "verrazano",
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This is the only borough of New York City that is not on an island.",
    "answer": "The #Bronx#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This is the port city serving Tokyo.",
    "answer": "Yokohama"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This is the residence of English monarchs.",
    "answer": "Buckingham Palace"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This island group is off the east coast of southern South America.",
    "answer": "#Falkland# Islands"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This re-opened in 1975 after being closed for 8 years.",
    "answer": "Suez Canal"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This section of Manhattan is noted for its Negro and Latin American residents.",
    "answer": "Harlem"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "To what country do the Faeroe Islands belong?",
    "answer": "Denmark"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "To what country does the Gaza Strip belong?",
    "answer": "Egypt"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "True Or False:  The Easter Bunny is from Easter Island.",
    "answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "True Or False:  There are only virgins on the Virgin Islands.",
    "answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Under what river does the Holland Tunnel run?",
    "answer": "Hudson"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Warsaw is the capital of what country?",
    "answer": "Poland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What American city is known as Little Havana?",
    "answer": "Miami"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What Asian city was once called Edo?",
    "answer": "Tokyo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What Canadian city is at the west end of Lake Ontario?",
    "answer": "Hamilton"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What European country administers the island of Martinique?",
    "answer": "France"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What European country has \"Vaduz\" as its capital city?",
    "answer": "Liechtenstein"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What London borough does the Prime Meridian pass through?",
    "answer": "Greenwich"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What U.S. city is known as Insurance City?",
    "answer": "Hartford"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What U.S. city is named after Saint Francis of Assisi?",
    "answer": "San Francisco"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What U.S. state is known as The Land of 10,000 Lakes?",
    "answer": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What US state is completely surrounded by the Pacific Ocean?",
    "answer": "Hawaii"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What are drumlins and eskers formed by?",
    "answer": "#glacier#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What are the worlds four oceans - alphabetically?",
    "answer": "Arctic, Atlantic, Indian and Pacific"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Arctic,? Atlantic,? Indian(,| and)? Pacific",
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What body of water borders Saudi Arabia to the east?",
    "answer": "Persian Gulf"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What canal connects Lake Ontario and Lake Erie?",
    "answer": "Welland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What city boasts the Copacabana Beach and Ipanema?",
    "answer": "#Rio# de Janeiro"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What city is associated with Alcatraz?",
    "answer": "San Francisco"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What city is on Lake Erie at the mouth of the Cuyahoga River?",
    "answer": "Cleveland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What city is the Christian Science Monitor based in?",
    "answer": "Boston"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What city is the Kremlin located in?",
    "answer": "Moscow"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What city was the setting for \"Gone With the Wind\"?",
    "answer": "Atlanta"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What color does the bride wear in China?",
    "answer": "red"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What continent is Cyprus considered to be part of?",
    "answer": "Asia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What continent is the home to the greatest number of countries?",
    "answer": "Africa"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country are the Islands of Quemoy and Matsu part of?",
    "answer": "Taiwan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country borders Egypt on the west?",
    "answer": "Libya"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country borders Egypt to the south?",
    "answer": "Sudan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country does the island of Mykonos belong to?",
    "answer": "Greece"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country formed the union of Tanganyika and Zanzibar?",
    "answer": "Tanzania"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country has the world's most southerly city?",
    "answer": "Chile"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country is Phnom Penh the capital of?",
    "answer": "Cambodia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country is Santo Domingo the capital of?",
    "answer": "Dominican Republic"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country is directly north of Israel?",
    "answer": "Lebanon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country is directly north of the continental United States?",
    "answer": "Canada"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country is directly west of Spain?",
    "answer": "Portugal"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country is known as the Hellenic Republic?",
    "answer": "Greece"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country is located between Panama and Nicaragua?",
    "answer": "Costa Rica"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country owns the island of Corfu?",
    "answer": "Greece"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country was once known as Gaul?",
    "answer": "France"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country was the setting for \"Casablanca\"?",
    "answer": "Morocco"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country was the setting for \"Doctor Zhivago\"?",
    "answer": "Russia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What famous geyser erupts regularly at the Yellowstone National Park?",
    "answer": "Old Faithful"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Alaska?",
    "answer": "Juneau"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Bangladesh?",
    "answer": "Dacca"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(dhakk?a|dacc?a)",
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Burma?",
    "answer": "Rangoon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Chile?",
    "answer": "Santiago"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Colorado?",
    "answer": "Denver"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Florida?",
    "answer": "Tallahassee"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of India?",
    "answer": "New Delhi"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Indonesia?",
    "answer": "Jakarta"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Kansas?",
    "answer": "Topeka"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Maine?",
    "answer": "Augusta"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Nebraska",
    "answer": "Lincoln"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Lin?coln",
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of New Zealand?",
    "answer": "Wellington"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Washington state?",
    "answer": "Olympia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of West Virginia?",
    "answer": "Charleston"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Wisconsin?",
    "answer": "Madison"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Zimbabwe?",
    "answer": "Harare"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of the United Arab Emirates?",
    "answer": "Abu Dhabi"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the current name for south-west Africa?",
    "answer": "Namibia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the highest mountain in Canada?",
    "answer": "Mt. #Logan#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the largest city in Australia, in terms of population?",
    "answer": "Sydney"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the largest city in China?",
    "answer": "Shanghai"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the largest of the countries in Central America?",
    "answer": "Nicaragua"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the monetary unit of India?",
    "answer": "Rupee"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the most sacred river in India?",
    "answer": "Ganges"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Gang(a|es)",
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the official language of Egypt?",
    "answer": "Arabic"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the principal river of Ireland?",
    "answer": "Shannon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the second largest of the United States?",
    "answer": "Texas"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the smallest Canadian province?",
    "answer": "Prince Edward Island"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the smallest independent state in the world?",
    "answer": "#Vatican# City"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the smallest of the Central American countries?",
    "answer": "El Salvador"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the world's highest city?",
    "answer": "Lhasa"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What island has Hamilton as its capital?",
    "answer": "Bermuda"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What island is known as the Spice Island?",
    "answer": "Zanzibar"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What mountain range separates Europe from Asia?",
    "answer": "Ural"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What prison island was off the coast of French Guiana?",
    "answer": "#Devil#'s Island"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What river has the largest drainage basin?",
    "answer": "Amazon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What river is Liverpool on?",
    "answer": "Mersey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What river is called \"Old Man River\"?",
    "answer": "Mississippi"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What river is known as China's Sorrow?",
    "answer": "Yellow"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What river is the Temple of Karnak near?",
    "answer": "Nile"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What sea is between Italy and Yugoslavia?",
    "answer": "Adriatic"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What south American country has both a Pacific and Atlantic coastline?",
    "answer": "Colombia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What state borders Alabama to the north?",
    "answer": "Tennessee"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What state is the Golden State?",
    "answer": "California"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What state was the home to Mayberry?",
    "answer": "North Carolina"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What symbol is on the flag of Vietnam?",
    "answer": "star"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What unit of currency will buy you dinner in Iraq, Jordan, Tunisia, and Yugoslavia?",
    "answer": "Dinar"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What volcano showers ash on Sicily?",
    "answer": "Etna"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What's the former name of Istanbul?",
    "answer": "Constantinople"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What's the highest mountain in the 48 contiguous U.S. states?",
    "answer": "Whitney"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where are the Nazca Lines?",
    "answer": "Peru"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where are the pyramids located?",
    "answer": "Egypt"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where is Beacon Street?",
    "answer": "Boston"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where is Euston Station?",
    "answer": "London"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where is George Washington buried?",
    "answer": "Mt. Vernon, Virginia"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "M(oun)?t.? ?Vernon",
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where is Queen Maud Land located?",
    "answer": "Antarctica"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where is Westminster Abbey located?",
    "answer": "London"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where is the Admirality Arch?",
    "answer": "London"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where is the Holy Kaaba?",
    "answer": "Mecca"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where is the Parthenon located?",
    "answer": "Athens"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where is the city of Brotherly Love?",
    "answer": "Philadelphia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where were the Pillars of Hercules located?",
    "answer": "Gibraltar"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which Canadian province extends farthest north?",
    "answer": "Quebec"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which Central American country extends furthest north?",
    "answer": "Belize"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which European country has the highest population density?",
    "answer": "Monaco"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which European country has the lowest population density?",
    "answer": "Iceland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which Irish city is famous for its crystal?",
    "answer": "Waterford"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which U.S. city is known as Beantown?",
    "answer": "Boston"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which U.S. city is known as the Biggest Little City in the World?",
    "answer": "Reno"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which U.S. state borders a Canadian territory?",
    "answer": "Alaska"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which U.S. state has the least rainfall?",
    "answer": "Nevada"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which U.S. state receives the most rainfall?",
    "answer": "Hawaii"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which capital is known as the Glass Capital of the World?",
    "answer": "Toledo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which city has the largest rodeo in the world?",
    "answer": "Calgary"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which city is known as Motown?",
    "answer": "Detroit"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which city is known as the Windy City?",
    "answer": "Chicago"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which city is on the east side of San Francisco Bay?",
    "answer": "Oakland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which country administers Christmas Island?",
    "answer": "Australia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which country are the Galapagos Islands part of?",
    "answer": "Ecuador"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which country borders Italy, Switzerland, West Germany, Czechoslovakia, Hungary, Yugoslavia, and Liechtenstein?",
    "answer": "Austria"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which country developed \"Tae-Kwan-Do\"?",
    "answer": "Korea"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which country has Ankara as its capital?",
    "answer": "Turkey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which country has Budapest as its capital?",
    "answer": "Hungary"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which country has the longest land border?",
    "answer": "China"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which country hosted the 1982 World Cup of soccer?",
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which country uses the \"yen\" for currency?",
    "answer": "Japan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which country would come first in an alphabetical list of countries?",
    "answer": "Afghanistan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which islands were named after Prince Philip of Spain?",
    "answer": "The #Philippine#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which mainland Latin American country is in neither South America nor Central America?",
    "answer": "Mexico"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which of the 48 contiguous states extends farthest north?",
    "answer": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which of the U.S. states borders only one other state?",
    "answer": "Maine"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which river contains the most fresh water?",
    "answer": "Amazon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which state has the most hospitals?",
    "answer": "California"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which state is divided into two parts by a large lake?",
    "answer": "Michigan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which state is the Evergreen State?",
    "answer": "Washington"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which state is the Garden State?",
    "answer": "New Jersey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which state is the Wolverine State?",
    "answer": "Michigan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "With what country is Fidel Castro associated?",
    "answer": "Cuba"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "With which country is Prince Rainier III identified?",
    "answer": "Monaco"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geogrpahy",
    "question": "Name the capital city of Utah.",
    "answer": "Salt Lake City"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "Earth's outer layer of surface soil or crust is called the ???????.",
    "answer": "Lithosphere"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "Peat, lignite and bituminous are types of ?????????.",
    "answer": "coal"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "Slate is formed by the metamorphosis of ?????????.",
    "answer": "shale"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "The green variety of beryl is called ????????.",
    "answer": "emerald"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "The molten material from a volcano is ?????????",
    "answer": "lava"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "The spot on the Earth's surface directly above an earthquake's focus is called the ??????.",
    "answer": "epicenter"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "The violet variety of quartz is called ????????.",
    "answer": "amethyst"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "There are three types of rocks: metamorphic, sedimentary, and ?????????.",
    "answer": "igneous"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "These limestone deposits rise from the floor of caves.",
    "answer": "stalagmites"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "This is the hardest naturally occurring substance.",
    "answer": "diamond"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "What name is used to describe permanently-frozen subsoil?",
    "answer": "permafrost"
  },
  {
    "category": "Hahaha",
    "question": "This normally has 4 legs and your butt is parked in it right now.",
    "answer": "chair"
  },
  {
    "category": "Hirtory",
    "question": "Name the first black nation to gain freedom from European colonial rule.",
    "answer": "Haiti"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Britain and Argentina fought over these islands in 1982.",
    "answer": "#Falkland#s Islands"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Canadian Prime Minister: Pierre Elliott ??????????.",
    "answer": "Trudeau"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Churchill, F.D. Roosvelt and Stalin met here in 1945.",
    "answer": "Yalta"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Eras are divided into units called ????????.",
    "answer": "periods"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "For what country did Columbus make his historic voyage?",
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Four Japanese carriers were destroyed in this battle.",
    "answer": "Midway"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Frankish ruler Charles the Great is better known as ?????????.",
    "answer": "Charlemagne"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "From what country did the U.S. buy the Virgin Islands?",
    "answer": "Denmark"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "General Sherman burned this city in 1864.",
    "answer": "Atlanta"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Germany's WW I allies were Austria-Hungary, Bulgaria, and ????????.",
    "answer": "Turkey"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Germany's allies in WW II were Japan, Italy, Hungary, Bulgaria, Finland, Libya, and ?????????.",
    "answer": "Romania"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He allowed the bugging of the Democratic Committee headquarters.",
    "answer": "Richard #Nixon#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He discovered the Grand Canyon.",
    "answer": "Francisco #Coronado#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He is identified with the expression, \"Eureka\".",
    "answer": "Archimedes"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He is said to have fiddled while Rome burned.",
    "answer": "Nero"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He led 900 followers in a mass suicide in 1979.",
    "answer": "Jim Jones"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He ordered the persecution of Christians in which Peter and Paul died.",
    "answer": "Nero"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He received the Nobel Peace Prize in 1964 for his civil rights leadership.",
    "answer": "#Martin Luther King# Jr."
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He said, \"I have nothing to offer but blood, tears, toil and sweat.\"",
    "answer": "Sir Winston #Churchill#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He shot Lee Harvey Oswald.",
    "answer": "Jack Ruby"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He taught Alexander the Great.",
    "answer": "Aristotle"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He was assassinated on Dec. 8, 1980 in New York City.",
    "answer": "John Lennon"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He was assassinated on Nov. 22, 1963.",
    "answer": "John Fitzgerald #Kennedy#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He was defeated at the Battle of Little Bighorn.",
    "answer": "General #Custer#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He was stabbed by Gaius Cassius Longinus.",
    "answer": "Julius Caesar"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He was the American inventor of the Cotton Gin.",
    "answer": "Eli #Whitney#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He was the U.S. president during the Civil War.",
    "answer": "Abraham #Lincoln#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "His ship was the H.M.S. Beagle.",
    "answer": "Charles #Darwin#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "His wife was Roxana. His horse was Bacephalus. He was ????????.",
    "answer": "Alexander the Great"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "How do you write 69 in Roman numerals?",
    "answer": "LXIX"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "How many astronauts manned each Apollo flight?",
    "answer": "three"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(three|3)",
    "category": "History",
    "question": "How old was John F. Kennedy when he became president?",
    "answer": "forty three"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(forty[- ]three|43)",
    "category": "History",
    "question": "In 1902 this volcano erupted, killing 30,000.",
    "answer": "Pelee"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "In what country did \"Sepoy Mutiny\" occur?",
    "answer": "India"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "In which city was President Kennedy killed?",
    "answer": "Dallas"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "In which city were the Hanging Gardens?",
    "answer": "Babylon"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "In which country did the Boxer Rebellion take place?",
    "answer": "China"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "In which country was Adolf Hitler born?",
    "answer": "Austria"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "In which country was the Rosetta Stone found?",
    "answer": "Egypt"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Israel occupied the Golan Heights.  Whose territory was it?",
    "answer": "Syria"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Israel occupied the West Bank.  It belonged to ???????.",
    "answer": "Jordan"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "John F. Kennedy Airport in New York used to be called ??????????.",
    "answer": "Idlewind"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Mussolini invaded this country in 1935.",
    "answer": "Ethiopia"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Name Jacques Cousteau's research ship.",
    "answer": "Calypso"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Name the incident in which tea was dumped into the harbour.",
    "answer": "Boston Tea Party"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Boston Tea[- ]Party",
    "category": "History",
    "question": "One who fought professionally in Roman arenas was a(n) ????????????.",
    "answer": "Gladiator"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "She overcame her handicaps to become a lecturer and a scholar.",
    "answer": "Helen #Keller#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "She was Queen of Egypt and mistress of Julius Caesar.",
    "answer": "Cleopatra"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "She was called \"The Maid of Orleans\".",
    "answer": "Joan of Arc"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "She was the first First Lady to be received privately by the Pope.",
    "answer": "Jackie #Kennedy#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "She was the first woman premier of Israel.",
    "answer": "Golda #Meir#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "She was the first woman to fly the Atlantic solo.",
    "answer": "Amelia #Earhart#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "She was the first woman to swim the English channel.",
    "answer": "Gertrude Caroline #Ederle#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "She was the greatest trick shot artist of all time.",
    "answer": "Annie Oakley"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "She won the 1979 Nobel Peace Prize for her work among the poor.",
    "answer": "Mother Teresa"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Spain ceded Florida to Britain in exchange for this territory.",
    "answer": "Cuba"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "The \"Bay of Pigs\" fiasco took place in this country.",
    "answer": "Cuba"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "The Devonian Period is also known as the Age of ??????????.",
    "answer": "fish"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "The Inquisition forced him to recant his belief in the Copernican Theory.",
    "answer": "Galileo"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "The Romans built these to convey water.",
    "answer": "aqueducts"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "The St. Valentine's Day massacre took place in this city.",
    "answer": "Chicago"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "The first dog in space was named ?????????.",
    "answer": "Laika"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "The last line of this document is \"Working men of all countries, unite.\"",
    "answer": "Communist Manifesto"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This F.B.I agent headed the investigation of Al Capone.",
    "answer": "Elliot Ness"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This French peasant girl led the army to victories.",
    "answer": "Joan of Arc"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This Indian group ruled in early Peru.",
    "answer": "Inca"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This Nazi leader had his six children poisoned prior to his own death.",
    "answer": "Joseph #Goebbels#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This Queen of France was beheaded in 1793.",
    "answer": "Marie Antoinette"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This Roman killed himself after his defeat at Actium.",
    "answer": "Marc Antony"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Anth?ony",
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This Sioux Indian toured with Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show.",
    "answer": "Sitting Bull"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This Spaniard conquered Mexico.",
    "answer": "Hernando #Cortez#"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "corte[sz]",
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This U.S. Secretary of State won the Nobel Peace Prize in 1973.",
    "answer": "Henry #Kissinger#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This U.S. president was fatally shot in 1881.",
    "answer": "James #Garfield#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This assassin of Julius Caesar was his friend.",
    "answer": "Brutus"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This frontiersman and politician was killed at the Alamo.",
    "answer": "Davy #Crockett#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This is said to be history's greatest military evacuation.",
    "answer": "Dunkirk"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This military attack took place on Dec. 7, 1941.",
    "answer": "Pearl Harbour"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This organization was founded by William Booth.",
    "answer": "Salvation Army"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This racist organization was formed in Tennessee in 1865.",
    "answer": "Ku Klux Klan"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This war began on June 25, 1950.",
    "answer": "Korean"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This was the largest real estate deal in U.S. history.",
    "answer": "Louisiana Purchase"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This word describes the Nazi annihilation of Jews.",
    "answer": "holocaust"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Those big black CD's that you see at garage sales that people call \"albums\" are made of ?????.",
    "answer": "vinyl"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Two 747's collided here in 1977.",
    "answer": "Canary Islands"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "U.S. President, Chester Alan ????????.",
    "answer": "Arthur"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "U.S. President, Herbert C. ?????????.",
    "answer": "Hoover"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "U.S. President, John Quincy ????????.",
    "answer": "Adams"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "U.S. President: Calvin ?????????.",
    "answer": "Coolidge"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What American feminist went bust as a silver dollar?",
    "answer": "Susan B. #Anthony#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What Chinese dynasty was overthrown in 1911?",
    "answer": "Manchu"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What age preceded the Iron Age?",
    "answer": "The #Bronze# Age"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What did President J. Buchanan not have?",
    "answer": "A #wife#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What did presidents Madison, Monroe, Polk, and Garfield have in common?",
    "answer": "The first name \"#James#\""
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What group landed in America in 1620?",
    "answer": "The #Pilgrim#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for fifty?",
    "answer": "L"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What is the name of the Russian Czar's daughter who might-or might not-have survived the Russian revolution?",
    "answer": "Anastasia"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What volcano destroyed Pompeii?",
    "answer": "Vesuvius"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What was the instrument of execution during the \"Reign of Terror\"?",
    "answer": "guillotine"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What was the name of Plato's school?",
    "answer": "Academy"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What was the name of the B-29 used at Hiroshima to drop the bomb?",
    "answer": "Enola Gay"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What was the nationality of the prisoners in the \"Black hole of Calcutta\"?",
    "answer": "British"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What was the third country to get the \"bomb\"?",
    "answer": "Britain"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What's the resting place of those buried at sea?",
    "answer": "Davey Jones's Locker"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(Dave?y Jones's? Locker)",
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Which U.S. president said, \"The buck stops here\"?",
    "answer": "Truman"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Which military battle took place in 1815?",
    "answer": "Waterloo"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Which nation was led by Genghis Khan?",
    "answer": "The #Mongol#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Which president was responsible for the Louisiana Purchase?",
    "answer": "Jefferson"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who is \"The Iron Lady\"?",
    "answer": "Margaret Thatcher"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who led the attack on the Alamo?",
    "answer": "Santa Ana"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "santa ann?a",
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who rode naked through the streets of Coventry?",
    "answer": "Lady Godiva"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who said \"Veni, vidi, vici\" (I came, I saw, I conquered)?",
    "answer": "Julius #Caesar#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who said: \"Let them eat cake\"?",
    "answer": "Marie Antoinette"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who sang Happy Birthday to John F. Kennedy for his 45th?",
    "answer": "Marilyn Monroe"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who succeeded Churchill when he resigned in 1955?",
    "answer": "Sir Anthony #Eden#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who was \"The Mad Monk\"?",
    "answer": "Rasputin"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who was George Washington's vice-president?",
    "answer": "Adams"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who was the first chancellor of West Germany after WW II?",
    "answer": "Konrad #Adenauer#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who was the second man to set foot on the moon?",
    "answer": "Edwin \"Buzz\" #Aldrin#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who was, \"First in war, first in peace and first in the hearts of his countrymen\"?",
    "answer": "George Washington"
  },
  {
    "category": "IRC",
    "question": "What three letters are overly used to indicate \"Laugh Out Loud\"?",
    "answer": "lol"
  },
  {
    "category": "Langauge",
    "question": "Many Meanings:  Fuel, vapor, flattulence, helium.  What is it?",
    "answer": "gas"
  },
  {
    "category": "Language",
    "question": "Multiple Meanings:  Drinking utensils or sight-enhancers.",
    "answer": "glasses"
  },
  {
    "category": "Language",
    "question": "Multiple Meanings:  Slamming your hands together quickly, or a venereal disease.",
    "answer": "clap"
  },
  {
    "category": "Language",
    "question": "Name the soda that is often confused with a drug.",
    "answer": "Coke"
  },
  {
    "category": "Language",
    "question": "Subject, verb and object are parts of a ?????????.",
    "answer": "sentence"
  },
  {
    "category": "Language",
    "question": "This animal is found at the beginning of an (English) encyclopedia",
    "answer": "aardvark"
  },
  {
    "category": "Language",
    "question": "What is the only English word formed by the first three letters of the alphabet?",
    "answer": "cab"
  },
  {
    "category": "Language",
    "question": "What three letter word means the same as \"to ingest\"?",
    "answer": "eat"
  },
  {
    "category": "Languages",
    "question": "\"faux pas\" means ???????????.",
    "answer": "mistake"
  },
  {
    "category": "Languages",
    "question": "Mardi Gras is French for ???????????.",
    "answer": "fat tuesday"
  },
  {
    "category": "Languages",
    "question": "The name Australia is derived from the Latin word \"australis\" which means ???????.",
    "answer": "southern"
  },
  {
    "category": "Languages",
    "question": "The name for this semi-precious stone comes from the Latin for \"sea water\"",
    "answer": "aquamarine"
  },
  {
    "category": "Languages",
    "question": "What ONE word fits? ????hood; ????hole; ????date.",
    "answer": "man"
  },
  {
    "category": "Languages",
    "question": "What ONE word fits? ????stream; ????hill; ?????pour.",
    "answer": "down"
  },
  {
    "category": "Languages",
    "question": "What does \"c'est la vie\" mean?",
    "answer": "that's life"
  },
  {
    "category": "Languages",
    "question": "What word contains the combination of letters: \"xop\"?",
    "answer": "saXOPhone"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "\"The Diary of Anne Frank\" was first published in English under what title?",
    "answer": "The #Diary of a Young Girl#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "Captain Hook, Tiger Lily, and Tinker Bell are characters in what story?",
    "answer": "Peter Pan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "Dr. Seuss wrote this book: The Cat in the ??????.",
    "answer": "Hat"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "Edgar Allen Poe wrote a famous poem about this animal.",
    "answer": "raven"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "From which Shakespeare play is this line taken: \"Double, double ... \"",
    "answer": "Macbeth"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "From which Shakespeare play is this line taken: \"Goodnight, goodnight! Parting is such sweet sorrow, That I should say goodnight till it be morrow.\"",
    "answer": "Romeo and Juliet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "From which Shakespeare play is this line taken: \"To be or not to be?\"",
    "answer": "Hamlet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "From which Shakespeare play is this line taken: \"What in a name? That which we call a rose, by any other name would smell as sweet.\"",
    "answer": "Romeo and Juliet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "How many lines are in a sonnet?",
    "answer": "fourteen"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(fourteen|14)",
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "How many plays is Shakespeare generally credited with today?",
    "answer": "thirty seven"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(thirty[- ]seven|37)",
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "Name the Shakespeare play from this ultra short plot summary: Urged on by his wife, a man murders his king in order to take his place.",
    "answer": "Macbeth"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "Stephen King's: \"Pet ????????\".",
    "answer": "Semetary"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "Stephen King's: \"Salem's ?????????\".",
    "answer": "Lot"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "Stephen King's: \"The Dead ????????\".",
    "answer": "Zone"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "This Shakespearean king was the actual king of Scotland for 17 years.",
    "answer": "Macbeth"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "This girl hid from the Nazis in Amsterdam.",
    "answer": "Anne Frank"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "What Shakespearean play features the line: A plague on both your houses?",
    "answer": "Romeo and Juliet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "What did Jeannie C. Riley describe as \"a little Peyton Place\"?",
    "answer": "Harper Valley"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "What other name does Stephen King write under?",
    "answer": "Richard #Bachman#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "What publication was subtitled The What's New Magazine?",
    "answer": "Popular Science"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "What was the name of Mother Goose's son?",
    "answer": "Jack"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "What's Penthouse's sister publication for women?",
    "answer": "Viva"
  },
  {
    "category": "Litterature",
    "question": "Homer wrote this account of the Trojan War.",
    "answer": "Iliad"
  },
  {
    "category": "Logic",
    "question": "You are in a room where all walls face south.  A bear walks by.  What color is it?",
    "answer": "White"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "A U.S. dime is worth ??? cents.",
    "answer": "ten"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(ten|10)",
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "A line drawn from an angle of a triangle to the mid-point of the opposite side is a(n) ???????.",
    "answer": "median"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "A triangle with three equal sides is called ???????.",
    "answer": "equilateral"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "A triangle with two equal sides is called ??????????.",
    "answer": "isosceles"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "An angle greater than 180 degrees and less than 360 degrees is a(n) ???????? angle.",
    "answer": "reflex"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "An angle greater than 90 degrees and less than 180 degrees is said to be ?????????.",
    "answer": "obtuse"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "An integer that is greater than 1 and is divisible only by itself and 1 is known as a(n) ???????.",
    "answer": "prime"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "Approximately how many inches are there in one meter?",
    "answer": "thirty nine"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(thirty[- ]nine|39)",
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "Arc, radius, and sector are parts of a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "circle"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "He is known as \"The Father of Geometry\".",
    "answer": "Euclid"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "How many corners are there in a cube?",
    "answer": "eight"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(eight|8)",
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "How many nickles are there in 2.25?",
    "answer": "forty five"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(forty[- ]five|45)",
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "If you cut through a solid sphere what shape will the flat area be?",
    "answer": "circle"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "Name the number system which uses only the symbols 1 and 0.",
    "answer": "The #binary# system"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "The angles inside a square total ??????? degrees.",
    "answer": "three hundred and sixty"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(three hundred (and |& )?sixty|360)",
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "The mathematical study of properties of lines, angels, etc., is ????????.",
    "answer": "geometry"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "The space occupied by a body is called its ??????.",
    "answer": "volume"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "The square root of 1 is?",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "Two angles that total 180 degrees are called ???????.",
    "answer": "supplementary"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "What geometric shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "answer": "square"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "A baby doctor is a ?????????.",
    "answer": "pediatrician"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "A bone specialist is a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "osteopath"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "A loss of memory is known as ??????????.",
    "answer": "amnesia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "A medicine that hastens the emptying of the bowels is called a ????????.",
    "answer": "laxative"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "A non-cancerous tumor is said to be ???????.",
    "answer": "benign"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "A thread used in surgery to tie a bleeding blood vessel is called a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "ligature"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Carditis, affects the ????????.",
    "answer": "heart"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Doctors often have this instrument around their neck.",
    "answer": "stethoscope"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Due to a lack of vitamin C, sailors used to contract this disease.",
    "answer": "scurvy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Encephalitis affects the ????????.",
    "answer": "brain"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Gastritis affects the ??????????.",
    "answer": "stomach"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Hammer, anvil, and stirrup are parts of the ????????.",
    "answer": "ear"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "He discovered the process of vaccination for prevention of smallpox.",
    "answer": "Edward #Jenner#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Hepatitis affects the ??????????.",
    "answer": "Liver"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "How many bones are there in the human body?",
    "answer": "two hundred and six"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(two hundred (and |& )?six|206)",
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "How many chambers does the human heart have?",
    "answer": "four"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(four|4)",
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "How many pints of blood does the average human have in his/her body?",
    "answer": "twelve"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(twelve|12)",
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "In the field of psychiatry this term means self-love.",
    "answer": "narcissism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "In what organ of the body is insulin produced?",
    "answer": "pancreas"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "In which organ is a clear watery solution known as the \"aqueous humor\" found?",
    "answer": "eye"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "In which organ is a pulmonary disease located?",
    "answer": "lung"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "In which organ is your \"hypothalmus\" located?",
    "answer": "brain"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Infantile Paralysis is commonly known as ????????.",
    "answer": "polio"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Meningitis affects the ?????????.",
    "answer": "brain"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Myositis affects the ?????????.",
    "answer": "muscles"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Name the hardest substance in the human body.",
    "answer": "enamel"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Name the largest artery in the human body.",
    "answer": "aorta"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Name the largest gland in the human body.",
    "answer": "liver"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Osteomyelitis affects the ?????????.",
    "answer": "bones"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Peritonitis, affects the ????????.",
    "answer": "abdomen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Prosthetics deals with the making of ??????????.",
    "answer": "artificial limbs"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Tarsus, metatarsus, and phalanges are parts of a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "foot"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "The branch of medicine dealing with curing by operative procedures is ????????.",
    "answer": "surgery"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "The lack of this element in the diet is a cause of goitre.",
    "answer": "iodine"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "The largest single organ of the human body is the ????????.",
    "answer": "skin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "The medical name for the voice box is the ?????????.",
    "answer": "larynx"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "The teeth used for biting or cutting are known as ???????.",
    "answer": "incisors"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "These animals were once used to bleed the sick.",
    "answer": "leeches"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "leech(es)?",
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "These attach muscles to bones or cartilage.",
    "answer": "#tendon#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "This branch of medicine deals with old age and its diseases.",
    "answer": "geriatrics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "This disease consists of a purposeless, continual growth of white blood cells.",
    "answer": "leukemia"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "leuka?emia",
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "This fingerlike projection is attached to the large intestine.",
    "answer": "appendix"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "This is known as \"The Royal Disease\".",
    "answer": "haemophilia"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "ha?emophilia",
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "This large bean-shaped lymph gland can expand and contract as needed.",
    "answer": "spleen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "This membrane controls the amount of light entering the eye.",
    "answer": "iris"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "This organ is a small pouch that stores bile.",
    "answer": "gall bladder"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "This parasite lives in the intestines of man and animals.",
    "answer": "tapeworm"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "This small gland attached to the brain exerts a control over growth.",
    "answer": "pituitary"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Ulna, radius, and clavicle are types of ??????????.",
    "answer": "bone"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "What disease is also known as \"rubella\"?",
    "answer": "German measles"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "What hormone is produced by the adrenal glands?",
    "answer": "adrenaline"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "What is a skin specialist called?",
    "answer": "dermatologist"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "What is an organism called that lives on or in a host animal?",
    "answer": "parasite"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "What is the biggest disqualifying factor for prospective astronauts?",
    "answer": "eyesight"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "What is the medical term for cancer of the blood?",
    "answer": "leukemia"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "leuka?emia",
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "What is the name of the bone in the lower leg?",
    "answer": "tibia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "What kind of poisoning is known as plumbism?",
    "answer": "#lead# poisoning"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "What toe is the foot reflexology pressure point for the head?",
    "answer": "big toe"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Where do you find the medulla oblongata?",
    "answer": "brain"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Where in the body is the tiniest human muscle?",
    "answer": "ear"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Which disease is also known as \"Hansen's Disease\"?",
    "answer": "leprosy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "With what body part is otology involved?",
    "answer": "ear"
  },
  {
    "category": "Meteorology",
    "question": "If the groundhog sees his shadow on Feb. 2, there will be how many more weeks of bad weather?",
    "answer": "six"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(six|6)",
    "category": "Meteorology",
    "question": "This dry, warm wind flows eastward down the slopes of the Rocky Mountains.",
    "answer": "Chinook"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Actor: ??????? Borgnine.",
    "answer": "Ernest"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Actor: ???????? Hackman.",
    "answer": "Gene"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Actor: ?????????? Nimoy.",
    "answer": "Leonard"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Actor: ?????????? Savalas.",
    "answer": "Telly"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "At the end of \"Planet of the Apes\" what protruded from the rocks?",
    "answer": "Statue of Liberty"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Barbara Streisand was the female lead in \"Hello, Dolly\".  Who was the male lead?",
    "answer": "Walter #Matthau#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Charles Laughton played Quasimodo in this epic film.",
    "answer": "Hunchback of Notre Dame"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Darth Vader was the villan in the movie, \"???? Wars\".",
    "answer": "Star"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Film Title: An Officer and a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "Gentleman"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Film Title: Fahrenheit ????????. (a number)",
    "answer": "451"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Film Title: The Last Days of ?????????. (a city)",
    "answer": "Pompeii"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Film Title: ?????? (a number) Leagues Under the Sea.",
    "answer": "20,000"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "20[\\,.]?000",
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Forrest ???? liked shrimp.",
    "answer": "Gump"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "He directed \"The Godfather\".",
    "answer": "Francis Ford #Coppola#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "He directed the movie E.T.",
    "answer": "Stephen Spielberg"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "ste(ph|f)en spielberg",
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "He played Superman in the 1978 movie version.",
    "answer": "Christopher Reeve"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "He starred in \"Conan the Barbarian\".",
    "answer": "Arnold #Schwarzenegger#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "He starred in, \"City Lights\".",
    "answer": "Charlie #Chaplin#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "He was known as the \"Elephant Man\".",
    "answer": "Joseph Merrick"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "He was the villain in \"Star Wars\".",
    "answer": "Darth Vader"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "His films include: Giant, Written on the Wind, and A Farewell to Arms.",
    "answer": "Rock #Hudson#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "His films include: Spartacus, The Vikings, and Ulysses.",
    "answer": "Kirk #Douglas#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "In \"Gone With the Wind\", Scarlett regains her wealth by investing in what type of business?",
    "answer": "sawmill"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "In 1975 Jack Nicholson won the best actor Oscar for his role in this film.",
    "answer": "One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "one flew over the cuckoo'?s nest",
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "In the 1996 version of \"Romeo and Juliet\", who played Juliet?",
    "answer": "Claire #Danes#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "In the film \"Bright Eyes\", Shirley Temple sang about this boat.",
    "answer": "The Good Ship #Lollipop#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "In this 1968 film the husband of an unsuspecting young wife becomes involved with a witch's coven.",
    "answer": "Rosemary's Baby"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Rosemary'?s Baby",
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "In which Disney movie is the song \"So This Is Love\"?",
    "answer": "Cinderella"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Name the Disney cartoon in which the character \"Belle\" appears.",
    "answer": "Beauty and the Beast"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Name the actor who played the leading role in \"The Good, the Bad, and the Ugly\".",
    "answer": "Clint #Eastwood#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Name the first full length color cartoon talking picture.",
    "answer": "Snow White"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Name the musical film named after a state.",
    "answer": "Oklahoma"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Nick Nolte and Eddie Murphy star in this 1982 film.",
    "answer": "48 Hours"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Peter Sellers is best known for his role as Inspector ?????????.",
    "answer": "Clouseau"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "She played Lois Lane in the 1978 film version of \"Superman\".",
    "answer": "Margot #Kidder#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "She played a Polish refugee in \"Sophie's Choice\".",
    "answer": "Meryl #Streep#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "She played the lead role in \"Coal Miner's Daughter\".",
    "answer": "Sissy #Spacek#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "She starred in the 1952 film, \"Niagara\".",
    "answer": "Marilyn Monroe"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "The first 18 minutes of this movie is black and white.",
    "answer": "Wizard of Oz"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "The song \"Matchmaker, Matchmaker\" came from which musical play?",
    "answer": "Fiddler On The Roof"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "The two rival gangs in \"West Side Story\" were the Sharks and the ?????????.",
    "answer": "Jets"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This 1974 film started a run of nostalgia culminating in the TV series \"Happy Days\".",
    "answer": "American Graffiti"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This Disney movie relies heavily on computer animation.",
    "answer": "TRON"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This actress appeared in \"St. Elmo's Fire\", \"The Scarlett Letter\", and \"Striptease\".",
    "answer": "Demi Moore"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This actress was Miss Hungary of 1936.",
    "answer": "Zsa-Zsa #Gabor#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This film starring Julie Andrews and Christopher Plummer wont he best picture Oscar for 1965.",
    "answer": "Sound of Music"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This film starring Richard Beymer and Natalie Wood won the best picture Oscar for 1961.",
    "answer": "West Side Story"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This film was an ambitious concert sequence of cartoons by Walt Disney.",
    "answer": "Fantasia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This is a classic film about a huge gorilla.",
    "answer": "King Kong"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This magic word was in the movie, \"Mary Poppins\".",
    "answer": "Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This movie directed by Woody Allen won the best picture Oscar in 1978.",
    "answer": "Annie Hall"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This movie is about the migration of poor workers from the dust bowl to the Californian fruit valleys.",
    "answer": "The #Grapes of Wrath#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This movie starring Marlon Brando won the best picture award in 1972.",
    "answer": "The #Godfather#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This was the first 3-D film.",
    "answer": "Bwana Devil"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This was the first cartoon talking picture.",
    "answer": "Steamboat Willie"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Steamboat Will(ie|y)",
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This was the sequel to \"Star Wars\".",
    "answer": "The #Empire Strikes Back#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This was the sequel to \"The Empire Strikes Back\".",
    "answer": "Return of the Jedi"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What actor appeared in all three of these films, Straw Dogs, Midnight Cowboy, and The Graduate?",
    "answer": "Dustin #Hoffman#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What actress has received the most Oscar nominations?",
    "answer": "Katherine #Hepburn#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What actress's real name was Frances Gumm?",
    "answer": "Judy Garland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What city's police force did Charlie Chan work with?",
    "answer": "Honolulu"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What color was Bullitt's car?",
    "answer": "Green"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What country was the setting for \"The King and I\"?",
    "answer": "#Siam# (Thailand)"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What detective duo was featured in Mystery at Devil's Paw?",
    "answer": "Hardy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What does the statue of Oscar stand on?",
    "answer": "A #Reel of Film#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What famous animal character called \"Skull Island\" home?",
    "answer": "King Kong"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What film did John Wayne win his only Oscar for?",
    "answer": "True Grit"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What is Hawkeye's full name in M.A.S.H.?",
    "answer": "Benjamin Franklin Pierce"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What is the destination of the plane at the end of the film \"Casablanca\"?",
    "answer": "Lisbon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What is the name of Pearce Brosnan's first James Bond film?",
    "answer": "Goldeneye"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What is the name of the Volkswagen in the film, \"The Love Bug\"?",
    "answer": "Herbie"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What is the name of the rabbit in the film, \"Bambi\"?",
    "answer": "Thumper"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What is the name of the skunk in the film, \"Bambi\"?",
    "answer": "Flower"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What is the name of the whale that swallowed Pinocchio.",
    "answer": "Monstro"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What is the stage name of Greta Gustafson?",
    "answer": "Greta #Garbo#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What is the title of the 1996 sequel to \"Terms of Endearment\"?",
    "answer": "Morning Star"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What kind of creature was Chewbacca in \"Star Wars\"?",
    "answer": "Wookiee"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What two words are normally at the end of most movies?",
    "answer": "The End"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was \"Rocky's\" last name?",
    "answer": "Balboa"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was Citizen Kane's dying word?",
    "answer": "Rosebud"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was Dorothy's last name in \"The Wizard of Oz\"?",
    "answer": "Gale"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was Rocky's nickname in the ring?",
    "answer": "The #Italian Stallion#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was Sir Alec Guinness's role in \"Star Wars\"?",
    "answer": "Obi-Wan Kenobi"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Obi(-|)?Wan Kenobi",
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was the first film directed by Robert Redford?",
    "answer": "Ordinary People"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was the name of Ashley Wilkes' plantation in \"Gone With the Wind\"?",
    "answer": "Twelve Oaks"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was the name of Han Solo's spaceship in \"Star Wars\"?",
    "answer": "Millennium Falcon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was the name of Luke's strange little advisor in \"The Empire Strikes Back\"?",
    "answer": "Yoda"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was the name of the motel in the film \"Psycho\"?",
    "answer": "#Bates# Motel"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was the setting for \"The Sound of Music\"?",
    "answer": "Austria"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Which actor said, \"Love means never having to say you're sorry\"?",
    "answer": "Ryan O'Neil"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Which character in \"Forrest Gump\" loved shrimp?",
    "answer": "Bubba"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Which character sang \"Come Out, Come Out, Wherever You Are\" in \"The Wizard of Oz\"?",
    "answer": "Glinda"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Which character sang, \"When you wish upon a star..\" in Disney's \"Pinocchio\"?",
    "answer": "Jiminy Cricket"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Which comedy duo did the famous, \"Who's on first?\" routine?",
    "answer": "Abbott and Costello"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Which planet was the \"Planet of the Apes\"?",
    "answer": "Earth"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who co-starred with Julie Andrews in \"Mary Poppins\"?",
    "answer": "Dick Van Dyke"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who hosted the 1997 Grammy Awards?",
    "answer": "Ellen #Degeneres#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who is Warren Beatty's sister?",
    "answer": "Shirley MacLaine"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who is the fastest mouse in all of Mexico?",
    "answer": "Speedy Gonzalez"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "speedy gonzale[sz]",
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who is the male lead in the \"Naked Gun\" movies?",
    "answer": "Leslie Nielsen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who is the voice of Darth Vadar?",
    "answer": "James Earl Jones"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who played \"Robin\" to Val Kilmer's \"Batman\"?",
    "answer": "Christopher #O'Donnell#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who played Brad Pitt's cop partner in the movie \"Seven\"?",
    "answer": "Morgan Freeman"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who played Dorothy in \"The Wizard of Oz\"?",
    "answer": "Judy Garland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who played Garth in \"Wayne's World\"?",
    "answer": "Dana Carvey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who played Matt Helm in the movies?",
    "answer": "Dean Martin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who played Scarlette O'Hara in \"Gone With the Wind\"?",
    "answer": "Vivien Leigh"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who played the 'Wicked Witch of the West' in \"The Wizard of Oz\"",
    "answer": "Margaret #Hamilton#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who played the role of Richard Blaine in Casablanca?",
    "answer": "Humphrey Bogart"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who plays the character of the only escapee from Alcatraz in the movie \"The Rock\"?",
    "answer": "Sean Connery"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who portrayed Han Solo in \"Star Wars\"?",
    "answer": "Harrison Ford"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who portrayed Moses in \"The Ten Commandments\"?",
    "answer": "Charlton Heston"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who produced, directed and starred in \"Citizen Kane\"?",
    "answer": "Orson Welles"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who starred with John Travolta in the movie \"Broken Arrow\"?",
    "answer": "Christian Slater"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who was C3PO's sidekick in \"Star Wars\"?",
    "answer": "R2D2"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "\"He's So Fine\", \"One Fine Day\" and \"A Love So Fine\" where hits for what fine group?",
    "answer": "The #Chiffons#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "\"Joy to the World\" was a hit in 1971 for what band with three lead vocalists?",
    "answer": "Three Dog Night"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Besides \"Auld Lang Syne\" and \"For He's a Jolly Good Fellow\", what is the most frequently sung song in English?",
    "answer": "Happy Birthday"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Fifties rock \"n\" roll was revived by what greased hair, T-shirted, TV frequenting group?",
    "answer": "Sha Na Na"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Jerry Lee Lewis had Great ????? Of Fire.",
    "answer": "#balls#!"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Name Jerry Garcia's long lived group.",
    "answer": "The #Grateful Dead#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "The Who's rock musical stars Elton John.  It's called ????????.",
    "answer": "Tommy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "This female artist enjoyed sucess on both popular and country & western stations with such tunes as \"Let Me Be There\" and \"Have You Never Been Mellow.\"",
    "answer": "Olivia Newton-John"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Olivia Newton[- ]John",
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "This was the Beatle's first film.",
    "answer": "A Hard Day's Night"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(A )?Hard Day'?s Night",
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Through 1963 this duo's total record sales exceeded 18 million with successes including \"Cathy's Clown\" and \"Wake Up Little Suzie\".",
    "answer": "The #Everly Brothers#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What Procol Harem tune was based on the Bach cantata \"Sleepers Awake\"?",
    "answer": "A #Whiter Shade of Pale#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What band recorded the 1978 hit album: \"Briefcase Full of Blues\"?",
    "answer": "The #Blues Brothers#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What city is also known as Music City, U.S.A.?",
    "answer": "Nashville"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What country singer/songwriter (and sometimes actor) is known as \"the country outlaw\"?",
    "answer": "Willie #Nelson#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What entertainer is allowing one of his songs to be used in a government campaign to beat drunk driving?",
    "answer": "Michael Jackson"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What famous classical composer continued to compose great music after becoming deaf?",
    "answer": "Ludwig van #Beethoven#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What famous singer was known to give automobiles to complete strangers?",
    "answer": "Elvis Presley"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What group refused to have their pictures taken while they were not in their makeup?",
    "answer": "Kiss"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What group's biggest-ever hit was Be My Baby?",
    "answer": "The #Ronettes#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What song by Don McLean talks about the day Buddy Holly died?",
    "answer": "American Pie"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What song did Aretha Franklin sing in \"The Blues Brothers\"?",
    "answer": "Think"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What was Elvis Presley's wife's name?",
    "answer": "Priscilla"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What was The Beatles' biggest hit single?",
    "answer": "Hey Jude"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What's the name of B.B. King's guitar?",
    "answer": "Lucille"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Which of Paul Simon's musical characters was told to hop on the bus?",
    "answer": "Gus"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Who invented the electrical bass?",
    "answer": "Leo #Fender#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Who recorded the 1957 hit \"Tammy\"?",
    "answer": "Debby Reynolds"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Debb(ie|y) Reynolds",
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Who recorded the lengthy song: \"In-A-Gadda-Da-Vida\" in 1969?",
    "answer": "Iron Butterfly"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Who was the first singer in Genesis?",
    "answer": "Peter Gabriel"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Whose theme song was Back In The Saddle Again?",
    "answer": "Gene #Autry#'s"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mythology",
    "question": "The sea gods had a three-pronged spear called a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "trident"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mythology",
    "question": "This Greek mountain was known as the home of the gods.",
    "answer": "Olympus"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mythology",
    "question": "What has no reflection, no shadow, and can't stand the smell of garlic?",
    "answer": "vampire"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mythology",
    "question": "What's heaven to fallen Norse warriors?",
    "answer": "Valhalla"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mythology",
    "question": "Where did Robin Hood supposedly live?",
    "answer": "Sherwood Forest"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mythology",
    "question": "Which ancient continent is said to be submerged?",
    "answer": "Atlantis"
  },
  {
    "category": "Natural History",
    "question": "Name the largest of the dinosaurs.",
    "answer": "brachiosaurus"
  },
  {
    "category": "Natural History",
    "question": "The remains of prehistoric organisms that have been preserved in rocks are called ????????.",
    "answer": "fossils"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "A \"sirocco\" refers to a type of ??????????.",
    "answer": "wind"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "A calm ocean region near the equator.",
    "answer": "#doldrum#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "A coral island consisting of a ring of rock enclosing a central lagoon is a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "atoll"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "A great wave resulting from an earthquakes is called a (an) ????????.",
    "answer": "tsunami"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "A group of gorillas is known as a ???????????.",
    "answer": "band"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "A group of kangaroos is known as a ???????.",
    "answer": "troop"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "A hot spring which shoots steam into the air is a ???????.",
    "answer": "geyser"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "A one-humped camel is called a ?????????.",
    "answer": "dromedary"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "A relationship between two different types of organism which live together for their mutual benefit.",
    "answer": "symbiosis"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "A terrapin is a type of ?????????.",
    "answer": "turtle"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "An animal is a bird if it has ???????.",
    "answer": "feathers"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "An animal is a fish if it has ?????????.",
    "answer": "gills"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Corolla, filament and stigma are parts of a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "flower"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Dense sea-water swamps along coasts of hot countries are called ????????.",
    "answer": "mangroves"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Dogs bark.  What do donkeys do?",
    "answer": "bray"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Excluding man, what is the longest-lived land mammal?",
    "answer": "elephant"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Fandible, lateral line, and dorsal fin are parts of a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "fish"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "From what animal is \"ambergis\" obtained?",
    "answer": "sperm whale"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "How man legs does a crab have?",
    "answer": "ten"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(ten|10)",
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "How many teats does a cow have?",
    "answer": "four"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(four|4)",
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "How many tentacles does a squid have?",
    "answer": "ten"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(ten|10)",
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Imperial, Buck, and Luna are types of ?????????.",
    "answer": "moth"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Knife, Clown, and Pencil are types of ??????????.",
    "answer": "fish"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Linseed oil is obtained from the seed of which plant?",
    "answer": "flax"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Maxillary palps, abdomen, and metathorax are parts of a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "insect"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the fastest land animal over a prolonged distance (1,000 yd. plus)",
    "answer": "antelope"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the heaviest breed of domestic dog.",
    "answer": "St. #Bernard#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the heaviest flying bird of prey.",
    "answer": "condor"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the largest living bird.",
    "answer": "ostrich"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the largest web-footed bird.",
    "answer": "albatross"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the longest venomous snake.",
    "answer": "cobra"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the mammal living at the highest altitude.",
    "answer": "yak"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the most venomous spider.",
    "answer": "black widow"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the only native North American marsupial.",
    "answer": "opossum"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the slowest moving land mammal.",
    "answer": "sloth"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the smallest breed of dog.",
    "answer": "chihuahua"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the wild dogs of Australia.",
    "answer": "dingo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Paper is made from the pulp of ?????.",
    "answer": "wood"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Snakes are reptiles.  What are frogs?",
    "answer": "amphibians"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Some animals spend the winter in a sleep-like state known as ?????????.",
    "answer": "hibernation"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "The \"canebrake\", \"timber\" and \"pygmy\" are types of what?",
    "answer": "rattlesnake"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "The fins of which fish are made into a soup?",
    "answer": "shark"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "The four stages in the life-cycle of an insect are: egg, adult, pupa, and ????????.",
    "answer": "larva"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "The koala bear eats the leaves from this tree.",
    "answer": "eucalyptus"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "These marine crustaceans often attach themselves to the hulls of ships.",
    "answer": "barnacles"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "barnacles?",
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This African animal kills the most people.",
    "answer": "crocodile"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This animal is armed with bony plates and rolls up into a ball if frightened.",
    "answer": "armadillo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This animal is kept as a house pet to kill cobras.",
    "answer": "mongoose"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This animal is normally measured in \"hands\".",
    "answer": "horse"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This animal is the symbol of the U.S. Democratic Party.",
    "answer": "donkey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This animal is the symbol of the U.S. Republican Party.",
    "answer": "elephant"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This animal's name is the same as that given to a high church official.",
    "answer": "cardinal"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This animal's shell is used to make attractive jewelry.",
    "answer": "abalone"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This bird lays its eggs in the nests of other birds.",
    "answer": "cuckoo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This is the largest of the deer family.",
    "answer": "moose"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This is the main food of the blue whale.",
    "answer": "plankton"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This is the only mammal with four knees.",
    "answer": "elephant"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This order of insects contains the most species.",
    "answer": "beetle"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This organic gem is a deep red secretion from a marine animal.",
    "answer": "coral"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This small animal is trained to hunt rats and rabbits.",
    "answer": "ferret"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This two ton animal can gallop at over 50 miles an hour.",
    "answer": "rhinoceros"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This ugly creature has patches of red on his rear-end.",
    "answer": "mandrill"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Walrus tusks are made of ????????.",
    "answer": "ivory"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What are the pouched animals called?",
    "answer": "marsupials"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What bird is an excellent swimmer, but can't fly?",
    "answer": "penguin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What does a camel store in its hump?",
    "answer": "fat"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What fish is the fastest?",
    "answer": "sailfish"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is a group of larks called?",
    "answer": "exaltation"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is a group of peacocks called?",
    "answer": "muster"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is a group of whales called?",
    "answer": "pod"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is a male goose called?",
    "answer": "gander"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is a male swan called?",
    "answer": "cob"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is a male swine called?",
    "answer": "boar"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is a young goose called?",
    "answer": "gosling"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is a young swan called?",
    "answer": "cygnet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is an emasculated stallion called?",
    "answer": "gelding"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is another term for a black leopard?",
    "answer": "panther"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is the horn of a rhinoceros made of?",
    "answer": "hair"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is the only dog that doesn't have a pink tongue?",
    "answer": "chow"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is the world's longest snake?",
    "answer": "python"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What large herbivore sleeps only one hour a night?",
    "answer": "antelope"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What name is given to a female calf?",
    "answer": "heifer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What plant is opium derived from?",
    "answer": "poppy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What travels in gaggles?",
    "answer": "geese"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What type of animal is a wallaby?",
    "answer": "marsupial"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What type of animal lives in a formicary?",
    "answer": "ant"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What word is used for a female fox?",
    "answer": "vixen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What word is used for a female sheep?",
    "answer": "ewe"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What word is used for a male ass? (Other than that the word used for that #*?^*&%@! ex-boyfriend.)",
    "answer": "jack"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What word is used for a male deer?",
    "answer": "buck"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What word is used for a male duck?",
    "answer": "drake"
  },
  {
    "category": "Neture",
    "question": "What do oak trees grow from?",
    "answer": "acorns"
  },
  {
    "category": "Not Telling ;-)",
    "question": "What would be kept in an \"aviary\"?",
    "answer": "#bird#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "Not Telling ;-)",
    "question": "Where is the Ocean of Storms located?",
    "answer": "On the #moon#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Not Telling ;-)",
    "question": "Who is Robert Zimmermann?",
    "answer": "Bob Dylan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Not Telling ;-P",
    "question": "What are white dwarfs and red giants?",
    "answer": "stars"
  },
  {
    "category": "Not telling ;-P",
    "question": "What are these: chrysolite, beryl, jasper, and tourmaline?",
    "answer": "gems"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nursery Rhymes",
    "question": "Jack and Jill went up a ???? to fetch a pail of water?",
    "answer": "hill"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nursery Rhymes",
    "question": "Name the nursery rhyme mother whos last name is that of a bird?",
    "answer": "goose"
  },
  {
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "The energy which a body possesses by virtue of its motion is called ????????.",
    "answer": "kinetic"
  },
  {
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "The pivot point of a lever is called the ?????????.",
    "answer": "fulcrum"
  },
  {
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "The process of water changing to water vapor is known as ???????.",
    "answer": "evaporation"
  },
  {
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "The rate of change of velocity is known as ?????????.",
    "answer": "acceleration"
  },
  {
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "The visible spectrum of light ranges from red to ????????.",
    "answer": "violet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "True Or False: Contrary to popular belief, a lightbulb actually absorbs darkness?",
    "answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "Two 1.5 volt batteries, when connected in series, produces _ volts.",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "Water freezes at _ degrees Celcius.",
    "answer": "zero"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(zero|0)",
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "Water freezes at ?? degrees Fahrenheit.",
    "answer": "thirty two"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(thirty[- ]two|32)",
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "What is measured by a Geiger counter?",
    "answer": "radioactivity"
  },
  {
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "When light waves pass from one medium into another they change direction.  This is called ?????????.",
    "answer": "refraction"
  },
  {
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "Work done, equals force multiplied by ????????.",
    "answer": "distance"
  },
  {
    "category": "Politics",
    "question": "For what does O.P.E.C. stand?",
    "answer": "The Organization of Petroleum Exporting Countries"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Organi[sz]ation of Petroleum Exporting Countries",
    "category": "Politics",
    "question": "He was elected President of France, in 1981.",
    "answer": "Francios #Mitterrand#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Politics",
    "question": "Name Ronald Reagan's first wife.",
    "answer": "Wyman"
  },
  {
    "category": "Presidents",
    "question": "U.S. President, Woodrow ??????????.",
    "answer": "Wilson"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "How is the state of Mississippi spelled?",
    "answer": "Mississippi"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "Name the circular plastic media you put in a CD-ROM drive.",
    "answer": "CD"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "On a standard computer keyboard, this is the letter just to the right of Z.",
    "answer": "x"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "The longest key on your keyboard is the ????? bar.",
    "answer": "space"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "The season ?????? comes right after Spring.",
    "answer": "summer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "There are ?? seconds in a minute.",
    "answer": "sixty"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(sixty|60)",
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "This is required to make all electric things work?",
    "answer": "electricity"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "What color is a blue crayon?",
    "answer": "blue"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "What color is a green crayon?",
    "answer": "green"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "What color is a red crayon?",
    "answer": "red"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "What company makes Microsoft Windows 2000?",
    "answer": "microsoft"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "Whats radar spelled backwards?",
    "answer": "radar"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "Whats the abbreviation for United States of America?",
    "answer": "USA"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "U.?S.?A.?",
    "category": "Quick! Where's my mirror? ;-",
    "question": "When spelled backwards, the word \"retupmoc\" becomes what?",
    "answer": "computer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Religion",
    "question": "Followers of the Unification Church are called ????????.",
    "answer": "Moonies"
  },
  {
    "category": "Religion",
    "question": "He led the Israelites out of Egypt.",
    "answer": "Moses"
  },
  {
    "category": "Religion",
    "question": "He was the first King of the Hebrews.",
    "answer": "Saul"
  },
  {
    "category": "Religion",
    "question": "He was the second King of Israel.",
    "answer": "David"
  },
  {
    "category": "Religion",
    "question": "In what month is Christmas observed?",
    "answer": "December"
  },
  {
    "category": "Religion",
    "question": "Name the holiest day in the Jewish calendar.",
    "answer": "Yom Kippur"
  },
  {
    "category": "Religion",
    "question": "On which mountain did Moses receive the Ten Commandments?",
    "answer": "Sinai"
  },
  {
    "category": "Religion",
    "question": "Which city is sacred to Jews, Christians, and Muslims?",
    "answer": "Jerusalem"
  },
  {
    "category": "Religion",
    "question": "Who founded Mormonism?",
    "answer": "Joseph #Smith#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Religion",
    "question": "Who founded the People's Temple Commune?",
    "answer": "Jim Jones"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "A flat-bottomed conical laboratory flask with a narrow neck is called a(n) ??????????.",
    "answer": "#erlenmeyer# flask"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "A phrenologist reads ?????????.",
    "answer": "skulls"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "A point to which rays of light converge is called a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "focus"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "A shallow dish with a cover, used for science specimens is a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "#petri# dish"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Acetylsalicylic acid is more commonly known as ?????????.",
    "answer": "aspirin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Botany and Zoology combined make up the science of ???????.",
    "answer": "biology"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "By what chemical process do plants manufacture food?",
    "answer": "photosynthesis"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "By what name is Lysergic acid diethylamide better known?",
    "answer": "LSD"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Cetology is the study of ????????.",
    "answer": "whales"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Circuits can be wired in series or in ?????????.",
    "answer": "parallel"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Cocci, Spirilla, and Streptococci are types of ????????.",
    "answer": "bacteria"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Deoxyribonucleic acid is better known as ??????????.",
    "answer": "DNA"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Dermatitis affects the ??????????.",
    "answer": "skin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Epidermal cells, palisade cells, and veins are parts of a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "leaf"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Ethylene glycol is frequently used in automobiles.. How?",
    "answer": "anti-freeze"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "anti[- ]?freeze",
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Forked, Sheet, and Ball are types of ??????????.",
    "answer": "lightning"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Growing plants in liquids rather than soil is known as ????????.",
    "answer": "hydroponics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "He designed the first feasible automobile with an internal combustion engine.",
    "answer": "Karl Freidrich #Benz#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "He invented \"bifocal\" lenses for eyeglasses.",
    "answer": "Benjamin Franklin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "He is known for his theory of \"Evolution\".",
    "answer": "Charles #Darwin#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "He transmitted radio signals across the Atlantic in 1901.",
    "answer": "Enrico #Marconi#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "He wrote \"Sexual Behaviour in the Human Male\" in 1948.",
    "answer": "Alfred #Kinsey#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "How many degrees does the earth rotate each hour?",
    "answer": "fifteen"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(fifteen|15)",
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "In which country was the match invented?",
    "answer": "France"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Nitrous oxide is better known as ??????????.",
    "answer": "laughing gas"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Nuclear membrane, cytoplasm, and nucleus are parts of a(n) ??????????.",
    "answer": "cell"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Pulp, crown, and root are parts of a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "tooth"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Quinine is added to water to make ???????.",
    "answer": "tonic water"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Sound Navigation Ranging is better known as ?????????.",
    "answer": "sonar"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "The Kelvin scale is used to measure ?????????.",
    "answer": "temperature"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "The filament of a regular light bulb is usually made of ????????.",
    "answer": "tungsten"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "The instrument used in geometry to measure angles is a(n) ???????.",
    "answer": "protractor"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "The name for the Russian equivalent of Skylab is ????????.",
    "answer": "Salyut"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "The second space shuttle was named ??????????.",
    "answer": "Columbia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "The vernal equinox is the beginning of ????????.",
    "answer": "spring"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "This Russian scientist used dogs to study conditioned reflexes.",
    "answer": "Ivan #Pavlov#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "This is like an airplane but has its propeller on top instead.",
    "answer": "helicopter"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "This is the reading system used by the blind.",
    "answer": "Braille"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "This science deals with the motion of projectiles.",
    "answer": "ballistics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "To make a car go backwards you have to put it in what gear?",
    "answer": "reverse"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "What are these: Ceres, Juno, Iris, and Flora?",
    "answer": "asteroids"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "What branch of science studies the motion of air and the forces acting on objects in air?",
    "answer": "aerodynamics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "What did Lewis E. Waterman invent in 1884?",
    "answer": "fountain pen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "What does the \"lithosphere\" refer to?",
    "answer": "The earth's crust"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Earth'?s crust",
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "What does the Binet test measure?",
    "answer": "intelligence"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Who invented dynamite?",
    "answer": "Alfred Nobel"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Who is known as the father of genetics?",
    "answer": "Gregor #Mendel#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As bold as ???????.",
    "answer": "brass"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As clean as a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "whistle"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As clear as a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "bell"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As cute as a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "button"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As easy as ????????.",
    "answer": "pie"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As fit as a(n) ??????????.",
    "answer": "fiddle"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As good as ?????????.",
    "answer": "gold"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As graceful as a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "swan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As large as ????????.",
    "answer": "life"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As loud as ?????????.",
    "answer": "thunder"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As pale as a(n) ???????????.",
    "answer": "ghost"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As pleased as ?????????.",
    "answer": "punch"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As pretty as a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "picture"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As proud as a(n) ???????????.",
    "answer": "peacock"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As quiet as a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "mouse"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As sick as a(n) ???????????.",
    "answer": "dog"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As sly as a(n) ??????????.",
    "answer": "fox"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As smart as a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "whip"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "Fresh as a(n) ??????????????.",
    "answer": "daisy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Baseball: The Baltimore ????????.",
    "answer": "Orioles"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Baseball: The Toronto ?????????.",
    "answer": "Bluejays"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Basketball: The Boston ???????????.",
    "answer": "Celtics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Basketball: The Denver ?????????.",
    "answer": "Nuggets"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Basketball: The Los Angeles ?????????.",
    "answer": "Lakers"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Basketball: The New York ??????????.",
    "answer": "Knicks"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Basketball: The Seattle ????????.",
    "answer": "Supersonics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Basketball: The Utah ????????.",
    "answer": "Jazz"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Football: The Baltimore ????????.",
    "answer": "Colts"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Football: The Buffalo ???????.",
    "answer": "Bills"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Football: The Cincinnati ?????????.",
    "answer": "Bengals"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Football: The Cleveland ????????.",
    "answer": "Browns"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Football: The Dallas ?????????.",
    "answer": "Cowboys"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Football: The Denver ?????????.",
    "answer": "Broncos"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Football: The Miami ??????????.",
    "answer": "Dolphins"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Football: The Minnesota ???????.",
    "answer": "Vikings"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Football: The New Orleans ??????????.",
    "answer": "Saints"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Football: The Seattle ???????.",
    "answer": "Seahawks"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "He holds the NHL record for the most goals scored during the regular season.",
    "answer": "Wayne #Gretzky#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "He was the NBA, MVP in 1976, 77, and 80.",
    "answer": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Kareem Abdul[- ]?Jabbar",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Boston ???????????.",
    "answer": "Bruins"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Buffalo ?????????.",
    "answer": "Sabres"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Calgary ??????????.",
    "answer": "Flames"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Chicago ?????????.",
    "answer": "Blackhawks"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "black ?hawks",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Detroit ????????.",
    "answer": "Red Wings"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Edmonton ??????????.",
    "answer": "Oilers"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Los Angeles ????????.",
    "answer": "Kings"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Montreal ????????.",
    "answer": "Canadians"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Pittsburgh ??????????.",
    "answer": "Penguins"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The St. Louis ??????????.",
    "answer": "Blues"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Toronto ???????.",
    "answer": "Maple Leafs"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Vancouver ????????.",
    "answer": "Canucks"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many feet high is a basketball net?",
    "answer": "ten"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(ten|10)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many games must you win to win a normal set in tennis?",
    "answer": "six"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(six|6)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many minutes is a major penalty in hockey?",
    "answer": "five"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(five|5)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many minutes is each period of hockey?",
    "answer": "twenty"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(twenty|20)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many players are there on a soccer team?",
    "answer": "eleven"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(eleven|11)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many players are there on a water polo team?",
    "answer": "seven"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(seven|7)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many players make up a field hockey team?",
    "answer": "eleven"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(eleven|11)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many points are awarded for a safety touch in football?",
    "answer": "two"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(two|2)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many referees work a soccer game?",
    "answer": "one"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(one|1)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many seams are there on a football? (American)",
    "answer": "four"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(four|4)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many sides does a home-plate have?",
    "answer": "five"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(five|5)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In pro football a \"sudden death\" period lasts how many minutes long?",
    "answer": "fifteen"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(fifteen|15)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In ten-pin bowling, how many points does a perfect game consist of?",
    "answer": "three hundred"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(three hundred|300)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In this team sport each player gets a chance to play every position.",
    "answer": "volleyball"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In what sport is the Heisman trophy awarded?",
    "answer": "American #football#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which city is the Cotton Bowl played?",
    "answer": "Dallas"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which city is the Hockey Hall of Fame located?",
    "answer": "Toronto"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which game or sport is a \"Zamboni\" used?",
    "answer": "hockey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which sport is a \"hole-in-one\" possible?",
    "answer": "golf"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which sport is the America's Cup awarded?",
    "answer": "sailing"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which sport is the Cy Young Trophy awarded?",
    "answer": "baseball"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which sport is the Davis Cup awarded?",
    "answer": "tennis"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which sport is the term \"love\" used?",
    "answer": "tennis"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which sport is the term \"wishbone\" used?",
    "answer": "football"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which sport is the term, \"Hang ten\" used?",
    "answer": "surfing"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which sport would you find the \"slapshot\".",
    "answer": "hockey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Name the hockey trophy awarded to the player demonstrating the best sportsmanship.",
    "answer": "The #Lady Byng# Trophy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "On what type of surface are the tennis matches at Wimbledon played?",
    "answer": "grass"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "She was \"Sports Illustrated's\" first female \"Sportsman of the Year\".",
    "answer": "Billie Jean King"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Soccer: The New York ?????????.",
    "answer": "Cosmos"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "The 1976 Summer Olympics were held in this city.",
    "answer": "Montreal"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "The Japanese martial art of fencing is called ????????.",
    "answer": "kendo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "The person who carries the golfer's clubs is called a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "caddie"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "cadd(ie|y)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "The white marks intersecting each five yard line are called ????????.",
    "answer": "#hash# marks"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "This is the most coveted trophy in Candian football.",
    "answer": "Grey Cup"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "This sport allows substitutions without a stoppage in play.",
    "answer": "hockey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "This sport is called the \"American pastime\".",
    "answer": "baseball"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "This team won their first World Series in 1969.",
    "answer": "New York #Mets#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "This traditional Japanese wrestling sport takes place in a circular ring.",
    "answer": "sumo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Two under par on a hole of golf is called a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "eagle"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What are large snow bumps known as in skiing terms?",
    "answer": "moguls"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What do runners pass to each other in a relay race?",
    "answer": "baton"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What do the letters ERA mean in baseball?",
    "answer": "Earned Run Average"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What does TKO stand for?",
    "answer": "Technical Knock Out"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What football player rushed for 2,003 yards in 1973?",
    "answer": "OJ #Simpson#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What game features the largest ball?",
    "answer": "earthball"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What is it called when a football team loses possession of the ball due to a misplay?",
    "answer": "turnover"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What is the heaviest class of weight-lifting?",
    "answer": "super heavyweight"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What number wood is a driver in golf?",
    "answer": "one"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(one|1)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What sport do the Harlem Globetrotters play?",
    "answer": "basketball"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What sport has a hooker in a scrum?",
    "answer": "rugby"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What sport would you helicopter to the Bugaboos for?",
    "answer": "skiing"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What trophy is awarded to the winner of the NHL play-offs?",
    "answer": "Stanley Cup"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What vehicles are involved in the \"Tour de France\"?",
    "answer": "bicycles"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What was football player Dick Lane's nickname?",
    "answer": "Night Train"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What's the nickname of the University of Georgia football team?",
    "answer": "Bulldogs"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Where are the U.S. Tennis Open Championships held?",
    "answer": "#Flushing Meadows#, NY"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Which NFL team's defensive unit was nicknamed \"The Purple People Eaters\"?",
    "answer": "Minnesota #Vikings#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Which country won the World Cup of Soccer in 1982.",
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Which football team was nicknamed the \"Orange Crush\"?",
    "answer": "Denver #Broncos#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Which is the only position in soccer allowed to handle the ball?",
    "answer": "goalkeeper"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(goalie|goalkeeper)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Which position is usually played by the tallest member on a basketball team?",
    "answer": "centre"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "cent(er|re)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Which sport has a movement called a \"telemark\"?",
    "answer": "skiing"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Which sport uses stones and brooms?",
    "answer": "curling"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Which swimming stroke is named after an insect?",
    "answer": "butterfly"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Who was known as the \"Sultan of Swat\"?",
    "answer": "Babe Ruth"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Who was the 1978 Wimbledon Women's Singles champ?",
    "answer": "Martina Navratilova"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Who was the first NHL player to score 50 goals in one season?",
    "answer": "Maurice #Richard# <-- pronounced \"Reeee-shard\""
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Who was the first to win the grand slam of tennis?",
    "answer": "Don #Budge#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "With which sport is Chris Evert Lloyd identified?",
    "answer": "tennis"
  },
  {
    "category": "Stand on your heads.... NOW! ;-)",
    "question": "When read upside down, what does the term \"umop apisdn\" signify?",
    "answer": "upside down"
  },
  {
    "category": "Stupid things to do ;-)",
    "question": "If you look at the sun long enough, you go ?????.",
    "answer": "blind"
  },
  {
    "category": "Summertime",
    "question": "This is the sandy area nearest the ocean.",
    "answer": "beach"
  },
  {
    "category": "TV Trivia",
    "question": "What did TVs IMF stand for?",
    "answer": "Impossible Mission Forces"
  },
  {
    "category": "TV Trivia",
    "question": "What was the first network series devoted entirely to rock and roll?",
    "answer": "American Bandstand"
  },
  {
    "category": "TV Trivia",
    "question": "Who was Carl in Five Easy Pieces before going to Walton's Mountain?",
    "answer": "Waite"
  },
  {
    "category": "TV Trivia",
    "question": "Who was Chief Marshall of the Mickey Mouse Club?",
    "answer": "Walt Disney"
  },
  {
    "category": "Triplets",
    "question": "Hook, line and ???????????.",
    "answer": "sinker"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "\"7X\" was used to refer to the secret ingredient of which drink?",
    "answer": "Coca Cola"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "A \"pigskin\" is another name for a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "football"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "A can of Pepsi holds ?? fluid ounces.",
    "answer": "twelve"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(twelve|12)",
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "A foot-long ruler is ?? inches long.",
    "answer": "twelve"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(twelve|12)",
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "Most men do this each morning, using a razor.",
    "answer": "shave"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "Most people wear a watch on their ???? wrist.",
    "answer": "left"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "Name the implement that removes water from your windshield on your car?",
    "answer": "wiper"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "Traffic Trivia:  Red means stop, ????? means go.",
    "answer": "green"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "What US state has the Worlds Champion Chili Cookoff every year?",
    "answer": "Texas"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "What bit of Bobby Goldsboro syrup focused on a dying young wife?",
    "answer": "honey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "What did Sally Rogers always wear in her hair?",
    "answer": "a #bow#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "What does the typical American eat 263 of each year? not pizza!!",
    "answer": "eggs"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "What game show had people dressed up funny?",
    "answer": "Let's #Make A Deal#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "What is Grimace of the McDonald's characters?",
    "answer": "A #tastebud#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "What was Simple Simon fishing for in his mother's pail?",
    "answer": "whale"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "What was the name of the Akla-Seltzer boy?",
    "answer": "Speedy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "What was the name of the dog in RCA Victor's trademark?",
    "answer": "Nipper"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "What's the telephone area code for Chicago?",
    "answer": "312"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "Where did Howdy Doody live?",
    "answer": "Doodyville"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "Where were Archie and Edith Bunker's chairs enshrined?",
    "answer": "The #Smithsonian# Institute"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "Who is also known as Mr. Warmth?",
    "answer": "Don #Rickles#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "Who is known as \"the world's oldest teenager\"?",
    "answer": "Dick #Clark#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Word Asssociation",
    "question": "Ball and ????????.",
    "answer": "chain"
  },
  {
    "category": "Word Asssociation",
    "question": "Peace and ?????????.",
    "answer": "quiet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Word Asssociation",
    "question": "Which word is related to these three: nap, walk, call?",
    "answer": "cat"
  },
  {
    "category": "Word Asssociation",
    "question": "Which word is related to these three: painting, bowl, nail?",
    "answer": "finger"
  },
  {
    "category": "Word Asssociation",
    "question": "Which word is related to these three: rat, blue, cottage?",
    "answer": "cheese"
  },
  {
    "category": "Words containing 'for'",
    "question": "A castle or enclosed place.",
    "answer": "FORt"
  },
  {
    "category": "Words containing 'for'",
    "question": "Make holes through something.",
    "answer": "perFORate"
  },
  {
    "category": "Words containing 'for'",
    "question": "Many trees.",
    "answer": "FORest"
  },
  {
    "category": "Words containing 'for'",
    "question": "Pardon.",
    "answer": "FORgive"
  },
  {
    "category": "Words containing 'ten'",
    "question": "A choice cut of meat.",
    "answer": "tenderloin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Americanisms",
    "question": "Britains say 'tarmac'; Americans say ??????.",
    "answer": "runway"
  },
  {
    "category": "Analogies",
    "question": "Analogy: 'Ancient' is to 'old' as 'recent' is to ????????.",
    "answer": "current"
  },
  {
    "category": "Analogies",
    "question": "Bull - cow as fox - ??????????.",
    "answer": "vixen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Analogies",
    "question": "Goose - geese as passerby - ???????????.",
    "answer": "passersby"
  },
  {
    "category": "Anatomy",
    "question": "Your ???? holds your head to your shoulders.",
    "answer": "neck"
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts",
    "question": "In what field of study would you find \"flying buttresses\"?",
    "answer": "architecture"
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts",
    "question": "The study of building design is ????????????.",
    "answer": "architecture"
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts",
    "question": "This statue was found on the Greek island of Melos in 1820.",
    "answer": "Venus de Milo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts",
    "question": "Three main types of Greek columns are Doric, Ionic, and ??????????.",
    "answer": "Corinthian"
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts",
    "question": "What Dutch master painted 64 self-portraits?",
    "answer": "Rembrandt"
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts",
    "question": "Where is the Louvre located?",
    "answer": "Paris"
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts",
    "question": "Who painted the Mona Lisa?",
    "answer": "Leonardo #da Vinci#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astrology",
    "question": "What is the only sign in the zodiac which doesn't represent a living thing?",
    "answer": "Libra"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astrology",
    "question": "Which month has a diamond as a birthstone?",
    "answer": "April"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "A heavenly body moving under the attraction of the Sun and consisting of a nucleus and a tail is a(n) ?????.",
    "answer": "comet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "Does Uranus have an aurora?",
    "answer": "yes"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "From 1979 until 2000 the most distant planet from the earth was ???????.",
    "answer": "Neptune"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "How many planets are there in our solar system?",
    "answer": "nine"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(nine|9)",
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "If you're in the northern hemisphere, Polaris, the North Star, can be found by looking which direction?",
    "answer": "north"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "Name the largest planet in the solar system.",
    "answer": "Jupiter"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "Name the second-largest planet in the solar system.",
    "answer": "saturn"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "Our galaxy is commonly known as the ????????.",
    "answer": "Milky Way"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "The Big Dipper is part of what constellation?",
    "answer": "Ursa Major"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "The North Star is also known as ???????.",
    "answer": "Polaris"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "The fourth planet from the sun is ????.",
    "answer": "Mars"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "The name for the group of stars which form a hunter with a club and shield is ?????.",
    "answer": "Orion"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "The planet closest to the sun is ???????.",
    "answer": "Mercury"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "The spiral galaxy nearest ours is the ????????? galaxy.",
    "answer": "Andromeda"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "The tides on the earth's oceans are actually created by gravitational pull from the ????.",
    "answer": "Moon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "This cluster of stars is also known as the Seven Sisters.",
    "answer": "Pleiades"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "This comet appears every 76.3 years.",
    "answer": "Comet #Halley#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "This planet's diameter is most equal to that of the earth's.",
    "answer": "Venus"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "What does \"Ursa Major\" mean in everyday English?",
    "answer": "great bear"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "What is the astronomical name for a group of stars?",
    "answer": "constellation"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "What is the name for the theoretical end-product of the gravitational collapse of a massive star?",
    "answer": "black hole"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "What is the name used to describe the \"minor planets\"?",
    "answer": "asteroids"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "What is the ocean of air around the earth called?",
    "answer": "atmosphere"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "What is the proper name for falling stars?",
    "answer": "meteors"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "What is the term for the path followed a by a small body around a massive body in space?",
    "answer": "orbit"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "What phenomenon is caused by the gravitational attraction of the moon?",
    "answer": "tides"
  },
  {
    "category": "Astronomy",
    "question": "What planet boasts the Great Red Spot?",
    "answer": "Jupiter"
  },
  {
    "category": "Bet you don't know ;-)",
    "question": "The two sexes of humans are male and ???????",
    "answer": "female"
  },
  {
    "category": "Biochemistry",
    "question": "This poisonous, oily liquid occurs in tobacco leaves.",
    "answer": "nicotine"
  },
  {
    "category": "Biochemistry",
    "question": "This protein makes the blood red in color.",
    "answer": "Haemoglobin"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Ha?emoglobin",
    "category": "Biology",
    "question": "Every human has one of these on their tummies.",
    "answer": "navel"
  },
  {
    "category": "Biology",
    "question": "How many large holes are in your head?",
    "answer": "seven"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(seven|7)",
    "category": "Biology",
    "question": "This complex substance makes up all living things.",
    "answer": "protoplasm"
  },
  {
    "category": "Biology",
    "question": "What is normal body temperature for an adult human (in degrees fahrenheit)?",
    "answer": "98.6"
  },
  {
    "category": "Botany",
    "question": "The practice of joining the parts of two plants to make them grow as one is called ????????.",
    "answer": "grafting"
  },
  {
    "category": "Botany",
    "question": "These flowerless plants grow on bare rocks and tree stumps.",
    "answer": "lichen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Botany",
    "question": "This fruit has its seeds on the outside.",
    "answer": "strawberry"
  },
  {
    "category": "Botany",
    "question": "This term means 'cone-bearing trees'.",
    "answer": "conifers"
  },
  {
    "category": "Botany",
    "question": "What fruit bear the latin name \"citrus grandis\"?",
    "answer": "grapefruit"
  },
  {
    "category": "Calendar",
    "question": "How many days where there in 1976?",
    "answer": "three hundred and sixty six"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(three hundred (and )?sixty[- ]six|366)",
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Alvin & Simon had a brother called ????.",
    "answer": "Theodore"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(theodore|theo)",
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "An Andy Panda cartoon gave birth to a famous, cantankerous bird. Name him.",
    "answer": "Woody Woodpecker"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "An adventurous penguin named Tennessee Tuxedo had a sidekick named ????????",
    "answer": "Chumley"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "An alien creature in a funny hat has opposed both Bugs Bunny and Daffy Duck.  Where is he from?",
    "answer": "Mars"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Before Olive Oil met Popeye she was engaged to someone.  Who was he?",
    "answer": "Ham Gravy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Benny and Cecil were at odds with whom?",
    "answer": "John"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Bugs always finds himself at the wrong end of a gun, usually toted by either Elmer Fudd or who?",
    "answer": "Yosemite Sam"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Casper the Friendly Ghost frolicked with which witch?",
    "answer": "Wendy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Charles Boyer inspired a cartoon skunk. Who?",
    "answer": "Pepe le Pew"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Famous Phrases: Who knows? The ??????.",
    "answer": "Shadow"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Gadzookie has a large, green friend. Who is he?",
    "answer": "Godzilla"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Hanna-Barbera rose to fame by creating what duo for MGM?",
    "answer": "Tom and Jerry"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "How does Wonder Woman control her invisible airplane?",
    "answer": "#mental# powers"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(mental|mind|brain|tele(pathy|kinesis))",
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "In the cartoons who was Hokie Wolf's sidekick?",
    "answer": "Ding"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "In what city does Fat Albert live?",
    "answer": "Philadelphia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Mentor of Titan had two children in the Marvel comics, Thanos and ????",
    "answer": "Ero"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Miss Buckley is secretary to what commanding officer?",
    "answer": "General Halftrack"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name Alley Oop's girl friend.",
    "answer": "Oola"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name Cathy's on again/off again boy friend?",
    "answer": "Irving"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name Dennis the Menace's next door neighbors.",
    "answer": "Mr and Mrs #Wilson#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name Donald Duck's girlfriend?",
    "answer": "Daisy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name Hagar the Horrible's dog.",
    "answer": "Snert"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name Li'l Abner's favorite Indian drink.",
    "answer": "Kickapoo Joy Juice"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name the European hit, now an animated series about underwater people.",
    "answer": "The #Snork#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name the apartments the Jetson's live in.",
    "answer": "The #Skypad# Apartments"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name the dog in the Yankee Doodle cartoons.",
    "answer": "Chopper"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name the fastest mouse in all of Mexico.",
    "answer": "Speedy Gonzalez"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name the ranger who was always after Yogi Bear.",
    "answer": "Rick"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Name the town that Fred, Wilma, Barney, and Betty lived in.",
    "answer": "Bedrock"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "On what T.V. show could Tom Terrific be found?",
    "answer": "Captain Kangaroo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Popeye's chief adversary has two names, Bluto and ???????",
    "answer": "Brutus"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Porky Pig had a girlfriend named ????????.",
    "answer": "Petunia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Tess Trueheart married which plainclothes detective?",
    "answer": "Dick Tracy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What came out of Milton's head?",
    "answer": "steam"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What character did Tex Avery first create upon arriving at MGM?",
    "answer": "Screwball Squirrel"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What comic strip character is Beetle Bailey's sister?",
    "answer": "Lois (of Hi and #Lois#)"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What did Dagwood give up to marry Blondie?",
    "answer": "A family #inheritance#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What did Peppermint Patty always call Charlie Brown?",
    "answer": "Chuck"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What is Batman's butler Alfred's last name.",
    "answer": "Pennyworth"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What is Blondie's maiden name?",
    "answer": "Oop"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What is Dennis the Menace's last name?",
    "answer": "Mitchell"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What is Smokey Stover's job?",
    "answer": "fireman"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What is Super Chicken's partners name?",
    "answer": "Fred"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What is the mother's name in Family Circus?",
    "answer": "Thelma"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What is the name of Duddley Do-Right's horse?",
    "answer": "Horse"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What is the name of the Family Circus's dog?",
    "answer": "Barf"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What kind of dog is Scooby Doo?",
    "answer": "great dane"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What type of plant does Broom Hilda sell?",
    "answer": "venus flytrap"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What was Daffy Duck's favorite insult?",
    "answer": "#You're dispicable#!"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What was George of the Jungle always running in to?",
    "answer": "A #tree#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What was the first cartoon to feature sound?",
    "answer": "Steamboat Willie"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Steamboat Will(ie|y)",
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What was the name of George of the Jungle's pet elephant?",
    "answer": "Shep"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What was the name of Speed Racer's car?",
    "answer": "The #Mach Five#"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(Mach (Five|5))",
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What was the original name Charles Schultz had for Peanuts?",
    "answer": "Li'l Folks"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Li'?l Folks",
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "What was the relationship between Superman and Supergirl?",
    "answer": "cousin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "When Tweety exclaimed, \"I thought I saw a putty tat!\", who did he see?",
    "answer": "Sylvester"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "When danger appeared, Quick Draw McGraw became which super hero?",
    "answer": "El KaBong"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "When not a Birdman, what does Ray Randall do for a living?",
    "answer": "#police# officer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "When not fighting crime, what did Underdog do for a living?",
    "answer": "#shoeshine# boy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Where are Rocket J. Squirel and Bullwinkle Moose from?",
    "answer": "Frostbite Falls"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Where did Clark Kent attend college?",
    "answer": "#Metropolis# University"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Where did George of the Jungle live?",
    "answer": "Imgwee Gwee Valley"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Where did Mighty Mouse get his superpowers?",
    "answer": "supermarket"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "super ?market",
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Where do Rocky and Bullwinkle play football?",
    "answer": "What'samatta University"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "What'?samatta U",
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Where does George Jetson work?",
    "answer": "Spacely Sprockets"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Where does Yogi Bear Live?",
    "answer": "#Jellystone# Park"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Which comic strip was banned from \"Stars and Stripes\"?",
    "answer": "Beetle Bailey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Which superhero loves peace enough to kill for it?",
    "answer": "Peacemaker"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who always tried to kill Krazy Kat?",
    "answer": "Captain Marvel"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who is Donald Duck's uncle?",
    "answer": "Scrooge"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who is Sally Brown's sweet baboo?",
    "answer": "Linus"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who is Scooby Doo's nephew??",
    "answer": "#Scrappy# Doo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who is Snoopy's arch enemy?",
    "answer": "The #Red Baron#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who is stationed at Camp Swampy in the comic strips?",
    "answer": "Beetle Bailey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who runs Andy Capp's favorite pub?",
    "answer": "Jack and Jill"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who says, \"Th-th-th-that's all folks!\"",
    "answer": "Porky Pig"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who shot Bruce Wayne's parents?",
    "answer": "Chill"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who was Dick Dastardly's pet?",
    "answer": "Muttley"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who was always trying to get rent from Andy Capp?",
    "answer": "Percy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who was the Hulk's first friend?",
    "answer": "Rick Jones"
  },
  {
    "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
    "question": "Who was the original voice of Mickey Mouse?",
    "answer": "Walt Disney"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "Hydrogen Hydroxide is more commonly known as what?",
    "answer": "water"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "Nitrogen, a poisonous gas, makes up 78% of the ??? that we breathe.",
    "answer": "air"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "Sodium Hydroxide is more commonly known as ???.",
    "answer": "lye"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "Sodium bicarbonate is better known as ?????????.",
    "answer": "baking soda"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "The process of removing salt from sea water is known as ???????????.",
    "answer": "desalination"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "The smallest portion of a substance capable of existing independently and retaining its original properties is a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "molecule"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "This ancient attempt to transmute base metals into gold was called ???????.",
    "answer": "alchemy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "This is the heaviest naturally occurring element.",
    "answer": "uranium"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "This is the symbol for tin.",
    "answer": "Sn"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "This poisonous gas is in the exhaust fumes from cars.",
    "answer": "carbon monoxide"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "Water containing carbon dioxide under pressure is called ???? ?????.",
    "answer": "soda water"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "What is it that turns blue litmus paper red?",
    "answer": "acid"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "What is the abbreviation for trinitrotoluene?",
    "answer": "TNT"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "What is the chemical symbol for copper?",
    "answer": "Cu"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "What is the chemical symbol for gold?",
    "answer": "Au"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "What is the main component of air?",
    "answer": "nitrogen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "What is the more scientific name for quicksilver?",
    "answer": "mercury"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "What is the symbol for iron in chemistry?",
    "answer": "Fe"
  },
  {
    "category": "Chemistry",
    "question": "What is the symbol for silver?",
    "answer": "Ag"
  },
  {
    "category": "Christmas",
    "question": "Name the loner rebel reindeer with the red shiny nose.",
    "answer": "Rudolph"
  },
  {
    "category": "Christmas",
    "question": "Santa Claus reportedly lives at the ????? Pole.",
    "answer": "north"
  },
  {
    "category": "Comic Strip Trivia",
    "question": "What comic strip is set at Camp Swampy?",
    "answer": "Beetle Bailey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Computer Science",
    "question": "That big square thing you're staring at right now is called a ????????",
    "answer": "monitor"
  },
  {
    "category": "Computer Science",
    "question": "The Internet Relay Chat Program, which normally connects to port 6667, is more commonly known as ???.",
    "answer": "IRC"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "--isms:  Exalting one's country above all others.",
    "answer": "nationalism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "--isms:  The belief that there is no God.",
    "answer": "atheism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "--isms:  The theory that man cannot prove the existence of a god.",
    "answer": "agnosticism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-ism: The belief in the existence of a god or gods.",
    "answer": "theism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-isms: A diseased condition resulting from the use of beverages such as whiskey.",
    "answer": "alcoholism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-isms: A one-party system of government in which control is maintained by force and regimentation.",
    "answer": "fascism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-isms: A painful stiffness of the muscles and joints",
    "answer": "rheumatism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-isms: A severe or unfavorable judgment.",
    "answer": "criticism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-isms: An economic system characterized by private ownership and competition.",
    "answer": "capitalism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-isms: Excessive emphasis on financial gain.",
    "answer": "commercialism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-isms: Excessive enthusiasm or zeal for a cause.",
    "answer": "fanaticism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-isms: Poisoning caused by a toxin in improperly prepared food.",
    "answer": "botulism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-isms: Public ownership of the basic means of production, distribution, and exchange.",
    "answer": "socialism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "-isms: The belief in living a very austere and self-denying life.",
    "answer": "asceticism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A clip, shaped like a bar to keep a woman's hair in place is a ???????.",
    "answer": "barrette"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A depilatory is a substance used for removing ????.",
    "answer": "hair"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A device used to change the voltage of alternating currents is a ??????????.",
    "answer": "transformer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A flat, round hat sometimes worn by soldiers is a ?????.",
    "answer": "beret"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A government in which power is restricted to a few is a(n) ??????????.",
    "answer": "oligarchy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A person in his eighties is called a(n) ????????????.",
    "answer": "octogenarian"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A person who starts fires maliciously is a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "arsonist"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A person with a strong desire to steal is a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "kleptomaniac"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A pugilist is a ?????.",
    "answer": "boxer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A receptacle for holy water is a(n) ????.",
    "answer": "font"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A sun-dried grape is known as a(n) ??????.",
    "answer": "raisin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "A word like 'NASA' formed from the initials of other words is a(n) ??????.",
    "answer": "acronym"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Acrophobia is a fear of ???????.",
    "answer": "heights"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "An \"omniscient\" person has unlimited ??????????.",
    "answer": "knowledge"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "An anemometer measures ???? ????????.",
    "answer": "wind velocity"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "An animal stuffer is a(n) ???????????.",
    "answer": "taxidermist"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "An artist supports his canvas on a(n) ?????.",
    "answer": "easel"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "An instrument on a car to measure the distance travelled is called a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "odometer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Androphobia is the fear of ?????.",
    "answer": "males"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(men|males?)",
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Animals that once existed but don't exist now are said to be ???????.",
    "answer": "extinct"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Any object worn as a charm may be called a(n) ??????.",
    "answer": "amulet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Bibliophobia is a fear of ?????.",
    "answer": "books"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Brontophobia is the fear of ???????.",
    "answer": "thunder"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Dendrochronology is better known as ??????????.",
    "answer": "ring dating"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Doraphobia is the fear of ?????????.",
    "answer": "fur"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Eleutherophobia is a fear of ???????.",
    "answer": "freedom"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Gymnophobia is the fear of ??????????.",
    "answer": "naked bodies"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Hills and ridges composed of drifting sand are known as ?????.",
    "answer": "dunes"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Ichthyology is the study of ????????.",
    "answer": "fish"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Legal Terms: A crime more serious than a misdemeanor.",
    "answer": "felony"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Legal Terms: A formal agreement enforceable by law.",
    "answer": "contract"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Legal Terms: A supplement to a will.",
    "answer": "codicil"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Legal Terms: The people chosen to render a verdict in a court.",
    "answer": "jury"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Legal Terms: To steal property entrusted to one's care.",
    "answer": "embezzle"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Name the pain-inflicting person you go to to get your teeth fixed.",
    "answer": "dentist"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Name the porceilan chair you sit on at least once a day.",
    "answer": "toilet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "One who tells fortunes by the stars is a(n) ??????????.",
    "answer": "astrologer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Rats, mice, beavers, and squirrels are all ???????.",
    "answer": "rodents"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The art of tracing designs and taking impressions of them is ???????????.",
    "answer": "lithography"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The covering on the tip of a shoelace is a(n) ?????.",
    "answer": "aglet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The distance around the outside of a circle is its ????????????.",
    "answer": "circumference"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The earth's atmosphere and the space beyond is known as ?????????.",
    "answer": "aerospace"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The effect produced when sound is reflected back is known as a(n) ????.",
    "answer": "echo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The feeling of having experienced something before is known as ???????.",
    "answer": "deja vu"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The science of preparing and dispensing drugs is ????????.",
    "answer": "pharmacy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The science of providing men, equipment and supplies for military operations is called ????????.",
    "answer": "logistics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of human behaviour is ??????????.",
    "answer": "psychology"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of human pre-history is ???????????.",
    "answer": "archaeology"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of insects is ??????????.",
    "answer": "entomology"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of light and its relation to sight is called ??????.",
    "answer": "optics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of man and culture is known as ??????????.",
    "answer": "anthropology"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of natural phenomena: motion, forces, light, sound, etc. is called ??????.",
    "answer": "physics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of plants is ??????.",
    "answer": "botany"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of religion is ????????.",
    "answer": "theology"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of sound is ?????????.",
    "answer": "acoustics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of the composition of substances and the changes that they undergo is ?????????.",
    "answer": "chemistry"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of the earth's physical divisions into mountains, seas, etc. is ?????????.",
    "answer": "geography"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The study of the manner in which organisms carry on their life processes is ?????????.",
    "answer": "physiology"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The symbols used on a map are explained by the ??????.",
    "answer": "legend"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The treatment of disease by chemical substances which are toxic to the causative micro-organisms is called ????????????.",
    "answer": "chemotherapy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The weight at the end of a pendulum is a(n) ??????.",
    "answer": "bob"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The wide wall built along the banks of rivers to stop flooding is a(n) ?????.",
    "answer": "levee"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "The word \"cumulus\" refers to a type of ???????????.",
    "answer": "cloud"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "This instrument is used for measuring the distance between two points, on a curved surface.",
    "answer": "calliper"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "This instrument measures atmospheric pressure.",
    "answer": "barometer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "This instrument measures the velocity of the wind.",
    "answer": "anemometer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "This is the fear of enclosed spaces.",
    "answer": "claustrophobia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "This word is used as the international radio distress call.",
    "answer": "mayday"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "This word means \"split personality\".",
    "answer": "schizophrenia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Throat, foxing, and platform are parts of a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "shoe"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Toxiphobia is a fear of ?????????.",
    "answer": "poison"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What does a brandophile collect?",
    "answer": "cigar bands"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What does a heliologist study?",
    "answer": "the #sun#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What does an ornithologist study?",
    "answer": "birds"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is a device to stem the flow of blood called?",
    "answer": "tourniquet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is a dried plum called?",
    "answer": "prune"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is a female swan called?",
    "answer": "pen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is a figure with eight equal sides called?",
    "answer": "octagon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is another name for a tombstone inscription?",
    "answer": "epitaph"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is measured by a chronometer?",
    "answer": "time"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is the common name for a Japanese dwarf tree?",
    "answer": "bonsai"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is the common name for the Aurora Borealis?",
    "answer": "northern lights"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is the common term for a \"somnambulist\"?",
    "answer": "sleepwalker"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is the name for a branch of a river?",
    "answer": "tributary"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is the study of heredity called?",
    "answer": "genetics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is the study of prehistoric plants and animals called?",
    "answer": "paleontology"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "What is the term for a castrated rooster?",
    "answer": "capon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Definitions",
    "question": "Which science studies weather?",
    "answer": "meteorology"
  },
  {
    "category": "Domestic Metallurgy",
    "question": "Name the clothing wrinkle remover that sounds like a kind of metal.",
    "answer": "iron"
  },
  {
    "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
    "question": "A 3 1/2\" floppy disk measures ??? and 1/2 inches across.",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
    "question": "A brown crayon is what color?",
    "answer": "brown"
  },
  {
    "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
    "question": "A smoke detector will alarm if it detects ?????.",
    "answer": "smoke"
  },
  {
    "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
    "question": "A water heater keeps ????? warm for you.",
    "answer": "water"
  },
  {
    "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
    "question": "Although not all come from France, ?????? fries are often served with hamburgers.",
    "answer": "french"
  },
  {
    "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
    "question": "An ????? clock usually wakes you in the morning.",
    "answer": "alarm"
  },
  {
    "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
    "question": "During the American Revolution, the Boston Tea Party took place in ?????? Harbor.",
    "answer": "boston"
  },
  {
    "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
    "question": "How do you spell abbreviation?",
    "answer": "abbreviation"
  },
  {
    "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
    "question": "How many pencils are there in a dozen?",
    "answer": "twelve"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(twelve|12)",
    "category": "Drama",
    "question": "\"Our Town\" is a play by whom?",
    "answer": "Thornton #Wilder#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Drama",
    "question": "The play \"Our Town\" is set where?",
    "answer": "Grover's Corners"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Grover'?s Corner",
    "category": "Fantasy",
    "question": "What is a sorcerer who deals in black magic called?",
    "answer": "necromancer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food",
    "question": "Boston butt, jowl, and picnic ham are parts of a ??????.",
    "answer": "pig"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Even though it tastes nothing like grapes, a ?????????? is often eaten for breakfast.",
    "answer": "grapefruit"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "From what animal do we get venison?",
    "answer": "deer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "From which fish is caviar obtained?",
    "answer": "sturgeon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "From which fruit is the liqueur Kirsh made?",
    "answer": "cherry"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Iceberg, Boston, and Bibb are types of ?????????.",
    "answer": "lettuce"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Laetrile is associated with the pit of which fruit?",
    "answer": "apricot"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Little round chocolate candies are known as _&m's.",
    "answer": "m"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Mustard, ketchup and onions on a hotdog are all ??????????.",
    "answer": "condiments"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Name the only fruit named for its color.",
    "answer": "orange"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Natural vanilla flavoring comes from this plant.",
    "answer": "orchid"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Often drunk, this liquid is normally harvested from female cows.",
    "answer": "milk"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Often eaten for breakfast, bacon is actually the flesh of what barnyard animal?",
    "answer": "pig"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Often eaten for breakfast, the egg comes from what barnyard animal?",
    "answer": "chicken"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Rum is made from this plant.",
    "answer": "sugar cane"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Vermicelli literally means ???????????.",
    "answer": "little worms"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "What do you get when you add fresh fruit to red wine?",
    "answer": "sangria"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "What is Japanese \"sake\" made from?",
    "answer": "rice"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "What is the name of the syrup drained from raw sugar?",
    "answer": "molasses"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "What kind of nuts are used in marzipan?",
    "answer": "almonds"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Where is the best brandy bottled?",
    "answer": "cognac"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food and Drink",
    "question": "Where was Budweiser first brewed?",
    "answer": "St. Louis"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "St.? Louis",
    "category": "Fun",
    "question": "Cocktails: Bourbon, sugar and mint make a(n) ???????????.",
    "answer": "mint julep"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fun",
    "question": "Cocktails: Cognac (brandy) and white creme de menthe make a(n) ?????????????.",
    "answer": "stinger"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fun",
    "question": "Cocktails: Creme de Cacao, cream, and brandy make a(n) ??????????.",
    "answer": "brandy alexander"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fun",
    "question": "Cocktails: Gin and Collins mix make a(n) ??????????.",
    "answer": "Tom Collins"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fun",
    "question": "Cocktails: Rum, lime, and cola drink make a(n) ????????????.",
    "answer": "cuba libre"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fun",
    "question": "Cocktails: Triple sec, tequila, and lemon or lime juice make a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "margarita"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fun",
    "question": "Cocktails: Vodka and Kahlua make a ???????????.",
    "answer": "black russian"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fun",
    "question": "Cocktails: Vodka, orange juice and Galliano make a(n) ???????????.",
    "answer": "Harvey Wallbanger"
  },
  {
    "category": "Fun",
    "question": "Cocktails: Whiskey, hot coffee, and whipped cream make a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "Irish coffee"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "A bridge hand with no cards in one suit is said to have a ???????.",
    "answer": "void"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "A poker hand consisting of three of a kind and a pair is called a ???????.",
    "answer": "full house"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "How many balls are used in a game of snooker including the cue ball?",
    "answer": "twenty two"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(twenty[- ]two|22)",
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "How many dots are there on a pair of dice?",
    "answer": "forty two"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(forty[- ]two|42)",
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "How many squares are there on a chessboard?",
    "answer": "sixty four"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(sixty[- ]four|64)",
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "If you \"peg out\" what game are you playing?",
    "answer": "cribbage"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "In poker five cards of the same suit is called a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "flush"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "In pool, what color is the eight ball?",
    "answer": "black"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "In which game might a person have a \"full house\"?",
    "answer": "poker"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "In which game or sport are \"Staunton\" pieces used?",
    "answer": "chess"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "In which game or sport can a person be \"skunked\"?",
    "answer": "cribbage"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "In which sport are terms \"spare\" and \"gutter\" used?",
    "answer": "tenpin #bowling#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "In which sport or game are the terms: 'pin', 'fork', and 'skewer' used?",
    "answer": "chess"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "In which sport or game is the term \"rook\" used?",
    "answer": "chess"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "Name the only flexible murder weapon in the game of \"Cluedo\".",
    "answer": "rope"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "Name the only woman suspect in the game of \"Cluedo\" who isn't married.",
    "answer": "Miss #Scarlett#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "These are the two highest valued letters in \"Scrabble\".  \"Q\" and ?????.",
    "answer": "Z"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "This ancient Chinese game is played with 156 small rectangular tiles.",
    "answer": "mah jongg"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "mah? ?jong",
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "This is the lowest ranking suit in Bridge.",
    "answer": "clubs"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "This term denotes a chess move in which both the king and the rook are moved.",
    "answer": "castling"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "What bowling term means three straight strikes?",
    "answer": "turkey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "What game or sport is Bobby Fischer identified with?",
    "answer": "chess"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "What number is on the opposite side of the \"five\" on dice?",
    "answer": "two"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(two|2)",
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "What score is not possible for a cribbage hand?",
    "answer": "nineteen"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(nineteen|19)",
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "Which chess piece is usually valued as 5 points?",
    "answer": "rook"
  },
  {
    "category": "Games",
    "question": "Which game usually begins with, \"Is it animal, vegetable, or mineral?\"",
    "answer": "twenty questions"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(twenty|20) questions",
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "Although it doesn't sound like a dog, ????dust is ornamental wood chips often placed in flowerbeds.",
    "answer": "bark"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "Chicago Transit Authority is now known as which group?",
    "answer": "Chicago"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "If you drive on a parkway, you park on a ????????",
    "answer": "driveway"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "To refuel your car you go to a ????? station.",
    "answer": "petrol"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "Wedding rings are normally worn on what finger of your hand?",
    "answer": "#ring# finger"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What are catalogued under the Dewey decimal system?",
    "answer": "books"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What are the 3 big colleges of the Ivy League? (name them alphabetically)",
    "answer": "Harvard, Princeton, Yale"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Harvard,? Princeton,?( and)? Yale",
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What company makes Pampers disposable diapers?",
    "answer": "Proctor & Gamble"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Proctor (&|and) Gamble",
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What do the initials U.F.O stand for?",
    "answer": "Unidentified Flying Object"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What do the letters in SAM missiles refer to?",
    "answer": "Surface-to-Air Missile"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Surface[- ]to[- ]Air",
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What does IRS stand for?",
    "answer": "Internal Revenue Service"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What does a compass needle point to?",
    "answer": "north"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What does the abbreviation a.m. stand for?",
    "answer": "Ante Meridian"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What does the acronym CIA stand for?",
    "answer": "Central Intelligence Agency"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What is the minimum IQ score for the genius category?",
    "answer": "one hundred and forty"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(one hundred (and |& )?forty|140)",
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "What is this sign called \"&\"?",
    "answer": "ampersand"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "When using a telephone, you must wait for a ???? tone before starting your call.",
    "answer": "dial"
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "question": "Which U.S. president is on the five-dollar bill?",
    "answer": "Abraham #Lincoln#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Acadia was the original name of which Canadian province?",
    "answer": "Nova Scotia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Bridgeport is the largest city in which state?",
    "answer": "Connecticut"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Bridgetown is the capital of ????????.",
    "answer": "Barbados"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Brussels is the capital of which country?",
    "answer": "Belgium"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Frankfort is the capital of which state?",
    "answer": "Kentucky"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Guayaquil is the largest city in what country?",
    "answer": "Ecuador"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Halifax is the capital of which Canadian province?",
    "answer": "Nova Scotia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Havana is the capital of which country?",
    "answer": "Cuba"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "He invented the most common projection for world maps.",
    "answer": "Gerardus #Mercator#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "He visited Australia and New Zealand, then surveyed the Pacific Coast of North America.",
    "answer": "Vancouver"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "How many stars are on the flag of New Zealand?",
    "answer": "four"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(four|4)",
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "If its 4:00pm in Seattle, Washington what time is it in Portland, Oregon?",
    "answer": "#4#:00pm"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what city are the famous Tivoli Gardens?",
    "answer": "Copenhagen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what city is the Leaning Tower?",
    "answer": "Pisa"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what city is the Smithsonian Institute?",
    "answer": "Washington"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is Banff National Park?",
    "answer": "Canada"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is Lahore?",
    "answer": "Pakistan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is Mandalay?",
    "answer": "#Myanmar# (formerly known as Burma)"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(Myanmar|Burma)",
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is Taipei?",
    "answer": "Taiwan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is Thunder Bay?",
    "answer": "Canada"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is the Jutland peninsula?",
    "answer": "Denmark"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is the Mekong River Delta?",
    "answer": "Vietnam"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is the Waterloo battlefield?",
    "answer": "Belgium"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is the highest point in South America?",
    "answer": "Argentina"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is the lowest point in South America?",
    "answer": "Argentina"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what country is the source of the Blue Nile?",
    "answer": "Ethiopia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what island group is Corregidor?",
    "answer": "#Philippine#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what mountain range is Kicking Horse Pass?",
    "answer": "Rocky"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Rock(y|ies)",
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In what state is Concord?",
    "answer": "New Hampshire"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which city is Red Square?",
    "answer": "Moscow"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which city is Saint Paul's Cathedral?",
    "answer": "London"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which city is Wembley Stadium?",
    "answer": "London"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which city is the Bridge of Sighs?",
    "answer": "Venice"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which city is the C.N. Tower?",
    "answer": "Toronto"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which city is the Canale Grande?",
    "answer": "Venice"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which city is the Colliseum located?",
    "answer": "Rome"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which city is the Wailing Wall?",
    "answer": "Jerusalem"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is Angel Falls?",
    "answer": "Venezuela"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is Brest? (NOT Breast!)",
    "answer": "France"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is Chennai (formerly Madras)?",
    "answer": "India"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is Cusco?",
    "answer": "Peru"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is Loch Ness?",
    "answer": "Scotland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is Normandy?",
    "answer": "France"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is Sapporo?",
    "answer": "Japan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is the Calabria region?",
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is the Dalai Lama's palace?",
    "answer": "Tibet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is the Great Victoria Desert?",
    "answer": "Australia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country is the Machu Picchu?",
    "answer": "Peru"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which country would you find the Yucatan Peninsula?",
    "answer": "Mexico"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which ocean or sea are the Seychelles?",
    "answer": "#Indian# Ocean"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state are Gettysburg and the Liberty Bell?",
    "answer": "Pennsylvania"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state are the Finger Lakes?",
    "answer": "New York"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is Appomattax?",
    "answer": "Virginia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is Cape Hatteras?",
    "answer": "North Carolina"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is Hoover Dam?",
    "answer": "Arizona"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is Mount McKinley?",
    "answer": "Alaska"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is Mount St. Helens?",
    "answer": "Washington"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is Mount Vernon?",
    "answer": "Virginia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is Stone Mountain?",
    "answer": "Georgia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is Walla Walla?",
    "answer": "Washington"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is the Kennedy Space Center?",
    "answer": "Florida"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is the Mayo Clinic?",
    "answer": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which state is the Painted Desert?",
    "answer": "Arizona"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Into what bay does the Ganges River flow?",
    "answer": "Bay Of #Bengal#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Into what body of water does the Danube River flow?",
    "answer": "Black Sea"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Into what body of water does the Yukon River flow?",
    "answer": "#Bering# Sea"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Into what sea does the Elbe River flow?",
    "answer": "#North# Sea"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Into what sea does the Mackenzie River flow?",
    "answer": "#Beaufort# Sea"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Khartoum is the capital of which country?",
    "answer": "Sudan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Kingston is the capital of which country?",
    "answer": "Jamaica"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Linz, Austria is a leading port on which river?",
    "answer": "Danube"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Madrid and Lisbon are both located near this river.",
    "answer": "Tagus"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Meridians converge at the ????????.",
    "answer": "#pole#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Mount Victoria is the highest peak of this island country.",
    "answer": "Fiji"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name a country which has the same name as a bird.",
    "answer": "Turkey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the U.S. state with the smallest population.",
    "answer": "Alaska"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the capital city of Massachusetts.",
    "answer": "Boston"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the capital city of Rhode Island.",
    "answer": "Providence"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the capital of Argentina.",
    "answer": "Buenos Aires"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the capital of Brazil.",
    "answer": "Brasilia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the capital of Italy.",
    "answer": "Rome"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the city at the west end of Lake Superior.",
    "answer": "Duluth"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the continent that consists of a single country.",
    "answer": "Australia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the desert located in south-east California.",
    "answer": "Mojave"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the large mountain chain in the eastern U.S.A.",
    "answer": "The #Appalachian#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the largest cathedral in the world.",
    "answer": "St. Peter's"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "St.? ?Peter'?s",
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the largest city in Canada.",
    "answer": "Toronto"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the largest island in the world.",
    "answer": "Greenland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the largest lake in Australia.",
    "answer": "Eyre"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the largest river forming part of the U.S. - Mexican border.",
    "answer": "Rio Grande"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the last province to become part of Canada.",
    "answer": "Newfoundland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the longest river in Asia.",
    "answer": "Yangtze"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the longest river in Nigeria.",
    "answer": "Niger"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the most north-easterly of the 48 contiguous states.",
    "answer": "Maine"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the only Central American country without an Atlantic coastline.",
    "answer": "El Salvador"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the sea between Asia Minor and Greece.",
    "answer": "Aegean"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the sea between Korea and China.",
    "answer": "#Yellow# Sea"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the sea north of Alaska.",
    "answer": "Beaufort"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the sea north of Murmansk, Russia.",
    "answer": "Barents"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the sea west of Alaska.",
    "answer": "Bering"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the second largest country in Africa.",
    "answer": "Algeria"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the second largest country in South America.",
    "answer": "Argentina"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the second largest lake in North America.",
    "answer": "Huron"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the smallest of the Great Lakes.",
    "answer": "Ontario"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the strait joining the Atlantic Ocean and the Mediterranean Sea.",
    "answer": "Gibraltar"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Name the world's most photographed and most climbed mountain.",
    "answer": "Fuji"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Nassau is the capital of which country?",
    "answer": "Bahamas"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "On what island is Honolulu?",
    "answer": "Oahu"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "On what island is Pearl Harbour?",
    "answer": "Oahu"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "On what island is the Blue Grotto?",
    "answer": "Capri"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "On what island is the U.S. naval base, Guantanamo?",
    "answer": "Cuba"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "On what mountain are four presidents' faces carved?",
    "answer": "Rushmore"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "On what peninsula are Spain and Portugal located?",
    "answer": "The #Iberia#n peninsula"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "On what river is the capital city of Canada?",
    "answer": "Ottawa"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "On which river is London, England?",
    "answer": "Thames"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "On which river is Rome located?",
    "answer": "Tiber"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "On which river is the Aswan High Dam?",
    "answer": "Nile"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Over 75% of the Earth's surface is covered by some form of ?????.",
    "answer": "Water"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Rabat is the capital of which country?",
    "answer": "Morocco"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "San Francisco Bay is located near what city?",
    "answer": "San Francisco"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Seoul is the capital of which country?",
    "answer": "South Korea"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "St. George's is the capital city of what island country?",
    "answer": "Grenada"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Surfing is believed to have originated here.",
    "answer": "Hawaii"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The Auckland Islands belong to which country?",
    "answer": "New Zealand"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The Hebrides are part of this country.",
    "answer": "Scotland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The Ionian and Cyclades are island groups of which country?",
    "answer": "Greece"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The Little Mermaid is found in the harbour of which city?",
    "answer": "Copenhagen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The Nationalist Chinese occupy this island.",
    "answer": "Taiwan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The Thatcher Ferry Bridge crosses what canal?",
    "answer": "#Panama# Canal"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The United States is made up of ?? states.",
    "answer": "50"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The Volta is the largest river in which country?",
    "answer": "Ghana"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The countries of Belgium, Netherlands, and Luxembourg are together called ????????.",
    "answer": "Benelux"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The longest river in Western Europe is ??????????",
    "answer": "Rhine"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "The sun sets in the ?????",
    "answer": "west"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This Canadian island is the world's fifth largest.",
    "answer": "Baffin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This Pacific island's puzzling monoliths attract ethnologists.",
    "answer": "Easter Island"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This country is divided at the 38th parallel.",
    "answer": "Korea"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This country occupies the \"horn of Africa\".",
    "answer": "Somalia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This country's flag has a large \"R\" on it.",
    "answer": "Rwanda"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This imaginary line approximately follows the 180 degree meridian through the Pacific Ocean.",
    "answer": "international date line"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This is called the \"Honeymoon Capital\" of the world.",
    "answer": "Niagara Falls"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This is the bridge with the longest span in the U.S.A.",
    "answer": "Verrazano Narrows"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "verrazano",
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This is the only borough of New York City that is not on an island.",
    "answer": "The #Bronx#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This is the port city serving Tokyo.",
    "answer": "Yokohama"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This is the residence of English monarchs.",
    "answer": "Buckingham Palace"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This island group is off the east coast of southern South America.",
    "answer": "#Falkland# Islands"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This re-opened in 1975 after being closed for 8 years.",
    "answer": "Suez Canal"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "This section of Manhattan is noted for its Negro and Latin American residents.",
    "answer": "Harlem"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "To what country do the Faeroe Islands belong?",
    "answer": "Denmark"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "To what country does the Gaza Strip belong?",
    "answer": "Egypt"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "True Or False:  The Easter Bunny is from Easter Island.",
    "answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "True Or False:  There are only virgins on the Virgin Islands.",
    "answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Under what river does the Holland Tunnel run?",
    "answer": "Hudson"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Warsaw is the capital of what country?",
    "answer": "Poland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What American city is known as Little Havana?",
    "answer": "Miami"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What Asian city was once called Edo?",
    "answer": "Tokyo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What Canadian city is at the west end of Lake Ontario?",
    "answer": "Hamilton"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What European country administers the island of Martinique?",
    "answer": "France"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What European country has \"Vaduz\" as its capital city?",
    "answer": "Liechtenstein"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What London borough does the Prime Meridian pass through?",
    "answer": "Greenwich"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What U.S. city is known as Insurance City?",
    "answer": "Hartford"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What U.S. city is named after Saint Francis of Assisi?",
    "answer": "San Francisco"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What U.S. state is known as The Land of 10,000 Lakes?",
    "answer": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What US state is completely surrounded by the Pacific Ocean?",
    "answer": "Hawaii"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What are drumlins and eskers formed by?",
    "answer": "#glacier#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What are the worlds four oceans - alphabetically?",
    "answer": "Arctic, Atlantic, Indian and Pacific"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Arctic,? Atlantic,? Indian(,| and)? Pacific",
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What body of water borders Saudi Arabia to the east?",
    "answer": "Persian Gulf"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What canal connects Lake Ontario and Lake Erie?",
    "answer": "Welland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What city boasts the Copacabana Beach and Ipanema?",
    "answer": "#Rio# de Janeiro"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What city is associated with Alcatraz?",
    "answer": "San Francisco"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What city is on Lake Erie at the mouth of the Cuyahoga River?",
    "answer": "Cleveland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What city is the Christian Science Monitor based in?",
    "answer": "Boston"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What city is the Kremlin located in?",
    "answer": "Moscow"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What city was the setting for \"Gone With the Wind\"?",
    "answer": "Atlanta"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What color does the bride wear in China?",
    "answer": "red"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What continent is Cyprus considered to be part of?",
    "answer": "Asia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What continent is the home to the greatest number of countries?",
    "answer": "Africa"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country are the Islands of Quemoy and Matsu part of?",
    "answer": "Taiwan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country borders Egypt on the west?",
    "answer": "Libya"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country borders Egypt to the south?",
    "answer": "Sudan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country does the island of Mykonos belong to?",
    "answer": "Greece"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country formed the union of Tanganyika and Zanzibar?",
    "answer": "Tanzania"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country has the world's most southerly city?",
    "answer": "Chile"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country is Phnom Penh the capital of?",
    "answer": "Cambodia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country is Santo Domingo the capital of?",
    "answer": "Dominican Republic"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country is directly north of Israel?",
    "answer": "Lebanon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country is directly north of the continental United States?",
    "answer": "Canada"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country is directly west of Spain?",
    "answer": "Portugal"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country is known as the Hellenic Republic?",
    "answer": "Greece"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country is located between Panama and Nicaragua?",
    "answer": "Costa Rica"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country owns the island of Corfu?",
    "answer": "Greece"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country was once known as Gaul?",
    "answer": "France"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country was the setting for \"Casablanca\"?",
    "answer": "Morocco"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What country was the setting for \"Doctor Zhivago\"?",
    "answer": "Russia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What famous geyser erupts regularly at the Yellowstone National Park?",
    "answer": "Old Faithful"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Alaska?",
    "answer": "Juneau"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Bangladesh?",
    "answer": "Dacca"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(dhakk?a|dacc?a)",
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Burma?",
    "answer": "Rangoon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Chile?",
    "answer": "Santiago"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Colorado?",
    "answer": "Denver"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Florida?",
    "answer": "Tallahassee"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of India?",
    "answer": "New Delhi"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Indonesia?",
    "answer": "Jakarta"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Kansas?",
    "answer": "Topeka"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Maine?",
    "answer": "Augusta"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Nebraska",
    "answer": "Lincoln"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Lin?coln",
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of New Zealand?",
    "answer": "Wellington"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Washington state?",
    "answer": "Olympia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of West Virginia?",
    "answer": "Charleston"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Wisconsin?",
    "answer": "Madison"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of Zimbabwe?",
    "answer": "Harare"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the capital of the United Arab Emirates?",
    "answer": "Abu Dhabi"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the current name for south-west Africa?",
    "answer": "Namibia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the highest mountain in Canada?",
    "answer": "Mt. #Logan#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the largest city in Australia, in terms of population?",
    "answer": "Sydney"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the largest city in China?",
    "answer": "Shanghai"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the largest of the countries in Central America?",
    "answer": "Nicaragua"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the monetary unit of India?",
    "answer": "Rupee"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the most sacred river in India?",
    "answer": "Ganges"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Gang(a|es)",
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the official language of Egypt?",
    "answer": "Arabic"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the principal river of Ireland?",
    "answer": "Shannon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the second largest of the United States?",
    "answer": "Texas"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the smallest Canadian province?",
    "answer": "Prince Edward Island"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the smallest independent state in the world?",
    "answer": "#Vatican# City"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the smallest of the Central American countries?",
    "answer": "El Salvador"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What is the world's highest city?",
    "answer": "Lhasa"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What island has Hamilton as its capital?",
    "answer": "Bermuda"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What island is known as the Spice Island?",
    "answer": "Zanzibar"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What mountain range separates Europe from Asia?",
    "answer": "Ural"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What prison island was off the coast of French Guiana?",
    "answer": "#Devil#'s Island"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What river has the largest drainage basin?",
    "answer": "Amazon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What river is Liverpool on?",
    "answer": "Mersey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What river is called \"Old Man River\"?",
    "answer": "Mississippi"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What river is known as China's Sorrow?",
    "answer": "Yellow"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What river is the Temple of Karnak near?",
    "answer": "Nile"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What sea is between Italy and Yugoslavia?",
    "answer": "Adriatic"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What south American country has both a Pacific and Atlantic coastline?",
    "answer": "Colombia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What state borders Alabama to the north?",
    "answer": "Tennessee"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What state is the Golden State?",
    "answer": "California"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What state was the home to Mayberry?",
    "answer": "North Carolina"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What symbol is on the flag of Vietnam?",
    "answer": "star"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What unit of currency will buy you dinner in Iraq, Jordan, Tunisia, and Yugoslavia?",
    "answer": "Dinar"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What volcano showers ash on Sicily?",
    "answer": "Etna"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What's the former name of Istanbul?",
    "answer": "Constantinople"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "What's the highest mountain in the 48 contiguous U.S. states?",
    "answer": "Whitney"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where are the Nazca Lines?",
    "answer": "Peru"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where are the pyramids located?",
    "answer": "Egypt"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where is Beacon Street?",
    "answer": "Boston"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where is Euston Station?",
    "answer": "London"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where is George Washington buried?",
    "answer": "Mt. Vernon, Virginia"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "M(oun)?t.? ?Vernon",
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where is Queen Maud Land located?",
    "answer": "Antarctica"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where is Westminster Abbey located?",
    "answer": "London"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where is the Admirality Arch?",
    "answer": "London"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where is the Holy Kaaba?",
    "answer": "Mecca"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where is the Parthenon located?",
    "answer": "Athens"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where is the city of Brotherly Love?",
    "answer": "Philadelphia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Where were the Pillars of Hercules located?",
    "answer": "Gibraltar"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which Canadian province extends farthest north?",
    "answer": "Quebec"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which Central American country extends furthest north?",
    "answer": "Belize"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which European country has the highest population density?",
    "answer": "Monaco"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which European country has the lowest population density?",
    "answer": "Iceland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which Irish city is famous for its crystal?",
    "answer": "Waterford"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which U.S. city is known as Beantown?",
    "answer": "Boston"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which U.S. city is known as the Biggest Little City in the World?",
    "answer": "Reno"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which U.S. state borders a Canadian territory?",
    "answer": "Alaska"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which U.S. state has the least rainfall?",
    "answer": "Nevada"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which U.S. state receives the most rainfall?",
    "answer": "Hawaii"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which capital is known as the Glass Capital of the World?",
    "answer": "Toledo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which city has the largest rodeo in the world?",
    "answer": "Calgary"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which city is known as Motown?",
    "answer": "Detroit"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which city is known as the Windy City?",
    "answer": "Chicago"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which city is on the east side of San Francisco Bay?",
    "answer": "Oakland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which country administers Christmas Island?",
    "answer": "Australia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which country are the Galapagos Islands part of?",
    "answer": "Ecuador"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which country borders Italy, Switzerland, West Germany, Czechoslovakia, Hungary, Yugoslavia, and Liechtenstein?",
    "answer": "Austria"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which country developed \"Tae-Kwan-Do\"?",
    "answer": "Korea"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which country has Ankara as its capital?",
    "answer": "Turkey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which country has Budapest as its capital?",
    "answer": "Hungary"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which country has the longest land border?",
    "answer": "China"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which country hosted the 1982 World Cup of soccer?",
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which country uses the \"yen\" for currency?",
    "answer": "Japan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which country would come first in an alphabetical list of countries?",
    "answer": "Afghanistan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which islands were named after Prince Philip of Spain?",
    "answer": "The #Philippine#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which mainland Latin American country is in neither South America nor Central America?",
    "answer": "Mexico"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which of the 48 contiguous states extends farthest north?",
    "answer": "Minnesota"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which of the U.S. states borders only one other state?",
    "answer": "Maine"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which river contains the most fresh water?",
    "answer": "Amazon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which state has the most hospitals?",
    "answer": "California"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which state is divided into two parts by a large lake?",
    "answer": "Michigan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which state is the Evergreen State?",
    "answer": "Washington"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which state is the Garden State?",
    "answer": "New Jersey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which state is the Wolverine State?",
    "answer": "Michigan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "With what country is Fidel Castro associated?",
    "answer": "Cuba"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "With which country is Prince Rainier III identified?",
    "answer": "Monaco"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geogrpahy",
    "question": "Name the capital city of Utah.",
    "answer": "Salt Lake City"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "Earth's outer layer of surface soil or crust is called the ???????.",
    "answer": "Lithosphere"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "Peat, lignite and bituminous are types of ?????????.",
    "answer": "coal"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "Slate is formed by the metamorphosis of ?????????.",
    "answer": "shale"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "The green variety of beryl is called ????????.",
    "answer": "emerald"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "The molten material from a volcano is ?????????",
    "answer": "lava"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "The spot on the Earth's surface directly above an earthquake's focus is called the ??????.",
    "answer": "epicenter"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "The violet variety of quartz is called ????????.",
    "answer": "amethyst"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "There are three types of rocks: metamorphic, sedimentary, and ?????????.",
    "answer": "igneous"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "These limestone deposits rise from the floor of caves.",
    "answer": "stalagmites"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "This is the hardest naturally occurring substance.",
    "answer": "diamond"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geology",
    "question": "What name is used to describe permanently-frozen subsoil?",
    "answer": "permafrost"
  },
  {
    "category": "Hahaha",
    "question": "This normally has 4 legs and your butt is parked in it right now.",
    "answer": "chair"
  },
  {
    "category": "Hirtory",
    "question": "Name the first black nation to gain freedom from European colonial rule.",
    "answer": "Haiti"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Britain and Argentina fought over these islands in 1982.",
    "answer": "#Falkland#s Islands"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Canadian Prime Minister: Pierre Elliott ??????????.",
    "answer": "Trudeau"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Churchill, F.D. Roosvelt and Stalin met here in 1945.",
    "answer": "Yalta"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Eras are divided into units called ????????.",
    "answer": "periods"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "For what country did Columbus make his historic voyage?",
    "answer": "Spain"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Four Japanese carriers were destroyed in this battle.",
    "answer": "Midway"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Frankish ruler Charles the Great is better known as ?????????.",
    "answer": "Charlemagne"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "From what country did the U.S. buy the Virgin Islands?",
    "answer": "Denmark"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "General Sherman burned this city in 1864.",
    "answer": "Atlanta"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Germany's WW I allies were Austria-Hungary, Bulgaria, and ????????.",
    "answer": "Turkey"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Germany's allies in WW II were Japan, Italy, Hungary, Bulgaria, Finland, Libya, and ?????????.",
    "answer": "Romania"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He allowed the bugging of the Democratic Committee headquarters.",
    "answer": "Richard #Nixon#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He discovered the Grand Canyon.",
    "answer": "Francisco #Coronado#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He is identified with the expression, \"Eureka\".",
    "answer": "Archimedes"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He is said to have fiddled while Rome burned.",
    "answer": "Nero"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He led 900 followers in a mass suicide in 1979.",
    "answer": "Jim Jones"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He ordered the persecution of Christians in which Peter and Paul died.",
    "answer": "Nero"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He received the Nobel Peace Prize in 1964 for his civil rights leadership.",
    "answer": "#Martin Luther King# Jr."
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He said, \"I have nothing to offer but blood, tears, toil and sweat.\"",
    "answer": "Sir Winston #Churchill#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He shot Lee Harvey Oswald.",
    "answer": "Jack Ruby"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He taught Alexander the Great.",
    "answer": "Aristotle"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He was assassinated on Dec. 8, 1980 in New York City.",
    "answer": "John Lennon"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He was assassinated on Nov. 22, 1963.",
    "answer": "John Fitzgerald #Kennedy#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He was defeated at the Battle of Little Bighorn.",
    "answer": "General #Custer#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He was stabbed by Gaius Cassius Longinus.",
    "answer": "Julius Caesar"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He was the American inventor of the Cotton Gin.",
    "answer": "Eli #Whitney#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "He was the U.S. president during the Civil War.",
    "answer": "Abraham #Lincoln#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "His ship was the H.M.S. Beagle.",
    "answer": "Charles #Darwin#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "His wife was Roxana. His horse was Bacephalus. He was ????????.",
    "answer": "Alexander the Great"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "How do you write 69 in Roman numerals?",
    "answer": "LXIX"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "How many astronauts manned each Apollo flight?",
    "answer": "three"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(three|3)",
    "category": "History",
    "question": "How old was John F. Kennedy when he became president?",
    "answer": "forty three"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(forty[- ]three|43)",
    "category": "History",
    "question": "In 1902 this volcano erupted, killing 30,000.",
    "answer": "Pelee"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "In what country did \"Sepoy Mutiny\" occur?",
    "answer": "India"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "In which city was President Kennedy killed?",
    "answer": "Dallas"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "In which city were the Hanging Gardens?",
    "answer": "Babylon"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "In which country did the Boxer Rebellion take place?",
    "answer": "China"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "In which country was Adolf Hitler born?",
    "answer": "Austria"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "In which country was the Rosetta Stone found?",
    "answer": "Egypt"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Israel occupied the Golan Heights.  Whose territory was it?",
    "answer": "Syria"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Israel occupied the West Bank.  It belonged to ???????.",
    "answer": "Jordan"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "John F. Kennedy Airport in New York used to be called ??????????.",
    "answer": "Idlewind"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Mussolini invaded this country in 1935.",
    "answer": "Ethiopia"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Name Jacques Cousteau's research ship.",
    "answer": "Calypso"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Name the incident in which tea was dumped into the harbour.",
    "answer": "Boston Tea Party"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Boston Tea[- ]Party",
    "category": "History",
    "question": "One who fought professionally in Roman arenas was a(n) ????????????.",
    "answer": "Gladiator"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "She overcame her handicaps to become a lecturer and a scholar.",
    "answer": "Helen #Keller#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "She was Queen of Egypt and mistress of Julius Caesar.",
    "answer": "Cleopatra"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "She was called \"The Maid of Orleans\".",
    "answer": "Joan of Arc"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "She was the first First Lady to be received privately by the Pope.",
    "answer": "Jackie #Kennedy#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "She was the first woman premier of Israel.",
    "answer": "Golda #Meir#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "She was the first woman to fly the Atlantic solo.",
    "answer": "Amelia #Earhart#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "She was the first woman to swim the English channel.",
    "answer": "Gertrude Caroline #Ederle#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "She was the greatest trick shot artist of all time.",
    "answer": "Annie Oakley"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "She won the 1979 Nobel Peace Prize for her work among the poor.",
    "answer": "Mother Teresa"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Spain ceded Florida to Britain in exchange for this territory.",
    "answer": "Cuba"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "The \"Bay of Pigs\" fiasco took place in this country.",
    "answer": "Cuba"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "The Devonian Period is also known as the Age of ??????????.",
    "answer": "fish"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "The Inquisition forced him to recant his belief in the Copernican Theory.",
    "answer": "Galileo"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "The Romans built these to convey water.",
    "answer": "aqueducts"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "The St. Valentine's Day massacre took place in this city.",
    "answer": "Chicago"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "The first dog in space was named ?????????.",
    "answer": "Laika"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "The last line of this document is \"Working men of all countries, unite.\"",
    "answer": "Communist Manifesto"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This F.B.I agent headed the investigation of Al Capone.",
    "answer": "Elliot Ness"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This French peasant girl led the army to victories.",
    "answer": "Joan of Arc"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This Indian group ruled in early Peru.",
    "answer": "Inca"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This Nazi leader had his six children poisoned prior to his own death.",
    "answer": "Joseph #Goebbels#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This Queen of France was beheaded in 1793.",
    "answer": "Marie Antoinette"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This Roman killed himself after his defeat at Actium.",
    "answer": "Marc Antony"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Anth?ony",
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This Sioux Indian toured with Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show.",
    "answer": "Sitting Bull"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This Spaniard conquered Mexico.",
    "answer": "Hernando #Cortez#"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "corte[sz]",
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This U.S. Secretary of State won the Nobel Peace Prize in 1973.",
    "answer": "Henry #Kissinger#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This U.S. president was fatally shot in 1881.",
    "answer": "James #Garfield#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This assassin of Julius Caesar was his friend.",
    "answer": "Brutus"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This frontiersman and politician was killed at the Alamo.",
    "answer": "Davy #Crockett#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This is said to be history's greatest military evacuation.",
    "answer": "Dunkirk"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This military attack took place on Dec. 7, 1941.",
    "answer": "Pearl Harbour"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This organization was founded by William Booth.",
    "answer": "Salvation Army"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This racist organization was formed in Tennessee in 1865.",
    "answer": "Ku Klux Klan"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This war began on June 25, 1950.",
    "answer": "Korean"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This was the largest real estate deal in U.S. history.",
    "answer": "Louisiana Purchase"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "This word describes the Nazi annihilation of Jews.",
    "answer": "holocaust"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Those big black CD's that you see at garage sales that people call \"albums\" are made of ?????.",
    "answer": "vinyl"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Two 747's collided here in 1977.",
    "answer": "Canary Islands"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "U.S. President, Chester Alan ????????.",
    "answer": "Arthur"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "U.S. President, Herbert C. ?????????.",
    "answer": "Hoover"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "U.S. President, John Quincy ????????.",
    "answer": "Adams"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "U.S. President: Calvin ?????????.",
    "answer": "Coolidge"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What American feminist went bust as a silver dollar?",
    "answer": "Susan B. #Anthony#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What Chinese dynasty was overthrown in 1911?",
    "answer": "Manchu"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What age preceded the Iron Age?",
    "answer": "The #Bronze# Age"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What did President J. Buchanan not have?",
    "answer": "A #wife#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What did presidents Madison, Monroe, Polk, and Garfield have in common?",
    "answer": "The first name \"#James#\""
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What group landed in America in 1620?",
    "answer": "The #Pilgrim#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What is the Roman numeral for fifty?",
    "answer": "L"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What is the name of the Russian Czar's daughter who might-or might not-have survived the Russian revolution?",
    "answer": "Anastasia"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What volcano destroyed Pompeii?",
    "answer": "Vesuvius"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What was the instrument of execution during the \"Reign of Terror\"?",
    "answer": "guillotine"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What was the name of Plato's school?",
    "answer": "Academy"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What was the name of the B-29 used at Hiroshima to drop the bomb?",
    "answer": "Enola Gay"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What was the nationality of the prisoners in the \"Black hole of Calcutta\"?",
    "answer": "British"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What was the third country to get the \"bomb\"?",
    "answer": "Britain"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "What's the resting place of those buried at sea?",
    "answer": "Davey Jones's Locker"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(Dave?y Jones's? Locker)",
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Which U.S. president said, \"The buck stops here\"?",
    "answer": "Truman"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Which military battle took place in 1815?",
    "answer": "Waterloo"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Which nation was led by Genghis Khan?",
    "answer": "The #Mongol#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Which president was responsible for the Louisiana Purchase?",
    "answer": "Jefferson"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who is \"The Iron Lady\"?",
    "answer": "Margaret Thatcher"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who led the attack on the Alamo?",
    "answer": "Santa Ana"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "santa ann?a",
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who rode naked through the streets of Coventry?",
    "answer": "Lady Godiva"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who said \"Veni, vidi, vici\" (I came, I saw, I conquered)?",
    "answer": "Julius #Caesar#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who said: \"Let them eat cake\"?",
    "answer": "Marie Antoinette"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who sang Happy Birthday to John F. Kennedy for his 45th?",
    "answer": "Marilyn Monroe"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who succeeded Churchill when he resigned in 1955?",
    "answer": "Sir Anthony #Eden#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who was \"The Mad Monk\"?",
    "answer": "Rasputin"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who was George Washington's vice-president?",
    "answer": "Adams"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who was the first chancellor of West Germany after WW II?",
    "answer": "Konrad #Adenauer#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who was the second man to set foot on the moon?",
    "answer": "Edwin \"Buzz\" #Aldrin#"
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Who was, \"First in war, first in peace and first in the hearts of his countrymen\"?",
    "answer": "George Washington"
  },
  {
    "category": "IRC",
    "question": "What three letters are overly used to indicate \"Laugh Out Loud\"?",
    "answer": "lol"
  },
  {
    "category": "Langauge",
    "question": "Many Meanings:  Fuel, vapor, flattulence, helium.  What is it?",
    "answer": "gas"
  },
  {
    "category": "Language",
    "question": "Multiple Meanings:  Drinking utensils or sight-enhancers.",
    "answer": "glasses"
  },
  {
    "category": "Language",
    "question": "Multiple Meanings:  Slamming your hands together quickly, or a venereal disease.",
    "answer": "clap"
  },
  {
    "category": "Language",
    "question": "Name the soda that is often confused with a drug.",
    "answer": "Coke"
  },
  {
    "category": "Language",
    "question": "Subject, verb and object are parts of a ?????????.",
    "answer": "sentence"
  },
  {
    "category": "Language",
    "question": "This animal is found at the beginning of an (English) encyclopedia",
    "answer": "aardvark"
  },
  {
    "category": "Language",
    "question": "What is the only English word formed by the first three letters of the alphabet?",
    "answer": "cab"
  },
  {
    "category": "Language",
    "question": "What three letter word means the same as \"to ingest\"?",
    "answer": "eat"
  },
  {
    "category": "Languages",
    "question": "\"faux pas\" means ???????????.",
    "answer": "mistake"
  },
  {
    "category": "Languages",
    "question": "Mardi Gras is French for ???????????.",
    "answer": "fat tuesday"
  },
  {
    "category": "Languages",
    "question": "The name Australia is derived from the Latin word \"australis\" which means ???????.",
    "answer": "southern"
  },
  {
    "category": "Languages",
    "question": "The name for this semi-precious stone comes from the Latin for \"sea water\"",
    "answer": "aquamarine"
  },
  {
    "category": "Languages",
    "question": "What ONE word fits? ????hood; ????hole; ????date.",
    "answer": "man"
  },
  {
    "category": "Languages",
    "question": "What ONE word fits? ????stream; ????hill; ?????pour.",
    "answer": "down"
  },
  {
    "category": "Languages",
    "question": "What does \"c'est la vie\" mean?",
    "answer": "that's life"
  },
  {
    "category": "Languages",
    "question": "What word contains the combination of letters: \"xop\"?",
    "answer": "saXOPhone"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "\"The Diary of Anne Frank\" was first published in English under what title?",
    "answer": "The #Diary of a Young Girl#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "Captain Hook, Tiger Lily, and Tinker Bell are characters in what story?",
    "answer": "Peter Pan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "Dr. Seuss wrote this book: The Cat in the ??????.",
    "answer": "Hat"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "Edgar Allen Poe wrote a famous poem about this animal.",
    "answer": "raven"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "From which Shakespeare play is this line taken: \"Double, double ... \"",
    "answer": "Macbeth"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "From which Shakespeare play is this line taken: \"Goodnight, goodnight! Parting is such sweet sorrow, That I should say goodnight till it be morrow.\"",
    "answer": "Romeo and Juliet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "From which Shakespeare play is this line taken: \"To be or not to be?\"",
    "answer": "Hamlet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "From which Shakespeare play is this line taken: \"What in a name? That which we call a rose, by any other name would smell as sweet.\"",
    "answer": "Romeo and Juliet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "How many lines are in a sonnet?",
    "answer": "fourteen"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(fourteen|14)",
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "How many plays is Shakespeare generally credited with today?",
    "answer": "thirty seven"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(thirty[- ]seven|37)",
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "Name the Shakespeare play from this ultra short plot summary: Urged on by his wife, a man murders his king in order to take his place.",
    "answer": "Macbeth"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "Stephen King's: \"Pet ????????\".",
    "answer": "Semetary"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "Stephen King's: \"Salem's ?????????\".",
    "answer": "Lot"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "Stephen King's: \"The Dead ????????\".",
    "answer": "Zone"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "This Shakespearean king was the actual king of Scotland for 17 years.",
    "answer": "Macbeth"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "This girl hid from the Nazis in Amsterdam.",
    "answer": "Anne Frank"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "What Shakespearean play features the line: A plague on both your houses?",
    "answer": "Romeo and Juliet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "What did Jeannie C. Riley describe as \"a little Peyton Place\"?",
    "answer": "Harper Valley"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "What other name does Stephen King write under?",
    "answer": "Richard #Bachman#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "What publication was subtitled The What's New Magazine?",
    "answer": "Popular Science"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "What was the name of Mother Goose's son?",
    "answer": "Jack"
  },
  {
    "category": "Literature",
    "question": "What's Penthouse's sister publication for women?",
    "answer": "Viva"
  },
  {
    "category": "Litterature",
    "question": "Homer wrote this account of the Trojan War.",
    "answer": "Iliad"
  },
  {
    "category": "Logic",
    "question": "You are in a room where all walls face south.  A bear walks by.  What color is it?",
    "answer": "White"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "A U.S. dime is worth ??? cents.",
    "answer": "ten"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(ten|10)",
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "A line drawn from an angle of a triangle to the mid-point of the opposite side is a(n) ???????.",
    "answer": "median"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "A triangle with three equal sides is called ???????.",
    "answer": "equilateral"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "A triangle with two equal sides is called ??????????.",
    "answer": "isosceles"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "An angle greater than 180 degrees and less than 360 degrees is a(n) ???????? angle.",
    "answer": "reflex"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "An angle greater than 90 degrees and less than 180 degrees is said to be ?????????.",
    "answer": "obtuse"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "An integer that is greater than 1 and is divisible only by itself and 1 is known as a(n) ???????.",
    "answer": "prime"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "Approximately how many inches are there in one meter?",
    "answer": "thirty nine"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(thirty[- ]nine|39)",
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "Arc, radius, and sector are parts of a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "circle"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "He is known as \"The Father of Geometry\".",
    "answer": "Euclid"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "How many corners are there in a cube?",
    "answer": "eight"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(eight|8)",
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "How many nickles are there in 2.25?",
    "answer": "forty five"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(forty[- ]five|45)",
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "If you cut through a solid sphere what shape will the flat area be?",
    "answer": "circle"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "Name the number system which uses only the symbols 1 and 0.",
    "answer": "The #binary# system"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "The angles inside a square total ??????? degrees.",
    "answer": "three hundred and sixty"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(three hundred (and |& )?sixty|360)",
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "The mathematical study of properties of lines, angels, etc., is ????????.",
    "answer": "geometry"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "The space occupied by a body is called its ??????.",
    "answer": "volume"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "The square root of 1 is?",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "Two angles that total 180 degrees are called ???????.",
    "answer": "supplementary"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mathematics",
    "question": "What geometric shape has 4 equal sides?",
    "answer": "square"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "A baby doctor is a ?????????.",
    "answer": "pediatrician"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "A bone specialist is a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "osteopath"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "A loss of memory is known as ??????????.",
    "answer": "amnesia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "A medicine that hastens the emptying of the bowels is called a ????????.",
    "answer": "laxative"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "A non-cancerous tumor is said to be ???????.",
    "answer": "benign"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "A thread used in surgery to tie a bleeding blood vessel is called a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "ligature"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Carditis, affects the ????????.",
    "answer": "heart"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Doctors often have this instrument around their neck.",
    "answer": "stethoscope"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Due to a lack of vitamin C, sailors used to contract this disease.",
    "answer": "scurvy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Encephalitis affects the ????????.",
    "answer": "brain"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Gastritis affects the ??????????.",
    "answer": "stomach"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Hammer, anvil, and stirrup are parts of the ????????.",
    "answer": "ear"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "He discovered the process of vaccination for prevention of smallpox.",
    "answer": "Edward #Jenner#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Hepatitis affects the ??????????.",
    "answer": "Liver"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "How many bones are there in the human body?",
    "answer": "two hundred and six"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(two hundred (and |& )?six|206)",
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "How many chambers does the human heart have?",
    "answer": "four"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(four|4)",
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "How many pints of blood does the average human have in his/her body?",
    "answer": "twelve"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(twelve|12)",
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "In the field of psychiatry this term means self-love.",
    "answer": "narcissism"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "In what organ of the body is insulin produced?",
    "answer": "pancreas"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "In which organ is a clear watery solution known as the \"aqueous humor\" found?",
    "answer": "eye"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "In which organ is a pulmonary disease located?",
    "answer": "lung"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "In which organ is your \"hypothalmus\" located?",
    "answer": "brain"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Infantile Paralysis is commonly known as ????????.",
    "answer": "polio"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Meningitis affects the ?????????.",
    "answer": "brain"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Myositis affects the ?????????.",
    "answer": "muscles"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Name the hardest substance in the human body.",
    "answer": "enamel"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Name the largest artery in the human body.",
    "answer": "aorta"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Name the largest gland in the human body.",
    "answer": "liver"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Osteomyelitis affects the ?????????.",
    "answer": "bones"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Peritonitis, affects the ????????.",
    "answer": "abdomen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Prosthetics deals with the making of ??????????.",
    "answer": "artificial limbs"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Tarsus, metatarsus, and phalanges are parts of a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "foot"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "The branch of medicine dealing with curing by operative procedures is ????????.",
    "answer": "surgery"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "The lack of this element in the diet is a cause of goitre.",
    "answer": "iodine"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "The largest single organ of the human body is the ????????.",
    "answer": "skin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "The medical name for the voice box is the ?????????.",
    "answer": "larynx"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "The teeth used for biting or cutting are known as ???????.",
    "answer": "incisors"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "These animals were once used to bleed the sick.",
    "answer": "leeches"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "leech(es)?",
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "These attach muscles to bones or cartilage.",
    "answer": "#tendon#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "This branch of medicine deals with old age and its diseases.",
    "answer": "geriatrics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "This disease consists of a purposeless, continual growth of white blood cells.",
    "answer": "leukemia"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "leuka?emia",
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "This fingerlike projection is attached to the large intestine.",
    "answer": "appendix"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "This is known as \"The Royal Disease\".",
    "answer": "haemophilia"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "ha?emophilia",
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "This large bean-shaped lymph gland can expand and contract as needed.",
    "answer": "spleen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "This membrane controls the amount of light entering the eye.",
    "answer": "iris"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "This organ is a small pouch that stores bile.",
    "answer": "gall bladder"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "This parasite lives in the intestines of man and animals.",
    "answer": "tapeworm"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "This small gland attached to the brain exerts a control over growth.",
    "answer": "pituitary"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Ulna, radius, and clavicle are types of ??????????.",
    "answer": "bone"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "What disease is also known as \"rubella\"?",
    "answer": "German measles"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "What hormone is produced by the adrenal glands?",
    "answer": "adrenaline"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "What is a skin specialist called?",
    "answer": "dermatologist"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "What is an organism called that lives on or in a host animal?",
    "answer": "parasite"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "What is the biggest disqualifying factor for prospective astronauts?",
    "answer": "eyesight"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "What is the medical term for cancer of the blood?",
    "answer": "leukemia"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "leuka?emia",
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "What is the name of the bone in the lower leg?",
    "answer": "tibia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "What kind of poisoning is known as plumbism?",
    "answer": "#lead# poisoning"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "What toe is the foot reflexology pressure point for the head?",
    "answer": "big toe"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Where do you find the medulla oblongata?",
    "answer": "brain"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Where in the body is the tiniest human muscle?",
    "answer": "ear"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "Which disease is also known as \"Hansen's Disease\"?",
    "answer": "leprosy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Medicine",
    "question": "With what body part is otology involved?",
    "answer": "ear"
  },
  {
    "category": "Meteorology",
    "question": "If the groundhog sees his shadow on Feb. 2, there will be how many more weeks of bad weather?",
    "answer": "six"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(six|6)",
    "category": "Meteorology",
    "question": "This dry, warm wind flows eastward down the slopes of the Rocky Mountains.",
    "answer": "Chinook"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Actor: ??????? Borgnine.",
    "answer": "Ernest"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Actor: ???????? Hackman.",
    "answer": "Gene"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Actor: ?????????? Nimoy.",
    "answer": "Leonard"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Actor: ?????????? Savalas.",
    "answer": "Telly"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "At the end of \"Planet of the Apes\" what protruded from the rocks?",
    "answer": "Statue of Liberty"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Barbara Streisand was the female lead in \"Hello, Dolly\".  Who was the male lead?",
    "answer": "Walter #Matthau#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Charles Laughton played Quasimodo in this epic film.",
    "answer": "Hunchback of Notre Dame"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Darth Vader was the villan in the movie, \"???? Wars\".",
    "answer": "Star"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Film Title: An Officer and a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "Gentleman"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Film Title: Fahrenheit ????????. (a number)",
    "answer": "451"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Film Title: The Last Days of ?????????. (a city)",
    "answer": "Pompeii"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Film Title: ?????? (a number) Leagues Under the Sea.",
    "answer": "20,000"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "20[\\,.]?000",
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Forrest ???? liked shrimp.",
    "answer": "Gump"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "He directed \"The Godfather\".",
    "answer": "Francis Ford #Coppola#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "He directed the movie E.T.",
    "answer": "Stephen Spielberg"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "ste(ph|f)en spielberg",
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "He played Superman in the 1978 movie version.",
    "answer": "Christopher Reeve"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "He starred in \"Conan the Barbarian\".",
    "answer": "Arnold #Schwarzenegger#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "He starred in, \"City Lights\".",
    "answer": "Charlie #Chaplin#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "He was known as the \"Elephant Man\".",
    "answer": "Joseph Merrick"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "He was the villain in \"Star Wars\".",
    "answer": "Darth Vader"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "His films include: Giant, Written on the Wind, and A Farewell to Arms.",
    "answer": "Rock #Hudson#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "His films include: Spartacus, The Vikings, and Ulysses.",
    "answer": "Kirk #Douglas#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "In \"Gone With the Wind\", Scarlett regains her wealth by investing in what type of business?",
    "answer": "sawmill"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "In 1975 Jack Nicholson won the best actor Oscar for his role in this film.",
    "answer": "One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "one flew over the cuckoo'?s nest",
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "In the 1996 version of \"Romeo and Juliet\", who played Juliet?",
    "answer": "Claire #Danes#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "In the film \"Bright Eyes\", Shirley Temple sang about this boat.",
    "answer": "The Good Ship #Lollipop#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "In this 1968 film the husband of an unsuspecting young wife becomes involved with a witch's coven.",
    "answer": "Rosemary's Baby"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Rosemary'?s Baby",
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "In which Disney movie is the song \"So This Is Love\"?",
    "answer": "Cinderella"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Name the Disney cartoon in which the character \"Belle\" appears.",
    "answer": "Beauty and the Beast"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Name the actor who played the leading role in \"The Good, the Bad, and the Ugly\".",
    "answer": "Clint #Eastwood#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Name the first full length color cartoon talking picture.",
    "answer": "Snow White"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Name the musical film named after a state.",
    "answer": "Oklahoma"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Nick Nolte and Eddie Murphy star in this 1982 film.",
    "answer": "48 Hours"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Peter Sellers is best known for his role as Inspector ?????????.",
    "answer": "Clouseau"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "She played Lois Lane in the 1978 film version of \"Superman\".",
    "answer": "Margot #Kidder#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "She played a Polish refugee in \"Sophie's Choice\".",
    "answer": "Meryl #Streep#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "She played the lead role in \"Coal Miner's Daughter\".",
    "answer": "Sissy #Spacek#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "She starred in the 1952 film, \"Niagara\".",
    "answer": "Marilyn Monroe"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "The first 18 minutes of this movie is black and white.",
    "answer": "Wizard of Oz"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "The song \"Matchmaker, Matchmaker\" came from which musical play?",
    "answer": "Fiddler On The Roof"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "The two rival gangs in \"West Side Story\" were the Sharks and the ?????????.",
    "answer": "Jets"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This 1974 film started a run of nostalgia culminating in the TV series \"Happy Days\".",
    "answer": "American Graffiti"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This Disney movie relies heavily on computer animation.",
    "answer": "TRON"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This actress appeared in \"St. Elmo's Fire\", \"The Scarlett Letter\", and \"Striptease\".",
    "answer": "Demi Moore"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This actress was Miss Hungary of 1936.",
    "answer": "Zsa-Zsa #Gabor#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This film starring Julie Andrews and Christopher Plummer wont he best picture Oscar for 1965.",
    "answer": "Sound of Music"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This film starring Richard Beymer and Natalie Wood won the best picture Oscar for 1961.",
    "answer": "West Side Story"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This film was an ambitious concert sequence of cartoons by Walt Disney.",
    "answer": "Fantasia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This is a classic film about a huge gorilla.",
    "answer": "King Kong"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This magic word was in the movie, \"Mary Poppins\".",
    "answer": "Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This movie directed by Woody Allen won the best picture Oscar in 1978.",
    "answer": "Annie Hall"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This movie is about the migration of poor workers from the dust bowl to the Californian fruit valleys.",
    "answer": "The #Grapes of Wrath#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This movie starring Marlon Brando won the best picture award in 1972.",
    "answer": "The #Godfather#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This was the first 3-D film.",
    "answer": "Bwana Devil"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This was the first cartoon talking picture.",
    "answer": "Steamboat Willie"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Steamboat Will(ie|y)",
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This was the sequel to \"Star Wars\".",
    "answer": "The #Empire Strikes Back#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "This was the sequel to \"The Empire Strikes Back\".",
    "answer": "Return of the Jedi"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What actor appeared in all three of these films, Straw Dogs, Midnight Cowboy, and The Graduate?",
    "answer": "Dustin #Hoffman#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What actress has received the most Oscar nominations?",
    "answer": "Katherine #Hepburn#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What actress's real name was Frances Gumm?",
    "answer": "Judy Garland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What city's police force did Charlie Chan work with?",
    "answer": "Honolulu"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What color was Bullitt's car?",
    "answer": "Green"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What country was the setting for \"The King and I\"?",
    "answer": "#Siam# (Thailand)"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What detective duo was featured in Mystery at Devil's Paw?",
    "answer": "Hardy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What does the statue of Oscar stand on?",
    "answer": "A #Reel of Film#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What famous animal character called \"Skull Island\" home?",
    "answer": "King Kong"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What film did John Wayne win his only Oscar for?",
    "answer": "True Grit"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What is Hawkeye's full name in M.A.S.H.?",
    "answer": "Benjamin Franklin Pierce"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What is the destination of the plane at the end of the film \"Casablanca\"?",
    "answer": "Lisbon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What is the name of Pearce Brosnan's first James Bond film?",
    "answer": "Goldeneye"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What is the name of the Volkswagen in the film, \"The Love Bug\"?",
    "answer": "Herbie"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What is the name of the rabbit in the film, \"Bambi\"?",
    "answer": "Thumper"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What is the name of the skunk in the film, \"Bambi\"?",
    "answer": "Flower"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What is the name of the whale that swallowed Pinocchio.",
    "answer": "Monstro"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What is the stage name of Greta Gustafson?",
    "answer": "Greta #Garbo#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What is the title of the 1996 sequel to \"Terms of Endearment\"?",
    "answer": "Morning Star"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What kind of creature was Chewbacca in \"Star Wars\"?",
    "answer": "Wookiee"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What two words are normally at the end of most movies?",
    "answer": "The End"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was \"Rocky's\" last name?",
    "answer": "Balboa"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was Citizen Kane's dying word?",
    "answer": "Rosebud"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was Dorothy's last name in \"The Wizard of Oz\"?",
    "answer": "Gale"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was Rocky's nickname in the ring?",
    "answer": "The #Italian Stallion#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was Sir Alec Guinness's role in \"Star Wars\"?",
    "answer": "Obi-Wan Kenobi"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Obi(-|)?Wan Kenobi",
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was the first film directed by Robert Redford?",
    "answer": "Ordinary People"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was the name of Ashley Wilkes' plantation in \"Gone With the Wind\"?",
    "answer": "Twelve Oaks"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was the name of Han Solo's spaceship in \"Star Wars\"?",
    "answer": "Millennium Falcon"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was the name of Luke's strange little advisor in \"The Empire Strikes Back\"?",
    "answer": "Yoda"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was the name of the motel in the film \"Psycho\"?",
    "answer": "#Bates# Motel"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "What was the setting for \"The Sound of Music\"?",
    "answer": "Austria"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Which actor said, \"Love means never having to say you're sorry\"?",
    "answer": "Ryan O'Neil"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Which character in \"Forrest Gump\" loved shrimp?",
    "answer": "Bubba"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Which character sang \"Come Out, Come Out, Wherever You Are\" in \"The Wizard of Oz\"?",
    "answer": "Glinda"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Which character sang, \"When you wish upon a star..\" in Disney's \"Pinocchio\"?",
    "answer": "Jiminy Cricket"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Which comedy duo did the famous, \"Who's on first?\" routine?",
    "answer": "Abbott and Costello"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Which planet was the \"Planet of the Apes\"?",
    "answer": "Earth"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who co-starred with Julie Andrews in \"Mary Poppins\"?",
    "answer": "Dick Van Dyke"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who hosted the 1997 Grammy Awards?",
    "answer": "Ellen #Degeneres#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who is Warren Beatty's sister?",
    "answer": "Shirley MacLaine"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who is the fastest mouse in all of Mexico?",
    "answer": "Speedy Gonzalez"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "speedy gonzale[sz]",
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who is the male lead in the \"Naked Gun\" movies?",
    "answer": "Leslie Nielsen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who is the voice of Darth Vadar?",
    "answer": "James Earl Jones"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who played \"Robin\" to Val Kilmer's \"Batman\"?",
    "answer": "Christopher #O'Donnell#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who played Brad Pitt's cop partner in the movie \"Seven\"?",
    "answer": "Morgan Freeman"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who played Dorothy in \"The Wizard of Oz\"?",
    "answer": "Judy Garland"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who played Garth in \"Wayne's World\"?",
    "answer": "Dana Carvey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who played Matt Helm in the movies?",
    "answer": "Dean Martin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who played Scarlette O'Hara in \"Gone With the Wind\"?",
    "answer": "Vivien Leigh"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who played the 'Wicked Witch of the West' in \"The Wizard of Oz\"",
    "answer": "Margaret #Hamilton#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who played the role of Richard Blaine in Casablanca?",
    "answer": "Humphrey Bogart"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who plays the character of the only escapee from Alcatraz in the movie \"The Rock\"?",
    "answer": "Sean Connery"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who portrayed Han Solo in \"Star Wars\"?",
    "answer": "Harrison Ford"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who portrayed Moses in \"The Ten Commandments\"?",
    "answer": "Charlton Heston"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who produced, directed and starred in \"Citizen Kane\"?",
    "answer": "Orson Welles"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who starred with John Travolta in the movie \"Broken Arrow\"?",
    "answer": "Christian Slater"
  },
  {
    "category": "Movie Trivia",
    "question": "Who was C3PO's sidekick in \"Star Wars\"?",
    "answer": "R2D2"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "\"He's So Fine\", \"One Fine Day\" and \"A Love So Fine\" where hits for what fine group?",
    "answer": "The #Chiffons#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "\"Joy to the World\" was a hit in 1971 for what band with three lead vocalists?",
    "answer": "Three Dog Night"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Besides \"Auld Lang Syne\" and \"For He's a Jolly Good Fellow\", what is the most frequently sung song in English?",
    "answer": "Happy Birthday"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Fifties rock \"n\" roll was revived by what greased hair, T-shirted, TV frequenting group?",
    "answer": "Sha Na Na"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Jerry Lee Lewis had Great ????? Of Fire.",
    "answer": "#balls#!"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Name Jerry Garcia's long lived group.",
    "answer": "The #Grateful Dead#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "The Who's rock musical stars Elton John.  It's called ????????.",
    "answer": "Tommy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "This female artist enjoyed sucess on both popular and country & western stations with such tunes as \"Let Me Be There\" and \"Have You Never Been Mellow.\"",
    "answer": "Olivia Newton-John"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Olivia Newton[- ]John",
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "This was the Beatle's first film.",
    "answer": "A Hard Day's Night"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(A )?Hard Day'?s Night",
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Through 1963 this duo's total record sales exceeded 18 million with successes including \"Cathy's Clown\" and \"Wake Up Little Suzie\".",
    "answer": "The #Everly Brothers#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What Procol Harem tune was based on the Bach cantata \"Sleepers Awake\"?",
    "answer": "A #Whiter Shade of Pale#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What band recorded the 1978 hit album: \"Briefcase Full of Blues\"?",
    "answer": "The #Blues Brothers#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What city is also known as Music City, U.S.A.?",
    "answer": "Nashville"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What country singer/songwriter (and sometimes actor) is known as \"the country outlaw\"?",
    "answer": "Willie #Nelson#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What entertainer is allowing one of his songs to be used in a government campaign to beat drunk driving?",
    "answer": "Michael Jackson"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What famous classical composer continued to compose great music after becoming deaf?",
    "answer": "Ludwig van #Beethoven#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What famous singer was known to give automobiles to complete strangers?",
    "answer": "Elvis Presley"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What group refused to have their pictures taken while they were not in their makeup?",
    "answer": "Kiss"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What group's biggest-ever hit was Be My Baby?",
    "answer": "The #Ronettes#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What song by Don McLean talks about the day Buddy Holly died?",
    "answer": "American Pie"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What song did Aretha Franklin sing in \"The Blues Brothers\"?",
    "answer": "Think"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What was Elvis Presley's wife's name?",
    "answer": "Priscilla"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What was The Beatles' biggest hit single?",
    "answer": "Hey Jude"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "What's the name of B.B. King's guitar?",
    "answer": "Lucille"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Which of Paul Simon's musical characters was told to hop on the bus?",
    "answer": "Gus"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Who invented the electrical bass?",
    "answer": "Leo #Fender#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Who recorded the 1957 hit \"Tammy\"?",
    "answer": "Debby Reynolds"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Debb(ie|y) Reynolds",
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Who recorded the lengthy song: \"In-A-Gadda-Da-Vida\" in 1969?",
    "answer": "Iron Butterfly"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Who was the first singer in Genesis?",
    "answer": "Peter Gabriel"
  },
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "question": "Whose theme song was Back In The Saddle Again?",
    "answer": "Gene #Autry#'s"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mythology",
    "question": "The sea gods had a three-pronged spear called a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "trident"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mythology",
    "question": "This Greek mountain was known as the home of the gods.",
    "answer": "Olympus"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mythology",
    "question": "What has no reflection, no shadow, and can't stand the smell of garlic?",
    "answer": "vampire"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mythology",
    "question": "What's heaven to fallen Norse warriors?",
    "answer": "Valhalla"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mythology",
    "question": "Where did Robin Hood supposedly live?",
    "answer": "Sherwood Forest"
  },
  {
    "category": "Mythology",
    "question": "Which ancient continent is said to be submerged?",
    "answer": "Atlantis"
  },
  {
    "category": "Natural History",
    "question": "Name the largest of the dinosaurs.",
    "answer": "brachiosaurus"
  },
  {
    "category": "Natural History",
    "question": "The remains of prehistoric organisms that have been preserved in rocks are called ????????.",
    "answer": "fossils"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "A \"sirocco\" refers to a type of ??????????.",
    "answer": "wind"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "A calm ocean region near the equator.",
    "answer": "#doldrum#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "A coral island consisting of a ring of rock enclosing a central lagoon is a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "atoll"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "A great wave resulting from an earthquakes is called a (an) ????????.",
    "answer": "tsunami"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "A group of gorillas is known as a ???????????.",
    "answer": "band"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "A group of kangaroos is known as a ???????.",
    "answer": "troop"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "A hot spring which shoots steam into the air is a ???????.",
    "answer": "geyser"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "A one-humped camel is called a ?????????.",
    "answer": "dromedary"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "A relationship between two different types of organism which live together for their mutual benefit.",
    "answer": "symbiosis"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "A terrapin is a type of ?????????.",
    "answer": "turtle"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "An animal is a bird if it has ???????.",
    "answer": "feathers"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "An animal is a fish if it has ?????????.",
    "answer": "gills"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Corolla, filament and stigma are parts of a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "flower"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Dense sea-water swamps along coasts of hot countries are called ????????.",
    "answer": "mangroves"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Dogs bark.  What do donkeys do?",
    "answer": "bray"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Excluding man, what is the longest-lived land mammal?",
    "answer": "elephant"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Fandible, lateral line, and dorsal fin are parts of a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "fish"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "From what animal is \"ambergis\" obtained?",
    "answer": "sperm whale"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "How man legs does a crab have?",
    "answer": "ten"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(ten|10)",
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "How many teats does a cow have?",
    "answer": "four"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(four|4)",
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "How many tentacles does a squid have?",
    "answer": "ten"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(ten|10)",
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Imperial, Buck, and Luna are types of ?????????.",
    "answer": "moth"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Knife, Clown, and Pencil are types of ??????????.",
    "answer": "fish"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Linseed oil is obtained from the seed of which plant?",
    "answer": "flax"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Maxillary palps, abdomen, and metathorax are parts of a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "insect"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the fastest land animal over a prolonged distance (1,000 yd. plus)",
    "answer": "antelope"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the heaviest breed of domestic dog.",
    "answer": "St. #Bernard#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the heaviest flying bird of prey.",
    "answer": "condor"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the largest living bird.",
    "answer": "ostrich"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the largest web-footed bird.",
    "answer": "albatross"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the longest venomous snake.",
    "answer": "cobra"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the mammal living at the highest altitude.",
    "answer": "yak"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the most venomous spider.",
    "answer": "black widow"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the only native North American marsupial.",
    "answer": "opossum"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the slowest moving land mammal.",
    "answer": "sloth"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the smallest breed of dog.",
    "answer": "chihuahua"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Name the wild dogs of Australia.",
    "answer": "dingo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Paper is made from the pulp of ?????.",
    "answer": "wood"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Snakes are reptiles.  What are frogs?",
    "answer": "amphibians"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Some animals spend the winter in a sleep-like state known as ?????????.",
    "answer": "hibernation"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "The \"canebrake\", \"timber\" and \"pygmy\" are types of what?",
    "answer": "rattlesnake"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "The fins of which fish are made into a soup?",
    "answer": "shark"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "The four stages in the life-cycle of an insect are: egg, adult, pupa, and ????????.",
    "answer": "larva"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "The koala bear eats the leaves from this tree.",
    "answer": "eucalyptus"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "These marine crustaceans often attach themselves to the hulls of ships.",
    "answer": "barnacles"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "barnacles?",
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This African animal kills the most people.",
    "answer": "crocodile"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This animal is armed with bony plates and rolls up into a ball if frightened.",
    "answer": "armadillo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This animal is kept as a house pet to kill cobras.",
    "answer": "mongoose"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This animal is normally measured in \"hands\".",
    "answer": "horse"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This animal is the symbol of the U.S. Democratic Party.",
    "answer": "donkey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This animal is the symbol of the U.S. Republican Party.",
    "answer": "elephant"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This animal's name is the same as that given to a high church official.",
    "answer": "cardinal"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This animal's shell is used to make attractive jewelry.",
    "answer": "abalone"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This bird lays its eggs in the nests of other birds.",
    "answer": "cuckoo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This is the largest of the deer family.",
    "answer": "moose"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This is the main food of the blue whale.",
    "answer": "plankton"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This is the only mammal with four knees.",
    "answer": "elephant"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This order of insects contains the most species.",
    "answer": "beetle"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This organic gem is a deep red secretion from a marine animal.",
    "answer": "coral"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This small animal is trained to hunt rats and rabbits.",
    "answer": "ferret"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This two ton animal can gallop at over 50 miles an hour.",
    "answer": "rhinoceros"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "This ugly creature has patches of red on his rear-end.",
    "answer": "mandrill"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "Walrus tusks are made of ????????.",
    "answer": "ivory"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What are the pouched animals called?",
    "answer": "marsupials"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What bird is an excellent swimmer, but can't fly?",
    "answer": "penguin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What does a camel store in its hump?",
    "answer": "fat"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What fish is the fastest?",
    "answer": "sailfish"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is a group of larks called?",
    "answer": "exaltation"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is a group of peacocks called?",
    "answer": "muster"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is a group of whales called?",
    "answer": "pod"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is a male goose called?",
    "answer": "gander"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is a male swan called?",
    "answer": "cob"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is a male swine called?",
    "answer": "boar"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is a young goose called?",
    "answer": "gosling"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is a young swan called?",
    "answer": "cygnet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is an emasculated stallion called?",
    "answer": "gelding"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is another term for a black leopard?",
    "answer": "panther"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is the horn of a rhinoceros made of?",
    "answer": "hair"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is the only dog that doesn't have a pink tongue?",
    "answer": "chow"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What is the world's longest snake?",
    "answer": "python"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What large herbivore sleeps only one hour a night?",
    "answer": "antelope"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What name is given to a female calf?",
    "answer": "heifer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What plant is opium derived from?",
    "answer": "poppy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What travels in gaggles?",
    "answer": "geese"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What type of animal is a wallaby?",
    "answer": "marsupial"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What type of animal lives in a formicary?",
    "answer": "ant"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What word is used for a female fox?",
    "answer": "vixen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What word is used for a female sheep?",
    "answer": "ewe"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What word is used for a male ass? (Other than that the word used for that #*?^*&%@! ex-boyfriend.)",
    "answer": "jack"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What word is used for a male deer?",
    "answer": "buck"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nature",
    "question": "What word is used for a male duck?",
    "answer": "drake"
  },
  {
    "category": "Neture",
    "question": "What do oak trees grow from?",
    "answer": "acorns"
  },
  {
    "category": "Not Telling ;-)",
    "question": "What would be kept in an \"aviary\"?",
    "answer": "#bird#s"
  },
  {
    "category": "Not Telling ;-)",
    "question": "Where is the Ocean of Storms located?",
    "answer": "On the #moon#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Not Telling ;-)",
    "question": "Who is Robert Zimmermann?",
    "answer": "Bob Dylan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Not Telling ;-P",
    "question": "What are white dwarfs and red giants?",
    "answer": "stars"
  },
  {
    "category": "Not telling ;-P",
    "question": "What are these: chrysolite, beryl, jasper, and tourmaline?",
    "answer": "gems"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nursery Rhymes",
    "question": "Jack and Jill went up a ???? to fetch a pail of water?",
    "answer": "hill"
  },
  {
    "category": "Nursery Rhymes",
    "question": "Name the nursery rhyme mother whos last name is that of a bird?",
    "answer": "goose"
  },
  {
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "The energy which a body possesses by virtue of its motion is called ????????.",
    "answer": "kinetic"
  },
  {
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "The pivot point of a lever is called the ?????????.",
    "answer": "fulcrum"
  },
  {
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "The process of water changing to water vapor is known as ???????.",
    "answer": "evaporation"
  },
  {
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "The rate of change of velocity is known as ?????????.",
    "answer": "acceleration"
  },
  {
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "The visible spectrum of light ranges from red to ????????.",
    "answer": "violet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "True Or False: Contrary to popular belief, a lightbulb actually absorbs darkness?",
    "answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "Two 1.5 volt batteries, when connected in series, produces _ volts.",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "Water freezes at _ degrees Celcius.",
    "answer": "zero"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(zero|0)",
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "Water freezes at ?? degrees Fahrenheit.",
    "answer": "thirty two"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(thirty[- ]two|32)",
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "What is measured by a Geiger counter?",
    "answer": "radioactivity"
  },
  {
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "When light waves pass from one medium into another they change direction.  This is called ?????????.",
    "answer": "refraction"
  },
  {
    "category": "Physics",
    "question": "Work done, equals force multiplied by ????????.",
    "answer": "distance"
  },
  {
    "category": "Politics",
    "question": "For what does O.P.E.C. stand?",
    "answer": "The Organization of Petroleum Exporting Countries"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Organi[sz]ation of Petroleum Exporting Countries",
    "category": "Politics",
    "question": "He was elected President of France, in 1981.",
    "answer": "Francios #Mitterrand#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Politics",
    "question": "Name Ronald Reagan's first wife.",
    "answer": "Wyman"
  },
  {
    "category": "Presidents",
    "question": "U.S. President, Woodrow ??????????.",
    "answer": "Wilson"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "How is the state of Mississippi spelled?",
    "answer": "Mississippi"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "Name the circular plastic media you put in a CD-ROM drive.",
    "answer": "CD"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "On a standard computer keyboard, this is the letter just to the right of Z.",
    "answer": "x"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "The longest key on your keyboard is the ????? bar.",
    "answer": "space"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "The season ?????? comes right after Spring.",
    "answer": "summer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "There are ?? seconds in a minute.",
    "answer": "sixty"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(sixty|60)",
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "This is required to make all electric things work?",
    "answer": "electricity"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "What color is a blue crayon?",
    "answer": "blue"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "What color is a green crayon?",
    "answer": "green"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "What color is a red crayon?",
    "answer": "red"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "What company makes Microsoft Windows 2000?",
    "answer": "microsoft"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "Whats radar spelled backwards?",
    "answer": "radar"
  },
  {
    "category": "Quick! Quick!",
    "question": "Whats the abbreviation for United States of America?",
    "answer": "USA"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "U.?S.?A.?",
    "category": "Quick! Where's my mirror? ;-",
    "question": "When spelled backwards, the word \"retupmoc\" becomes what?",
    "answer": "computer"
  },
  {
    "category": "Religion",
    "question": "Followers of the Unification Church are called ????????.",
    "answer": "Moonies"
  },
  {
    "category": "Religion",
    "question": "He led the Israelites out of Egypt.",
    "answer": "Moses"
  },
  {
    "category": "Religion",
    "question": "He was the first King of the Hebrews.",
    "answer": "Saul"
  },
  {
    "category": "Religion",
    "question": "He was the second King of Israel.",
    "answer": "David"
  },
  {
    "category": "Religion",
    "question": "In what month is Christmas observed?",
    "answer": "December"
  },
  {
    "category": "Religion",
    "question": "Name the holiest day in the Jewish calendar.",
    "answer": "Yom Kippur"
  },
  {
    "category": "Religion",
    "question": "On which mountain did Moses receive the Ten Commandments?",
    "answer": "Sinai"
  },
  {
    "category": "Religion",
    "question": "Which city is sacred to Jews, Christians, and Muslims?",
    "answer": "Jerusalem"
  },
  {
    "category": "Religion",
    "question": "Who founded Mormonism?",
    "answer": "Joseph #Smith#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Religion",
    "question": "Who founded the People's Temple Commune?",
    "answer": "Jim Jones"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "A flat-bottomed conical laboratory flask with a narrow neck is called a(n) ??????????.",
    "answer": "#erlenmeyer# flask"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "A phrenologist reads ?????????.",
    "answer": "skulls"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "A point to which rays of light converge is called a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "focus"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "A shallow dish with a cover, used for science specimens is a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "#petri# dish"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Acetylsalicylic acid is more commonly known as ?????????.",
    "answer": "aspirin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Botany and Zoology combined make up the science of ???????.",
    "answer": "biology"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "By what chemical process do plants manufacture food?",
    "answer": "photosynthesis"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "By what name is Lysergic acid diethylamide better known?",
    "answer": "LSD"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Cetology is the study of ????????.",
    "answer": "whales"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Circuits can be wired in series or in ?????????.",
    "answer": "parallel"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Cocci, Spirilla, and Streptococci are types of ????????.",
    "answer": "bacteria"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Deoxyribonucleic acid is better known as ??????????.",
    "answer": "DNA"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Dermatitis affects the ??????????.",
    "answer": "skin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Epidermal cells, palisade cells, and veins are parts of a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "leaf"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Ethylene glycol is frequently used in automobiles.. How?",
    "answer": "anti-freeze"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "anti[- ]?freeze",
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Forked, Sheet, and Ball are types of ??????????.",
    "answer": "lightning"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Growing plants in liquids rather than soil is known as ????????.",
    "answer": "hydroponics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "He designed the first feasible automobile with an internal combustion engine.",
    "answer": "Karl Freidrich #Benz#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "He invented \"bifocal\" lenses for eyeglasses.",
    "answer": "Benjamin Franklin"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "He is known for his theory of \"Evolution\".",
    "answer": "Charles #Darwin#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "He transmitted radio signals across the Atlantic in 1901.",
    "answer": "Enrico #Marconi#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "He wrote \"Sexual Behaviour in the Human Male\" in 1948.",
    "answer": "Alfred #Kinsey#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "How many degrees does the earth rotate each hour?",
    "answer": "fifteen"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(fifteen|15)",
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "In which country was the match invented?",
    "answer": "France"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Nitrous oxide is better known as ??????????.",
    "answer": "laughing gas"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Nuclear membrane, cytoplasm, and nucleus are parts of a(n) ??????????.",
    "answer": "cell"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Pulp, crown, and root are parts of a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "tooth"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Quinine is added to water to make ???????.",
    "answer": "tonic water"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Sound Navigation Ranging is better known as ?????????.",
    "answer": "sonar"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "The Kelvin scale is used to measure ?????????.",
    "answer": "temperature"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "The filament of a regular light bulb is usually made of ????????.",
    "answer": "tungsten"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "The instrument used in geometry to measure angles is a(n) ???????.",
    "answer": "protractor"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "The name for the Russian equivalent of Skylab is ????????.",
    "answer": "Salyut"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "The second space shuttle was named ??????????.",
    "answer": "Columbia"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "The vernal equinox is the beginning of ????????.",
    "answer": "spring"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "This Russian scientist used dogs to study conditioned reflexes.",
    "answer": "Ivan #Pavlov#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "This is like an airplane but has its propeller on top instead.",
    "answer": "helicopter"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "This is the reading system used by the blind.",
    "answer": "Braille"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "This science deals with the motion of projectiles.",
    "answer": "ballistics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "To make a car go backwards you have to put it in what gear?",
    "answer": "reverse"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "What are these: Ceres, Juno, Iris, and Flora?",
    "answer": "asteroids"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "What branch of science studies the motion of air and the forces acting on objects in air?",
    "answer": "aerodynamics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "What did Lewis E. Waterman invent in 1884?",
    "answer": "fountain pen"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "What does the \"lithosphere\" refer to?",
    "answer": "The earth's crust"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Earth'?s crust",
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "What does the Binet test measure?",
    "answer": "intelligence"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Who invented dynamite?",
    "answer": "Alfred Nobel"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "question": "Who is known as the father of genetics?",
    "answer": "Gregor #Mendel#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As bold as ???????.",
    "answer": "brass"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As clean as a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "whistle"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As clear as a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "bell"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As cute as a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "button"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As easy as ????????.",
    "answer": "pie"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As fit as a(n) ??????????.",
    "answer": "fiddle"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As good as ?????????.",
    "answer": "gold"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As graceful as a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "swan"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As large as ????????.",
    "answer": "life"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As loud as ?????????.",
    "answer": "thunder"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As pale as a(n) ???????????.",
    "answer": "ghost"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As pleased as ?????????.",
    "answer": "punch"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As pretty as a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "picture"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As proud as a(n) ???????????.",
    "answer": "peacock"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As quiet as a(n) ?????????.",
    "answer": "mouse"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As sick as a(n) ???????????.",
    "answer": "dog"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As sly as a(n) ??????????.",
    "answer": "fox"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "As smart as a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "whip"
  },
  {
    "category": "Similes",
    "question": "Fresh as a(n) ??????????????.",
    "answer": "daisy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Baseball: The Baltimore ????????.",
    "answer": "Orioles"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Baseball: The Toronto ?????????.",
    "answer": "Bluejays"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Basketball: The Boston ???????????.",
    "answer": "Celtics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Basketball: The Denver ?????????.",
    "answer": "Nuggets"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Basketball: The Los Angeles ?????????.",
    "answer": "Lakers"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Basketball: The New York ??????????.",
    "answer": "Knicks"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Basketball: The Seattle ????????.",
    "answer": "Supersonics"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Basketball: The Utah ????????.",
    "answer": "Jazz"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Football: The Baltimore ????????.",
    "answer": "Colts"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Football: The Buffalo ???????.",
    "answer": "Bills"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Football: The Cincinnati ?????????.",
    "answer": "Bengals"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Football: The Cleveland ????????.",
    "answer": "Browns"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Football: The Dallas ?????????.",
    "answer": "Cowboys"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Football: The Denver ?????????.",
    "answer": "Broncos"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Football: The Miami ??????????.",
    "answer": "Dolphins"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Football: The Minnesota ???????.",
    "answer": "Vikings"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Football: The New Orleans ??????????.",
    "answer": "Saints"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Football: The Seattle ???????.",
    "answer": "Seahawks"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "He holds the NHL record for the most goals scored during the regular season.",
    "answer": "Wayne #Gretzky#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "He was the NBA, MVP in 1976, 77, and 80.",
    "answer": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "Kareem Abdul[- ]?Jabbar",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Boston ???????????.",
    "answer": "Bruins"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Buffalo ?????????.",
    "answer": "Sabres"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Calgary ??????????.",
    "answer": "Flames"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Chicago ?????????.",
    "answer": "Blackhawks"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "black ?hawks",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Detroit ????????.",
    "answer": "Red Wings"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Edmonton ??????????.",
    "answer": "Oilers"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Los Angeles ????????.",
    "answer": "Kings"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Montreal ????????.",
    "answer": "Canadians"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Pittsburgh ??????????.",
    "answer": "Penguins"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The St. Louis ??????????.",
    "answer": "Blues"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Toronto ???????.",
    "answer": "Maple Leafs"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Hockey: The Vancouver ????????.",
    "answer": "Canucks"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many feet high is a basketball net?",
    "answer": "ten"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(ten|10)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many games must you win to win a normal set in tennis?",
    "answer": "six"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(six|6)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many minutes is a major penalty in hockey?",
    "answer": "five"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(five|5)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many minutes is each period of hockey?",
    "answer": "twenty"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(twenty|20)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many players are there on a soccer team?",
    "answer": "eleven"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(eleven|11)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many players are there on a water polo team?",
    "answer": "seven"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(seven|7)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many players make up a field hockey team?",
    "answer": "eleven"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(eleven|11)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many points are awarded for a safety touch in football?",
    "answer": "two"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(two|2)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many referees work a soccer game?",
    "answer": "one"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(one|1)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many seams are there on a football? (American)",
    "answer": "four"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(four|4)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "How many sides does a home-plate have?",
    "answer": "five"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(five|5)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In pro football a \"sudden death\" period lasts how many minutes long?",
    "answer": "fifteen"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(fifteen|15)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In ten-pin bowling, how many points does a perfect game consist of?",
    "answer": "three hundred"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(three hundred|300)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In this team sport each player gets a chance to play every position.",
    "answer": "volleyball"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In what sport is the Heisman trophy awarded?",
    "answer": "American #football#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which city is the Cotton Bowl played?",
    "answer": "Dallas"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which city is the Hockey Hall of Fame located?",
    "answer": "Toronto"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which game or sport is a \"Zamboni\" used?",
    "answer": "hockey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which sport is a \"hole-in-one\" possible?",
    "answer": "golf"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which sport is the America's Cup awarded?",
    "answer": "sailing"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which sport is the Cy Young Trophy awarded?",
    "answer": "baseball"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which sport is the Davis Cup awarded?",
    "answer": "tennis"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which sport is the term \"love\" used?",
    "answer": "tennis"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which sport is the term \"wishbone\" used?",
    "answer": "football"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which sport is the term, \"Hang ten\" used?",
    "answer": "surfing"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "In which sport would you find the \"slapshot\".",
    "answer": "hockey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Name the hockey trophy awarded to the player demonstrating the best sportsmanship.",
    "answer": "The #Lady Byng# Trophy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "On what type of surface are the tennis matches at Wimbledon played?",
    "answer": "grass"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "She was \"Sports Illustrated's\" first female \"Sportsman of the Year\".",
    "answer": "Billie Jean King"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Soccer: The New York ?????????.",
    "answer": "Cosmos"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "The 1976 Summer Olympics were held in this city.",
    "answer": "Montreal"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "The Japanese martial art of fencing is called ????????.",
    "answer": "kendo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "The person who carries the golfer's clubs is called a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "caddie"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "cadd(ie|y)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "The white marks intersecting each five yard line are called ????????.",
    "answer": "#hash# marks"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "This is the most coveted trophy in Candian football.",
    "answer": "Grey Cup"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "This sport allows substitutions without a stoppage in play.",
    "answer": "hockey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "This sport is called the \"American pastime\".",
    "answer": "baseball"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "This team won their first World Series in 1969.",
    "answer": "New York #Mets#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "This traditional Japanese wrestling sport takes place in a circular ring.",
    "answer": "sumo"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Two under par on a hole of golf is called a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "eagle"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What are large snow bumps known as in skiing terms?",
    "answer": "moguls"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What do runners pass to each other in a relay race?",
    "answer": "baton"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What do the letters ERA mean in baseball?",
    "answer": "Earned Run Average"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What does TKO stand for?",
    "answer": "Technical Knock Out"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What football player rushed for 2,003 yards in 1973?",
    "answer": "OJ #Simpson#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What game features the largest ball?",
    "answer": "earthball"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What is it called when a football team loses possession of the ball due to a misplay?",
    "answer": "turnover"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What is the heaviest class of weight-lifting?",
    "answer": "super heavyweight"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What number wood is a driver in golf?",
    "answer": "one"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(one|1)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What sport do the Harlem Globetrotters play?",
    "answer": "basketball"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What sport has a hooker in a scrum?",
    "answer": "rugby"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What sport would you helicopter to the Bugaboos for?",
    "answer": "skiing"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What trophy is awarded to the winner of the NHL play-offs?",
    "answer": "Stanley Cup"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What vehicles are involved in the \"Tour de France\"?",
    "answer": "bicycles"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What was football player Dick Lane's nickname?",
    "answer": "Night Train"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "What's the nickname of the University of Georgia football team?",
    "answer": "Bulldogs"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Where are the U.S. Tennis Open Championships held?",
    "answer": "#Flushing Meadows#, NY"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Which NFL team's defensive unit was nicknamed \"The Purple People Eaters\"?",
    "answer": "Minnesota #Vikings#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Which country won the World Cup of Soccer in 1982.",
    "answer": "Italy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Which football team was nicknamed the \"Orange Crush\"?",
    "answer": "Denver #Broncos#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Which is the only position in soccer allowed to handle the ball?",
    "answer": "goalkeeper"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(goalie|goalkeeper)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Which position is usually played by the tallest member on a basketball team?",
    "answer": "centre"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "cent(er|re)",
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Which sport has a movement called a \"telemark\"?",
    "answer": "skiing"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Which sport uses stones and brooms?",
    "answer": "curling"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Which swimming stroke is named after an insect?",
    "answer": "butterfly"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Who was known as the \"Sultan of Swat\"?",
    "answer": "Babe Ruth"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Who was the 1978 Wimbledon Women's Singles champ?",
    "answer": "Martina Navratilova"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Who was the first NHL player to score 50 goals in one season?",
    "answer": "Maurice #Richard# <-- pronounced \"Reeee-shard\""
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "Who was the first to win the grand slam of tennis?",
    "answer": "Don #Budge#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sport",
    "question": "With which sport is Chris Evert Lloyd identified?",
    "answer": "tennis"
  },
  {
    "category": "Stand on your heads.... NOW! ;-)",
    "question": "When read upside down, what does the term \"umop apisdn\" signify?",
    "answer": "upside down"
  },
  {
    "category": "Stupid things to do ;-)",
    "question": "If you look at the sun long enough, you go ?????.",
    "answer": "blind"
  },
  {
    "category": "Summertime",
    "question": "This is the sandy area nearest the ocean.",
    "answer": "beach"
  },
  {
    "category": "TV Trivia",
    "question": "What did TVs IMF stand for?",
    "answer": "Impossible Mission Forces"
  },
  {
    "category": "TV Trivia",
    "question": "What was the first network series devoted entirely to rock and roll?",
    "answer": "American Bandstand"
  },
  {
    "category": "TV Trivia",
    "question": "Who was Carl in Five Easy Pieces before going to Walton's Mountain?",
    "answer": "Waite"
  },
  {
    "category": "TV Trivia",
    "question": "Who was Chief Marshall of the Mickey Mouse Club?",
    "answer": "Walt Disney"
  },
  {
    "category": "Triplets",
    "question": "Hook, line and ???????????.",
    "answer": "sinker"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "\"7X\" was used to refer to the secret ingredient of which drink?",
    "answer": "Coca Cola"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "A \"pigskin\" is another name for a(n) ????????.",
    "answer": "football"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "A can of Pepsi holds ?? fluid ounces.",
    "answer": "twelve"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(twelve|12)",
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "A foot-long ruler is ?? inches long.",
    "answer": "twelve"
  },
  {
    "regexp": "(twelve|12)",
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "Most men do this each morning, using a razor.",
    "answer": "shave"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "Most people wear a watch on their ???? wrist.",
    "answer": "left"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "Name the implement that removes water from your windshield on your car?",
    "answer": "wiper"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "Traffic Trivia:  Red means stop, ????? means go.",
    "answer": "green"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "What US state has the Worlds Champion Chili Cookoff every year?",
    "answer": "Texas"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "What bit of Bobby Goldsboro syrup focused on a dying young wife?",
    "answer": "honey"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "What did Sally Rogers always wear in her hair?",
    "answer": "a #bow#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "What does the typical American eat 263 of each year? not pizza!!",
    "answer": "eggs"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "What game show had people dressed up funny?",
    "answer": "Let's #Make A Deal#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "What is Grimace of the McDonald's characters?",
    "answer": "A #tastebud#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "What was Simple Simon fishing for in his mother's pail?",
    "answer": "whale"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "What was the name of the Akla-Seltzer boy?",
    "answer": "Speedy"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "What was the name of the dog in RCA Victor's trademark?",
    "answer": "Nipper"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "What's the telephone area code for Chicago?",
    "answer": "312"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "Where did Howdy Doody live?",
    "answer": "Doodyville"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "Where were Archie and Edith Bunker's chairs enshrined?",
    "answer": "The #Smithsonian# Institute"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "Who is also known as Mr. Warmth?",
    "answer": "Don #Rickles#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Trivia",
    "question": "Who is known as \"the world's oldest teenager\"?",
    "answer": "Dick #Clark#"
  },
  {
    "category": "Word Asssociation",
    "question": "Ball and ????????.",
    "answer": "chain"
  },
  {
    "category": "Word Asssociation",
    "question": "Peace and ?????????.",
    "answer": "quiet"
  },
  {
    "category": "Word Asssociation",
    "question": "Which word is related to these three: nap, walk, call?",
    "answer": "cat"
  },
  {
    "category": "Word Asssociation",
    "question": "Which word is related to these three: painting, bowl, nail?",
    "answer": "finger"
  },
  {
    "category": "Word Asssociation",
    "question": "Which word is related to these three: rat, blue, cottage?",
    "answer": "cheese"
  },
  {
    "category": "Words containing 'for'",
    "question": "A castle or enclosed place.",
    "answer": "FORt"
  },
  {
    "category": "Words containing 'for'",
    "question": "Make holes through something.",
    "answer": "perFORate"
  },
  {
    "category": "Words containing 'for'",
    "question": "Many trees.",
    "answer": "FORest"
  },
  {
    "category": "Words containing 'for'",
    "question": "Pardon.",
    "answer": "FORgive"
  },
  {
    "category": "Words containing 'ten'",
    "question": "A choice cut of meat.",
    "answer": "tenderloin"
  }
]
